Clothes
Saki
You have one new message.
A
[K-Coupons] Coupons for You
From: Kushida Records
This week's featured release
now streaming at our online store!
This summer, Kushida is where it's at!
Kushida Card
Double Chance Campaign
We're giving out 10,000 points in our raffle!!
Come in!
Saki-chan?
Oh, you're all packed.
What is it?
I'm going to City Hall.
Do you want me to come too?
You need to fill out a lot of paperwork, right?
You don't have to.
You're hanging out with
Natsumi-chan today, aren't you?
We don't have something planned every day.
Saki-chan, why don't you invite them out for a change?
Aizawa Natsumi
Hanaki Yuka
Tamaki Rinko
Aizawa Natsumi
Hanaki Yuka
Tamaki Rinko
Free today? Want to do something?
This doesn't feel right.
Why hasn't Yuka done anything crazy today?
Text Received
Aizawa Natsumi
Natsumi?
Hello?
Saki, are you home? Did Yuka call you yet?
Not yet.
Did something happen?
No! A trip!
We're going on a trip!
Flowing off the edge, the end of a dream
A world where we always search for sensations
What kind of spirit will you glow with as you jump into tomorrow?
Just tell me
The beat of the future, a drumbeat in my ears
Do you hear the start of my melody calling you?
I'm ready! The sky is so blue and so high
I'll never forget this moment as we cried together
I promise that I'll keep on running straight ahead
The moment when we understood
shun
stop
road
is a precious non-stop road
If we could be together,
zu
tto
i
ssho
ni
if I could be with you
ki
mi
to
i
ssho
ni
And be happy it would be the best I think
If we could be together, if I could be with you
zu
tto
i
ssho
ssho
ga
That's the key to the world
Are you ready? So believe in the moment
And be amazed at what you have, your determination
Your smile is just so strong and blindingly bright
shii
I'll look straight ahead and say
shin
wa
I won't give in, I've a non-stop mind
stop
mind
A Summer-Colored Miracle
Come see Bali!
Have fun all day and all night!
Five days on the island of Bali!
Overseas?
Down for Trips
I don't have a passport.
Fine.
Have it your way!
Three days in Okinawa!
I'm scared of planes.
Seriously?
How about Hokkaido, then?
Oh! I want some Genghis Khan!
Crab?
Can you afford it?
With an advance on my allowance... 20,000 to 30,000.
Same here.
That's a "no."
Can't we go by train?
The Hokutosei?
Wait, is that a train?
That would cost more, you know.
Come on, Saki. All you do is complain.
Then where do you think we should go?
Where do you want to go, Saki?
Me?
I'll go wherever—
"Wherever" is nowhere!
My plans are all going down the drain!
What about Kyoto?
Yeah.
Hey look, "The Maiko Experience."
That sounds like fun!
That's like a school trip thing.
"School trip"?
Oh right, the school trip...
You can't come with us next year...
I wish we could go together...
We can't do anything about it.
Why don't you come back just for that week?
I can't do that.
We've already decided that we're moving.
Don't say things like that.
Sorry.
I'm going home.
What about the trip?
We can't decide on where to go.
But we should go somewhere!
Where is "somewhere"?
Um...
Tokyo?
I want to see where you're moving to!
Why don't we all go check it out?
Like a school trip for the four of us!
Yeah! I want to go to Tokyo!
Let's go sightseeing!
The Skytree.
I want to see the Budokan! And the Dome!
All the concert halls?
Hang on a second!
There isn't anything interesting where I'm moving!
Why not?
Can't we?
I want to go to Tokyo!
Tokyo! Tokyo!
That's not it.
It's in Tokyo, but...
it's an island.
11 hours by boat?!
Just getting there is an adventure!
Yeah. You get onboard at Takeshiba.
It leaves at night and arrives in the morning.
I wonder if they still have room.
Should I call?
No, I'm okay.
H-Hello?
I'd like tickets for a boat.
Yes.
Four middle school students.
Found it!
Wow, it smells like mothballs!
Guess I have to buy one.
You're going to the island?
Saki,
I'm sorry we have to move at a time like this.
But it's a good place.
I'm sure you'll like it too.
I can't do anything about it.
I have to go to school.
Did you do the English homework?
They're going to call on me today.
That means they're calling on me too.
Rin, do you have your dictionary?
I forgot it.
I have mine with me.
Didn't you bring yours, Yuka?
Nah, it's too heavy.
Aww, come on...
What am I supposed to do now?
Shoot! It's the teacher!
I'm done for!
Why did I have a dream like that?
I like this one!
But does it look good on me?
Try it on?
Yeah. I'll be back in a minute.
Aren't you going to buy one?
No, I already have one.
Right.
But don't you feel like getting one when you see them?
Oh! This one's nice!
Here. In case you feel sick.
Thanks.
Do we have any more for the train and boat too?
Call me if anything happens.
Okay.
I hope you like the island too.
I'll be back in a few days.
It looks like it's going to rain.
Rinko, did you bring an umbr—
Isn't that bag a bit small?
Even I'm bringing one...
this big.
Mama said that traveling light is
better in case something happens.
Is there something on the island I don't know about?
Saki.
You two are early.
Where's Yuka?
She said she'd be late.
Yuka...
Can't do anything about that.
I'll just give you yours first.
A School Trip
for the Four of Us
Rain or Shine
A guide?
Wow! Did you make this?
We don't get chances like this often, you know.
You've always been kind of uptight.
It's almost like a real school trip.
Though, thanks to someone, we're already behind schedule.
Hey, everyone! Sorry I'm late!
That's huge.
Farewell, Shimoda.
We part for a short time.
What's wrong?
I left the CD inside my CD player!
Why did you bring that with you?
I wanted to listen to it with you!
It's on my player.
I love you, Rin!
Ready?
I'm starting it.
mugiwara boushi wa mou kieta
All the straw hats are long gone
tanbo no kaeru wa mou kieta
The frogs in the fields are long gone
sore demo matteru natsuyasumi
But still I wait for summer vacation
Why can't we live here?
Can you afford it?
neesan sensei mou inai
That young teacher is now gone
No...
So many people!
Next stop: Hamamatsuchou. Hamamatsuchou.
kirei na sensei mou inai
That pretty teacher is now gone
Please exit to your—
Hey, which way is the ferry?
Let's see... Takeshiba Pier is...
sore demo matteru natsuyasumi
But still I wait for summer vacation
Wow, it's dark.
It's Tokyo Tower!
Tokyo Tower!
It looks amazing!
It's so cute.
Take one of me!
Tokyo Tower!
Really cute.
Now with you!
Are you sure you didn't want to visit somewhere like this?
Yeah. We're not here to go sightseeing.
Why did you want to see where I'm moving to?
Doesn't everyone get curious? Why do you ask?
No reason.
I've never been there either, so I don't know if it's going to be fun or not.
Saki! Natsumi! Let's take one together!
Don't be so loud!
Hurry up already!
Let's take a lot if it looks good!
Look what happened because you took your time taking pictures!
Sorry!
Wow, it's huge!
Let's go.
Hey, let's go on deck!
Rainbow Bridge!
You're right!
It's so pretty.
Farewell, Tokyo.
A Summer-Colored Miracle
We're not leaving Tokyo, though.
I heard the ship would rock, but it's not moving at all!
It's going to start rocking once we leave Tokyo Bay.
Seriously?
Did you bring something for seasickness?
Yeah. Did you?
I'm fine! I'm fine!
We need to put down our bags first.
What's this mean?
Oh. It means they might not take us to the island.
Why?
If the waves get too rough, the ship can't stop.
Then what will happen?
We'll turn back halfway there?
What?!
Let's see...
The two by the wall and the two in the middle.
Dibs on this one!
There's a number on your ticket!
I called it first!
Rin, do you want the wall too?
Can I?
You can.
Thanks.
Come on! Put down your stuff and let's go!
Wait for me, Rin!
Honestly. They're such kids.
Nothing weird in the mirror?
No. It's not midnight yet.
Stop it! I can't go to the bathroom now!
Should I hold it for you?
Thanks.
Yuka!
Special rooms mean they're important people, right?
Think there's anyone famous?
Let's take a look!
Don't! They'll get mad at us!
Oh? Saki-chan's scared that they'll get mad at us.
I'm not!
Someone's coming!
Oh no!
Yuka, pillow.
Rin.
Oh, sorry.
What now?
Do we need to change into our pajamas?
No one else is changing.
Guess I'll just take this off.
Me too.
D-D-D-Don't do that!
It's nothing you need to hide.
Think of the other people!
Finally, a chance to lie down.
I'm so tired.
No, no. The night is still young. Look!
Oh, wow!
It's full of snacks.
Every sleepover needs snacks!
Here, Saki-chan.
I'm not eating any.
Saki-chan, you don't need to hold back.
Come on, I went through all that trouble to bring them here. Eat! Eat!
It's consommé flavor! Not only that, it's rich consommé flavor!
One here.
They're good.
Come on, Saki-chan. Open wide.
Open wide!
They're good.
Now then, what do you do on a school trip?
Pillow fights!
No.
Test of courage.
No!
Talk about love?
Saki-chan just said, "Talk about love"!
I was just answering your question.
Or so you say.
There isn't really anyone I like...
I said there isn't!
What about you, Natsumi?
"There isn't."
That's just too bad!
Want to play cards? I brought this too.
And this, and...
You brought way too much with you.
Oh, right. Remember these?
To all passengers aboard the ship: we will be turning out the lights shortly.
The ship is currently cruising through Tokyo Bay toward Miyakejima.
Due to the bad weather, we expect the waves to grow strong and rock the ship.
We recommend that those unaccustomed to travel by ship take their rest early.
Already?!
Use your phone?
You're bothering everyone around us!
Sorry.
You too, Yuka!
It's like it's only us four.
We're in the middle of the ocean right now, right?
It feels kind of weird.
It's hot.
Saki!
Yuka! Get off—
Yuka, what did you want to show us earlier?
Oh, right...
Ta-da!
Water balloons?
I remember those!
I found these while looking for my swimsuit.
We used to play with them a lot.
Yeah, we did!
Rinko was the best at filling them.
Want to do it again when we get to the island?
Yeah, let's do it!
We can invite kids there to...
Yuka?
I feel sick.
What? You're sick?
Anyone have a bag?
Should I call one of the crew?
Let's do that.
Stop the ship...
We'll still be on the ocean if we stop it.
Let's wish on the big rock.
Can it cure you if you're sick?
Seasickness isn't a disease, so it might.
Will it work here in the middle of nowhere?
H-Hold on!
Yuka!
Did you do the English homework?
They're going to call on me today.
Yuka, Rin, Natsumi!
Morning!
Morning, Natsumi.
Hey, do you have your dictionary?
Yeah, I have it.
See you later.
Could I borrow it later?
Sure.
It stopped raining!
We're really in the middle of the ocean.
Did you just realize that?
I mean, it was dark all night.
Is that it?
Yeah.
We're almost there.
Did you not want to go there?
You've been like this the whole time.
You've looked kind of down ever since we left Shimoda.
I'm not down...
Really?
I was just thinking that I'm going for a trip this time,
but next time I come here, it'll be to move.
Do you really have to move?
Can't they just leave you in Shimoda?
At least until the end of middle school.
You could even live with us, Saki!
I can't.
They're moving to the hospital on the island.
My dad always wanted to work on the island.
It's a dream come true for him.
He was really happy.
I can't tell him that I want to stay in Shimoda.
I can't do anything about it.
There you go again.
"Can't do anything"?
You always say that, Saki.
What can't you do?
There is something you can do!
Why do you always avoid the problem and live with it?
You always give up and say you can't do anything!
Do you want to move?
I don't—
Then why—
I can't!
If you can't tell them, then I will!
When we get back, I'll tell your dad!
I'll tell him not to take you away!
Because...
I...
Stop right there!
No fighting!
No, we're not fighting!
But you're crying!
kyuu ni damarikonde
You suddenly stayed silent,
kimi wa te wo tsunaida
And then you took and held my hand
akanezora ni kieteku kyou wo
We watched as our shadows grew taller,
miokuru nagai kageboushi
And the day sank into the orange sky
houkago wa eien mitai ni
After school always seemed like forever
sayonara wo gomakashiteta ne
We would always try not to say good-bye
dakedo kokoro wa tabidachi no yokan wo shitteta
But deep inside we knew that we would have to go our separate ways
hateshinai mirai he no tamerai wo kakushite
Hiding our worries about everything that lay in the future
hohoemu kimi no yume ga mabushii yo
Your smile I saw in my dreams was just so bright
ato sukoshi no kisetsu wo oshimu you ni hashaida
With the season's end coming closer, we played so much to make up for time
ashita he no kaerimichi
The road back home and to tomorrow
It's the island!
And the ocean!
Yay!
When did she put that on?
It feels so good!
My leg!
You idiot!
Grab on!
Did you stretch before you got in?
Thought so.
I'm sorry.
Thank goodness.
Um... Do you live here?
Thank you for saving my friend—
This is why I hate mainlanders.
What a jerk!
Wow, what a jerk!
That was so uncalled for!
Oh wow, this island's sushi is amazing!
Saki, do you still want to move here?
Totally!
These grapes look kind of icky, but they're delish!
Who knew this place would be like this?
This island's so awesome!
Yuka!
Come on, Natsumi. Open wide!
Next time, on Natsuiro Kiseki.
Saki and the Sky on Her Trip
Episode 9: Saki and the Sky on Her Trip.
Where'd Saki go?