Do you want to move?
I don't—
Then why—
I can't!
Because I...
You idiot!
Grab on!
Um... Do you live here?
Thank you for saving my friend—
This is why I hate mainlanders.
Flowing off the edge, the end of a dream
A world where we always search for sensations
What kind of spirit will you glow with as you jump into tomorrow?
Just tell me
The beat of the future, a drumbeat in my ears
Do you hear the start of my melody calling you?
I'm ready! The sky is so blue and so high
I'll never forget this moment as we cried together
I promise that I'll keep on running straight ahead
The moment when we understood
shun
stop
road
is a precious non-stop road
If we could be together,
zu
tto
i
ssho
ni
if I could be with you
ki
mi
to
i
ssho
ni
And be happy it would be the best I think
If we could be together, if I could be with you
zu
tto
i
ssho
ssho
ga
That's the key to the world
Are you ready? So believe in the moment
And be amazed at what you have, your determination
Your smile is just so strong and blindingly bright
shii
I'll look straight ahead and say
shin
wa
I won't give in, I've a non-stop mind
stop
mind
A Summer-Colored Miracle
Saki and the Sky on Her Trip
Rin, slow down!
It's so hot!
Let's go back to the beach.
After we leave our stuff at the inn.
You don't need to get mad...
Sorry.
You're still mad about that guy?
I mean, we are mainlanders, you know.
There's a shop with wetsuits up ahead!
You mean the ones they wear underwater?
Yeah! They have scuba diving lessons!
Seriously? Scuba diving? Let's do it!
Think we could swim with a school of fish?
We might even see sea turtles! Sea turtles live around this island!
What is it?
Nothing. How far is it to the inn?
Let's see. It's past the next intersection, so...
A bell?
A bell? For lunch?
A school?
They're doing club stuff!
Let's check it out, Rin!
Wait, wait, wait!
Why? We're just going to look at the school.
Don't you want to see what it's like, Saki?
Huh?
Don't give me that. Aren't you transferring here?
Let's go.
We can't go to the beach if we look at the school.
But we're already here...
Is this the place?
Finally!
Hello!
Coming!
Huh?
Welcome!
That guy!
They're bigger...
What is?
B-B-B-Boobs?!
Please don't stare...
Wow! A mountain right there!
That's so awesome!
How does that work?
Are they twins?
Or maybe a doppelgänger.
Excuse me.
The bath is open if...
Is something the matter?
Did you turn into a girl?
Yuka!
Did you meet Ko-chan?
Ko-chan?
My twin, Koharu. Okiyama Koharu.
I'm the older one, Chiharu.
Oh, so they're twins.
Chiharu-san, are you in high school?
We're in our second year of middle school.
So am I!
The same age...
We just have to keep trying...
Where on the mainland are you from?
We're from Shimoda, in Shizuoka.
Shimoda? I've heard of that!
Do you know a doctor called Mizukoshi-sensei there?
You should have told us sooner!
Do you know my father?
Everyone around here knows about him.
The clinic is closed right now.
Things will be so much better with Mizukoshi-sensei around.
I see.
Big news! Big news!
Oh, it's just Chi.
Okiyama Chiharu
Big news!
Everyone!
Our new doctor's daughter
is here to visit!
Koharu? You're home?
Why don't you help me?
Nothing beats a morning bath.
I'll wash your back.
The new doctor's daughter?
Yes. She's the same age as my twins.
Found it!
Let's take a bath.
Don't worry. You don't need to move.
Excuse us, but is there a "Saki-san" in?
Yes?
Who is it?
Um... We live around here...
Chiharu texted that you were here!
We're here to show you around!
Let's play!
Saki-san? Saki-san?
Saki-san?
What?
Let's go.
Hey!
Hey! Hey!
Someone was there, right?
Let's just go in.
I'm getting dizzy.
Rin, are you?
What was that for?
Saki-san!
Why's she running away?
You guys!
What are you doing?
Sorry! Sorry!
Everyone! Did you welcome her properly?
You're popular already!
She's not for show.
Again?
Saki, hide.
We're sorry they disturbed you.
I'm leaving some towels for you.
Thank you very much!
It was a worker here.
It's okay now.
Saki?
Yeah, thanks.
Feeling dizzy?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Saki!
Don't worry.
But your nose!
It's okay.
Saki?
You need to get out of here.
What's wrong?
It's you!
That was Koharu, right?
Nice throw.
Huh?
Where's Saki?
Saki?
A Summer-Colored Miracle
Saki's gone!
She might be underwater!
Rin?
Huh? I just ran into something...
Something's here.
It's
Rin?
Sa
ki
Saki?
What's that mean?
They can't see me?
Natsumi!
So Saki's invisible?
Why? The big rock isn't here.
It's its fault.
Don't tell me...
It's the big rock's... cousin.
A rock can have a cousin?!
Don't put something like that in a bath!
Are there bugs in the bath?
No, nothing happened!
Ko-chan?
What happened?
Saki-san isn't with you?
Our room!
She's taking a nap in our room!
Ko-chan.
Ko-chan!
Sorry!
They were peeping, so...
Oh, I see!
Ko-chan is a girl.
A girl?!
Can you stand?
Yeah.
We're so sorry about that.
Saki?
So they're twin sisters.
So Saki's here?
Here?
I'll take care of the rest today.
Chi.
Which one is she?
Ko-chan?
What are we going to do now?
So you can hold stuff.
You need to get back to normal first.
We can't see you or hear you. It's hard.
We don't know when I'll go back to normal, so why don't the three of you go to the beach?
What are we going to do now?
We don't know when
I'll go back to normal,
so why don't the three
of you go to the beach?
It has to be the four of us!
That's right! Don't worry about us!
More importantly, Saki-chan...
you're walking around naked right now, right?
Thank you for the meal!
Wow, this tempura is great!
They're going to come to lay out the futons next, right?
What should we tell them this time?
Bathroom.
Good idea!
Sorry, was that bad?
Sorry I'm not
back to normal yet.
Don't worry, don't worry!
As long as you're back before we go home.
What if she doesn't?
Hey! Don't jinx it!
There are so many stars.
Saki isn't back to normal yet.
I wonder why she turned invisible.
It's because of the big rock's cousin, right?
Right, but...
Maybe she was embarrassed?
Yeah, but Koharu's a girl, so wouldn't that end the wish?
Her nose isn't bleeding anymore either.
I don't think that's it.
Then what else is there?
I don't know, but...
Saki doesn't know what to do.
I'm sorry we have to move at a time like this.
I hope you like the island too.
Things will be so much better with Mizukoshi-sensei around.
This is why I hate mainlanders.
Do you want to move?
What should I do?
She was acting kind of weird by the school, too.
I don't think she wants to move.
She never said anything like—
Saki wouldn't say it.
You're right. Well, that's a problem.
I won't let Saki move.
Did you wish on the big rock?
Of course not.
When we were on the boat, I told her that I'd convince her dad to let her stay.
How could you say something like that?
How could I not? Do you want her to move?
I don't, but we're still in middle school.
We have to stay with our parents.
She can live with me.
It's hard having another person at home.
I know firsthand since my sister came back home.
But that's only for the summer.
How long are you going to keep Saki?
Your mom is nice, so she might say okay, but what about Daiki—
It'll work out!
Natsumi, there are things out there you can't do anything about.
It's sad, but it's not like we'll never see her again.
We can just go see her when we want to!
It's not that easy!
How long did it take to get here from Shimoda?
It's really far away!
She won't be there when I open my window.
It's completely different.
A friendship doesn't end just because you're far apart.
That's right! We can take a day to go and visit her!
Or maybe you won't go because it's so far away?
I'll go.
Oh, but then there are those times when they say they'll text you, but they never do.
I'll do it! I'll definitely text her! And call her!
Then we're all good.
You're going already?
So what?
I thought we would show them around...
I don't know anything interesting around here.
Don't take it out on them!
Sensei was—
Ko-chan!
Where's Saki?
Brushing her teeth.
Thank you for the meal!
Excuse me...
Where is Saki-san?
Um... She went out for a little walk.
I see.
I wanted to show her places around the island.
What kinds of places?
Like places where sea turtles are and the biggest souvenir shop on the island!
Sea turtles.
Souvenirs!
Let's go.
But...
I just have to go with you
Let's go.
Wow, that's a lot of boats!
They catch flying fish and alfonsinos here.
Mister!
Another sea turtle!
They're so big!
Stop! Stop!
I feel sick!
Sorry to bother you while you're working.
Silly kids, just have fun!
I can't choose...
Can you carry all that?
I'll mail it!
Then here's a little extra.
Think Mizukoshi-sensei's daughter will like it?
Of course! Thank you very much!
Can it see you?
Natsumi!
Oh, whoops.
Both of you.
On video.
Rin!
Thank you! Thank you for coming!
I'm not...
Grandma, this isn't Saki-san.
No, no. Your father is a great doctor.
Our health is in good hands.
Everyone loves Saki's dad!
Everyone on this island is so nice.
Now if only Koharu wasn't so rude.
Oh, Chiharu.
Where is Saki's dad going to be working?
There's a clinic near our inn. He'll be working there.
A clinic?
Yes.
I want to see!
Okay. We're pretty far from there, so I'll call a taxi.
You're so heavy...
Ow!
Those mainlanders...
Have a look.
It's so simple.
Rin, try sitting here.
Don't touch Sensei's desk!
Ko-chan!
Chiharu! Don't let these people in!
They're outsiders!
Sensei?
We used to have an old doctor here.
What about now?
He isn't doing very well, so...
He's going to live with his son on the mainland.
Because he can't be a doctor anymore.
Because some replacement is coming!
Ko-chan!
Sensei said that he could keep working!
But no...
You're wrong—
Wrong about what?
He told you too!
He said that he'd look after everyone here.
That he'd always be right here!
Yes, but Sensei was pushing himself too hard.
It was really hard for him.
But he promised.
He just didn't want to leave.
But one day, he got a phone call from one of his former students.
Sensei smiled and said,
"I can trust them—I can trust Mizukoshi-kun to look after everyone."
He was here since before I was born.
Swimming, school...
He taught me everything!
Why aren't you sad?
You and everyone else...
I don't get it!
Saying good-bye is hard on everyone.
On me, on Sensei...
You're not the only one who's sad.
I hope the new doctor is as good as they say.
Don't worry. He's definitely a good doctor.
It's our friend's dad.
Thank you.
natsu no kaori semishigure yo
The scent of the summer air, the sound of the cicadas
Would you mind if we went to one more place?
kimi to sugoshita kono hibi
I'll never forget the time that I spent
It's so pretty!
Only people on the island know about this place.
wasurenai zutto
Together with you
Saki's going to live here...
Yeah.
Saki!
You're right, it's Saki!
Welcome back.
Yeah.
W-Where did you come from?!
tonari wo yuku hashagu koe ga
Walking right next to me, your voice full of life
Saki-san, your clothes?!
ureshikute akiretaku nattari
You're so happy, I almost want to sigh
Okay.
Thanks for bringing my clothes with you.
nanigenakute tokubetsu na jikan
These moments aren't special, but then again, they are
Saki, I...
hanaretakunai yo sotto mitsumeta
I looked at you thinking, I don't want you to leave
It's okay.
Sorry.
Thanks.
Hey, Saki-chan!
tsuyogaru kimi wa yasashii
You act like it doesn't bother you because you're so kind
Come here.
Um... What?
Introduction practice.
bukiyou na yokogao wakatteru yo
You can never say things straight, but I know that
What do you mean by "introduction practice"?
A suggestion from Rin-senpai!
Senpai in what?
nido to nai ima wo issho ni
We'll never have another moment together like this again
In transferring!
You only get one chance!
Your first impression is very important.
omoikkiri waratteitai
So let's smile as big as we can
Saki
Mizukoshi
My name is Mizukoshi Saki.
Pleased to meet you.
Make it longer!
natsu wo koete todokete hoshii
I want you to know it won't be just the summer
I'll say something when I actually do it!
What? Aren't we supposed to clap?
zutto itsumademo tomodachi da yo
We'll be the best of friends forever and ever
Okiyama-san, pleased to meet you.
You can... call me Koharu.
sora no mukou yuuhi wa ochite
The sun is setting beyond the horizon
ashita he no hikari ni kawaru ne
Let's watch it become tomorrow's light
mitsumete aruitekou
As we walk together
Bye!
natsu wo koete todokete hoshii
I want you to know it won't be just the summer
Bye-bye!
See you!
Come again soon!
Bye!
zutto itsumademo tomodachi da yo
We'll be the best of friends forever and ever
koe ni dashite tsutaetaku naru
I want to tell you, as best as I can
I'm glad we came.
All right! Where to next?
tatoe hanretetemo
Even if we're far apart
Planning something already?
We don't have much time before Saki moves.
kokoro de aeru to shinjiteru
We can still meet one another in our hearts
"A young girl ages easily; 'tis difficult to make memories."
Well, I guess we should.
What?
I never thought Saki-chan would ever agree with me.
But we're going to make memories, right?
Yeah!
Let's go! Let's go!
Where do you want to go?
I'll go wherever.
As long as it's with you.
kyuu ni damarikonde
You suddenly stayed silent,
kimi wa te wo tsunaida
And then you took and held my hand
akanezora ni kieteku kyou wo
We watched as our shadows grew taller,
miokuru nagai kageboushi
And the day sank into the orange sky
houkago wa eien mitai ni
After school always seemed like forever
sayonara wo gomakashiteta ne
We would always try not to say good-bye
dakedo kokoro wa tabidachi no yokan wo shitteta
But deep inside we knew that we would have to go our separate ways
hateshinai mirai he no tamerai wo kakushite
Hiding our worries about everything that lay in the future
hohoemu kimi no yume ga mabushii yo
Your smile I saw in my dreams was just so bright
ato sukoshi no kisetsu wo oshimu you ni hashaida
With the season's end coming closer, we played so much to make up for time
ashita he no kaerimichi
The road back home and to tomorrow
That was a fun trip!
Let's go on another sometime!
What should we do today?
They say there's a typhoon coming.
Even though it's so sunny?
I think something happened the last time we had a typhoon on a sunny day...
I just felt a chill down my spine...
Oh, right! We went ghost hunting!
Quit it! Quit it! Quit it!
Okay.
Next time, on Natsuiro Kiseki.
A Typhoon, Ghosts, and Today's Memory
Episode 10: A Typhoon, Ghosts, and Today's Memory.
Hey, Natsumi, that little girl over there...
I said, quit it!