All right, let's start.
Saki.
That's right. Four years ago, Saki was the last one to put her hands on this rock.
Yuka, do you really believe that?
There's no way something like that could ever—
We won't know unless we try it!
Natsumi's right!
Come on, Saki.
Okay...
Ready?
Let's start!
Okay.
It has to be all four of us or it won't work!
And all of us have to wish for the same thing.
I know that.
Okay, then! One, two, three!
Back then, we really believed
that if all four of us wished for the same thing, our wish would come true.
That no matter what the wish was,
it would come true.
Flowing off the edge, the end of a dream
A world where we always search for sensations
What kind of spirit will you glow with as you jump into tomorrow?
Just tell me
The beat of the future, a drumbeat in my ears
Do you hear the start of my melody calling you?
I'm ready! The sky is so blue and so high
I'll never forget this moment as we cried together
I promise that I'll keep on running straight ahead
The moment when we understood
shun
stop
road
is a precious non-stop road
If we could be together,
zu
tto
i
ssho
ni
if I could be with you
ki
mi
to
i
ssho
ni
And be happy it would be the best I think
If we could be together, if I could be with you
zu
tto
i
ssho
ssho
ga
That's the key to the world
Are you ready? So believe in the moment
And be amazed at what you have, your determination
Your smile is just so strong and blindingly bright
shii
I'll look straight ahead and say
shin
wa
I won't give in, I've a non-stop mind
stop
mind
A Summer-Colored Miracle
Our 11th Summer Vacation
Daiki, wake up!
I'm leaving for work!
He's not going to wake up until the last minute, you know.
You're always acting like such a kid.
Why can't you be more like your sister?
Because I'm not a kid anymore.
Club
New Text
Mizukoshi Saki
You'd better come
to morning practice!
Sending Text
I never thought you'd be able to get up for morning practice for this long.
It's because I promised.
Promised?
See you later.
Take care.
Text Received
Aizawa Natsumi
A
Text Received
Aizawa Natsumi
A
Text Received
Aizawa Natsumi
A
Text Received
Aizawa Natsumi
A
Text Received
Aizawa Natsumi
A
Text Received
Aizawa Natsumi
A
Text Received
Aizawa Natsumi
A
Text Received
Aizawa Natsumi
A
Text Received
Aizawa Natsumi
A
Text Received
Aizawa Natsumi
A
Text Received
Aizawa Natsumi
A
Text Received
Aizawa Natsumi
A
Text Received
Aizawa Natsumi
A
Text Received
Aizawa Natsumi
A
Text Received
Aizawa Natsumi
A
Text Received
Aizawa Natsumi
A
Text Received
Aizawa Natsumi
A
Text Received
Aizawa Natsumi
A
Text Received
Aizawa Natsumi
A
Text Received
Aizawa Natsumi
A
Text Received
Aizawa Natsumi
A
Text Received
Aizawa Natsumi
A
Text Received
Aizawa Natsumi
A
Text Received
Aizawa Natsumi
A
Text Received
Aizawa Natsumi
A
Text Received
Aizawa Natsumi
A
Text Received
Aizawa Natsumi
A
Text Received
Aizawa Natsumi
A
Text Received
Aizawa Natsumi
A
Text Received
Aizawa Natsumi
A
Text Received
Aizawa Natsumi
A
Text Received
Aizawa Natsumi
A
Text Received
Aizawa Natsumi
A
Text Received
Aizawa Natsumi
A
Text Received
Aizawa Natsumi
A
Text Received
Aizawa Natsumi
A
Text Received
Aizawa Natsumi
A
Text Received
Aizawa Natsumi
A
Text Received
Aizawa Natsumi
A
Text Received
Aizawa Natsumi
A
Text Received
Aizawa Natsumi
A
Text Received
Aizawa Natsumi
A
Text Received
Aizawa Natsumi
A
Text Received
Aizawa Natsumi
A
Text Received
Aizawa Natsumi
A
Text Received
Aizawa Natsumi
A
Text Received
Aizawa Natsumi
A
Text Received
Aizawa Natsumi
A
Why isn't she here?
Saki!
Morning!
Morning.
Look!
What?
It's a limited edition of Four Season's latest single!
It comes with a special DVD!
They're still around?
What? It hit number one on the daily ranking! Number one—
I haven't heard them anywhere lately.
That can't be true, right?
They always play them at the convenience store.
I haven't seen them on TV, though.
That's harsh, Rin.
Maybe they just haven't gotten a time slot lately.
Oh, Saki! You should watch it and tell me what you think!
Sorry.
I don't have time for that.
Club?
Natsumi.
Saki, come with me.
Why?
You know why!
Come with me!
No.
Just come!
Wow, she's mad.
Club?
What?
Why haven't you been coming to morning practice?
It's my choice to go or not.
You're the one who wanted to do it!
After the district tournament,
you said we should practice since we're going to be the main pair next year.
But now... it's been a whole week!
You haven't been coming to morning practice or to club!
You don't even answer the door when I stop by your house.
I don't know what's gotten into you,
but summer vacation starts in two days.
At least try, Saki.
Saki!
Natsumi, you can take over as club president.
What?
I'm quitting.
You're not my friend anymore if you do.
I'm fine with that.
Saki!
You're definitely not my friend anymore!
Senpai's kind of scary today.
You know how the Shibata-Mizuno pair that beat Asano-senpai are still second years?
Isn't that bad news for us next year?
And Mizukoshi-senpai hasn't been coming to practice...
Staff Room
A
What? Seriously?
You two haven't talked since?
She's not my friend anymore.
All this "not my friend anymore" stuff sure brings back memories!
Not my friend, not my friend, my friends aren't friends!
I'm being serious here.
Ouch!
It's in the shade! Why is it so hot?!
It was in the sun before we went into the store.
You should've told me!
I could've melted!
Here!
I haven't heard anything from them recently.
What?! Come on! They're still releasing CDs and having live concerts and stuff!
We don't see them on TV, though.
Remember how they used to be on any channel you flipped to?
You could almost get sick of them!
Back then, whenever you and Saki fought,
you'd always be like, "You're not my friend anymore!"
That was back in elementary school.
I haven't said that since we got into middle school.
In other words, you grew up?
If they did, they wouldn't be fighting like this.
Saki was the one that wanted to shoot for nationals, you know.
Staff Room
A
Quit being stubborn and make up with her tomorrow.
It's none of your business.
This is between me and Saki.
Natsumi-chan! What's gotten into you?
It would suck if this fight lasted all
summer vacation, don't you think?
Yeah. It would suck.
Tell that to Saki, not me!
What if it really lasted all summer vacation?
"A young girl ages easily;
'tis difficult to become an idol."
That's not funny.
See you later!
Take care!
Daiki! Hurry up and eat your breakfast!
'kay...
Saki didn't go to morning practice again today?
I haven't seen her yet.
Is she skipping the last day because it's just the assembly?
Saki's never been absent before.
Okay, everyone. Take your seats.
Saki?
Settle down.
I have something to announce to you all before the assembly.
Unfortunately, Mizukoshi Saki will be transferring to another school.
Mizukoshi.
Um...
Thank you very much for all you've done for me.
Natsumi! Did you hear that?!
Hey, did you know?
A Summer-Colored Miracle
Hey! Hey—
Saki?
Don't forget about the mid-break check-in.
Mizukoshi-san, where are you moving to?
Tokyo.
Wow! Sounds nice!
Where in Tokyo?
It's only the outskirts of Tokyo.
Tokyo?
Let's have a farewell party!
Yeah!
When?
Good luck!
Keep in touch!
Why didn't you tell us?
I thought I wasn't your friend.
You—you're not, but...
Why didn't you tell us sooner?!
You're the one who wanted me to join the club!
You said, "If we're going to do this, then let's shoot for nationals!"
Didn't you say that?
Yet...
I don't remember saying that.
Saki!
I said, I don't remember.
I never promised to shoot for nationals in tennis.
Natsumi!
Saki!
How could you forget a promise with Natsumi?
It's none of your business.
It's better to forget a promise than not be able to fulfill it.
That's all for today.
Thank you for the match!
I'll leave cleaning up to you.
Okay!
I hate you, Saki.
Exchange Diary
A
Nobody can look
except us four!!!
A
I was supposed to write the next entry.
Come in.
Saki, you didn't tell our neighbors we were moving?
Natsumi-chan's mom couldn't
believe her ears when I told her.
I just forgot to.
You forgot to?
It doesn't matter.
Just leave me alone.
I know.
It's all my fault.
I don't remember saying that.
I said, I don't remember.
I never promised to shoot for nationals in tennis.
Tamaki Rinko
Emergency
Yuka fainted at our shrine. Come over now!
See you!
Thank you for practicing with us!
Yuka!
Yuka, what's wrong?
Did you call an ambulance?
Not yet.
What are you doing?
We need one now!
What's the meaning of this?!
Saki?
That's the tennis club for you! So fast!
Yuka!
Sorry, sorry!
That wasn't funny.
Why would you do that?
Isn't it obvious?
Here.
Is this...
Now we're all friends again!
If four people touch the big rock and wish for the same thing,
any wish will come true!
Natsumi, did you plan this?
How could you even think that?
I wonder.
Hey. You all remember, right?
Back when the four of us would wish on this rock?
That's right.
That time four years ago,
Yuka and Rin called me here.
The big rock will grant our wishes?
Yeah!
Rin said she overheard her mom talking about it.
She said that if four close friends touch the rock and wish for the same thing,
that wish will definitely come true!
Yuka, do you really believe that?
There's no way that something like that could ever—
We won't know unless we try it!
Natsumi's right!
Come on, Saki.
Okay...
So, what are we wishing for?
That we can all become idols together!
Idols?
Yeah! Together! Like Four Season!
Four Season?!
Rin?
Ready?
Let's start!
Okay.
It has to be all four of us or it won't work!
And all of us have to wish for the same thing.
I know that.
Okay, then! One, two, three!
That all four of us can become idols together!
A
Singing Competition
And in the kids' competition, the winner is...
A
Singing Competition
Four Stars!
A
Singing Competition
Yay! Yay!
Our wish came true!
Yep! It's all thanks to the big rock!
That we can pass a talent audition!
That we can get on TV!
That we can have a concert at the Budokan!
That we can do all that!
That all our wishes can come true!
So, before Saki-chan moves away,
you have to make up with the big rock's help.
Yuka, don't tell me you still believe that?
Of course!
Rin, you can't just do whatever Yuka tells you!
But I don't want you two fighting like this...
Fine.
All right, let's start.
Saki.
That all four of us can become idols together.
Can become idols together.
What the heck are you wishing for?
Our dream.
Listen, didn't you say you wanted us to make up?
Yeah!
If our dream comes true, then we can all be friends again!
We promised that we would be idols together!
Back when we were in fourth grade!
Our dream?
Grow up already!
Saki...
You still believe that stuff?
There's no way something like that could ever happen!
We did win the singing competition that year, though.
That's true...
You know, that was just the kids' competition. There were only ten contestants that year.
You know that, right?
We still won, though! That's all that matters!
So let's wish for it again.
If all four of us wish for the same thing, it'll definitely come true!
Enough, already!
When are you going to grow up?!
We're in our second year of middle school.
We're not in fourth grade anymore!
Quit trying to force this childhood dream stuff on me!
But...
No buts!
Yuka...
Could you cut it out, Saki?
What's wrong with believing in a dream?
Oh, so you still believe in this stuff too?
You're in your second year of middle
school and still think you can be an idol?
I do.
You liar!
I'm not lying!
I believed that I could play tennis with you!
Oh, come on!
That doesn't have anything to do with being an idol!
That I can go to nationals with Saki in tennis.
Don't wish for something only you want!
All four of us have to wish for the same thing or it won't come true.
It was my dream!
I wanted to play tennis with you—
What do you want me to do?
I didn't want to move, you know!
Why didn't you tell us you were moving?
That's because—
Because what?
It doesn't matter!
It does!
No, it doesn't!
Yes, it does!
The sky is blue.
No, it doesn't!
Yes, it does!
I wish...
I could fly.
What?!
Your hand!
Saki.
What's going on?
We're flying?
We're really...
Wow!
How?
Because I wished for it?
I mean... I did.
Well, yeah...
No...
It's because we all wished for it!
kyuu ni damarikonde
You suddenly stayed silent,
kimi wa te wo tsunaida
And then you took and held my hand
akanezora ni kieteku kyou wo
We watched as our shadows grew taller,
miokuru nagai kageboushi
And the day sank into the orange sky
houkago wa eien mitai ni
After school always seemed like forever
sayonara wo gomakashiteta ne
We would always try not to say good-bye
dakedo kokoro wa
But deep inside we knew
tabidachi no yokan wo shitteta
That we would have to go our separate ways
hateshinai mirai he no tamerai wo kakushite
Hiding our worries about everything that lay in the future
hohoemu kimi no yume ga mabushii yo
Your smile I saw in my dreams was just so bright
ato sukoshi no kisetsu wo
With the season's end coming closer,
oshimu you ni hashaida
We played so much to make up for time
ashita he no kaerimichi
The road back home and to tomorrow
I'm going home.
Wa-Wait—Saki!
Yuka!
I'm okay...
The day before summer vacation started,
a miracle came and swept us off our feet.
Oh, wow! We really flew, you know?
Thanks to the big rock.
I wonder what else it'll grant!
Should we try a few?
That I can be an idol!
That I can be a model!
That I never have to do homework again!
That I never have to do chores again!
That Four Season makes a ton of albums!
That I can keep getting my allowance forever!
Wow, Yuka, that's a lot.
It would be so awesome if all of these came true!
We have to go to the big rock now!
Next time, on Natsuiro Kiseki.
Wishing Together
Episode 2: Wishing Together.
Shoot, Rin, let's get out of here!