Huh?
My room?
Morning.
Hey, weren't we at the inn—
Hello?
This is crazy! Today is yesterday, and today is the audition,
and today is yesterday, and yesterday is today!
What are you trying to say?
Today turned into yesterday, and yesterday is today,
Today is yesterday?
and yesterday was the audition, and today... Today is the audition?
Audition
Okay...
Okay... I got it, so just calm down, okay?
Flowing off the edge, the end of a dream
A world where we always search for sensations
What kind of spirit will you glow with as you jump into tomorrow?
Just tell me
The beat of the future, a drumbeat in my ears
Do you hear the start of my melody calling you?
I'm ready! The sky is so blue and so high
I'll never forget this moment as we cried together
I promise that I'll keep on running straight ahead
The moment when we understood
shun
stop
road
is a precious non-stop road
If we could be together,
zu
tto
i
ssho
ni
if I could be with you
ki
mi
to
i
ssho
ni
And be happy it would be the best I think
If we could be together, if I could be with you
zu
tto
i
ssho
ssho
ga
That's the key to the world
Are you ready? So believe in the moment
And be amazed at what you have, your determination
Your smile is just so strong and blindingly bright
shii
I'll look straight ahead and say
shin
wa
I won't give in, I've a non-stop mind
stop
mind
A Summer-Colored Miracle
The Endless Summer Vacation
Yuka
Get over here now!
And don't forget your stuff!
Yuka
Get over here now!
And don't forget your stuff!
Yuka
Get over here now!
And don't forget your stuff!
Yuka
Get over here now!
And don't forget your stuff!
Yuka
Get over here now!
And don't forget your stuff!
Yuka
Get over here now!
And don't forget your stuff!
Yuka
Get over here now!
And don't forget your stuff!
Yuka
Get over here now!
And don't forget your stuff!
Yuka
Get over here now!
And don't forget your stuff!
Yuka
Get over here now!
And don't forget your stuff!
Yuka
Get over here now!
And don't forget your stuff!
Yuka
Get over here now!
And don't forget your stuff!
Yuka
Get over here now!
And don't forget your stuff!
Yuka
Get over here now!
And don't forget your stuff!
Yuka
Get over here now!
And don't forget your stuff!
Yuka
Get over here now!
And don't forget your stuff!
Yuka
Get over here now!
And don't forget your stuff!
Yuka
Get over here now!
And don't forget your stuff!
Yuka
Get over here now!
And don't forget your stuff!
Yuka
Get over here now!
And don't forget your stuff!
Yuka
Get over here now!
And don't forget your stuff!
Oh, you're up early.
Yuka
Get over here now!
And don't forget your stuff!
Yuka
Get over here now!
And don't forget your stuff!
Yuka
Get over here now!
And don't forget your stuff!
Yuka
Get over here now!
And don't forget your stuff!
Yuka
Get over here now!
And don't forget your stuff!
Yuka
Get over here now!
And don't forget your stuff!
Yuka
Get over here now!
And don't forget your stuff!
Yuka
Get over here now!
And don't forget your stuff!
Yeah.
See you.
Good luck.
Thanks.
What's going on?
What happened?
I don't know.
But we're back in Shimoda, and the calendar says it's yesterday...
I don't get it.
Natsumi, how's your fever?
It's gone.
It's not gone, Natsumi.
What do you mean?
When I left my house, Mama said, "Good luck."
Something wrong with that?
Yesterday, she said, "Take care."
So...
I think today is a second yesterday.
What does that mean?
Wait, hold on! Does that mean I'm
going to get another fever tonight?!
Should I get some medicine?
Yeah. No, no, no, wait! I mean—
Saki, what do we do?
I don't know, either.
Why is this happening?
The big rock!
Wait, we didn't wish for anything...
Everyone, this is our chance.
Our big chance!
What is?
Don't you get it?
The audition!
We can give it another try!
Oh, you mean...
Exactly! We've done it once, so I won't trip this time!
It's perfect!
May I have your attention, please.
The Resort 21 regional departing at 6:43 a.m. is
now boarding from the Atami-bound platform.
Let's go!
Our future awaits!
Yuka, at least you didn't trip this time.
I never thought you of all people could forget what move to do.
We can't do anything about it now. Cheer up.
But Saki's going to transfer!
I thought we'd pass the audition this
time and be together forever as idols!
Yuka...
Come on! I told you that going to auditions is going to be easy after I transfer!
Saki...
The Skytree is so tall!
Yeah, but it wasn't as good as I thought.
Well, we can't really say it's our first time.
It is our second time.
Guess we can say it was worth it.
I see!
What's up?
This is where we sat down.
Yeah.
This place has the same name as Rin's!
You're right!
Mama said that there were a lot of shrines with this name throughout Japan.
Wait, does that mean...
Don't tell me...
I touched this rock yesterday.
This is one of those rocks?
Here!
So?
Yeah. This is the big rock's cousin.
You think a big rock is at all the shrines with this name?
I don't know. Maybe.
How many are there in Japan?
A lot.
But we didn't touch this rock.
It says here that all the rocks around the shrine were cut from this one.
I see.
Yuka!
Come on, just one more time!
We can't do that!
Let go of me, Natsumi!
It's too hot!
I said no!
Hey...
What wish do you think the rock granted?
What we wished for yesterday evening, I think.
Stop, Natsumi.
We don't have much more time to be together.
What did we wish for then?
It would be so nice if we could get extensions on summer vacation...
We wished...
...that summer vacation wouldn't end.
And the big rock...
Wait, does that mean...
Hey, how would that wish come true?
Yuka, it's true right now.
Oh, I get it!
That's why today is yesterday!
Wait, then what about right now?
Does that mean our wish is over?
Maybe.
It isn't.
Yeah.
So basically...
...summer vacation won't end?
Oh, you're up early.
See you.
Be careful.
Yeah.
It'll be perfect today!
Totally flawless!
Let's go!
I messed up again...
It's a beautiful day.
See you.
Good luck.
Thanks.
What's wrong?
She said that she doesn't know what else to do.
Cheer up!
Let's go to the beach!
Huh?!
That's so random.
A change of pace! That's what we need!
For an idol, stress is natural!
So we need to let loose!
What about swimsuits?
It feels so good!
Yuka!
Wow, it's so salty!
Take this!
Saki! It feels great!
Yeah! Here I come!
Hey, Suzu!
Sana!
It's so hard to meet up these days.
You're just too busy.
It's my fault?
It's not your fault.
I was just thinking that you've
always been such a hard worker.
Oh, quit it.
I sure miss summer vacations.
Back then, it was just another part of the year to us.
Even though it was the only time when we
could be with our friends all day, every day.
I wonder how Natsumi's doing at the audition.
That's a weird place to be auditioning.
Hey, why don't we play tennis tomorrow?
Great idea! Doubles with the four of us?
Right, Saki?
Sure...
Yay! Hear that? It's tennis tomorrow, Rin!
Wow, that's high tech.
Sometimes Rin makes me worry, you know.
Maybe I'll have Daiki carry one too.
Wait, that's weird. They said this audition is
their last memory with Saki-chan this summer.
There's something that's been bothering me for a while now.
Sana?
Hey, how long are we going to keep doing this?
Forever!
You're up early.
Yeah.
See you.
Oh, Rin-chan...
When are you four coming home?
A Summer-Colored Miracle
When are we coming home?
Yeah.
Rin's mom was the one who told us about the big rock, after all.
Do you think maybe Rin's mom wished on it too?
Definitely possible.
Either way, we can't just leave things the way they are.
But what can we do?
We couldn't cancel or wish away any of our wishes.
Yeah.
Let's go to Tokyo.
Again?
For what?
The audition, of course!
If we don't have anything else to do anymore, the wish might end.
You're right.
Yuka, you're a genius.
Yuka!
Did I...
do it?
You did!
It was perfect!
I did it! I did it! Finally!
Yuka!
That was awesome!
Natsumi.
Don't fall asleep now.
Thanks.
I hope it worked.
Don't worry!
The audition went great!
How many tries did it take?
For us, anyway.
It's almost time.
Looks like it didn't work.
Yeah.
Tamaki Rinko
Big rock, everyone.
What's up?
Rin says that she figured it out.
How to end the summer vacation?
Yes.
How do we do it?
I think we need to end everything.
What do you mean?
I mean we need to say good-bye to
the miracle that the big rock gave us.
Say good-bye...
...to the miracle?
I think that's what Mama meant by "coming home."
You're right.
Then let's hop to it!
We're doing it now?
There's no point in waiting.
You're right.
Natsumi.
I was just thinking it's going to be kind of sad.
Haven't had enough yet?
It's not that...
I'm satisfied!
Well, maybe you are, Yuka.
I know how you feel.
I'm sad too.
But if it doesn't end, it won't be a memory.
Natsumi, Yuka, and Rinko.
You all made this an amazing summer vacation.
That's why I want it to be the best memory ever.
Okay.
You used to always be the first one.
Well, sorry!
Thanks, everyone.
Good-bye.
I'll never forget anything that happened.
This summer,
every day we spent together,
every precious memory.
That's why I'll say good-bye.
Good-bye, summer vacation.
Good-bye, eternity.
Good-bye, miracle!
Good-bye!
Is it over?
Yeah.
Really?
I think so.
Which is it?
Oh! Should we try it?
Touch the big rock?
It's okay. We'll know when tomorrow comes.
Tomorrow?
That's right.
When today ends,
and tomorrow comes.
Morning.
Morning, Natsumi.
You're up early.
Yeah.
See you.
Rin-chan, come home soon.
Yeah.
Morning!
Morning.
This is where it all started.
Hey, why don't we try wishing again?
Yuka?
I've had enough already.
Natsumi, you have a fever.
It worked.
Morning.
Your fever?
It's gone.
Morning!
And so, our summer vacation—our miracle—ended.
When they got back, they all helped clean out the house.
Oh, really?
Natsumi-chan was very helpful.
I hope you all come visit on the island.
Of course.
kyuu ni damarikonde
You suddenly stayed silent,
Mom, I'm heading out to Yuusuke's.
kimi wa te wo tsunaida
And then you took and held my hand
Daiki, do you know where Natsumi went?
akanezora ni kieteku kyou wo
We watched as our shadows grew taller,
She said she was going to Rin-chan's.
Saki Nee-chan went with her.
akanezora ni kieteku kyou wo
We watched as our shadows grew taller,
miokuru nagai kageboushi
And the day sank into the orange sky
It's too bad we didn't pass the audition.
houkago wa eien mitai ni
After school always seemed like forever
Yeah.
houkago wa eien mitai ni
After school always seemed like forever
But we can always go for another.
sayonara wo gomakashiteta ne
We would always try not to say good-bye
Yeah.
sayonara wo gomakashiteta ne
We would always try not to say good-bye
It's so nice and warm.
dakedo kokoro wa tabidachi no yokan wo shitteta
But deep inside we knew that we would have to go our separate ways
They're here.
What took you?
dakedo kokoro wa tabidachi no yokan wo shitteta
But deep inside we knew that we would have to go our separate ways
We were helping move stuff.
dakedo kokoro wa tabidachi no yokan wo shitteta
But deep inside we knew that we would have to go our separate ways
Did you finish?
Not yet. We have to go back soon.
dakedo kokoro wa tabidachi no yokan wo shitteta
But deep inside we knew that we would have to go our separate ways
Then we'd better hurry.
hateshinai mirai he no tamerai wo kakushite
Hiding our worries about everything that lay in the future
Hey, should we wish that Saki-chan didn't have to move?
Yuka!
I'm just kidding!
hohoemu kimi no yume ga mabushii yo
Your smile I saw in my dreams was just so bright
See?
All right! Let's do it!
Saki.
ato sukoshi no kisetsu wo oshimu you ni hashaida
With the season's end coming closer, we played so much to make up for time
ashita he no kaerimichi
The road back home and to tomorrow
The big rock won't give us any more miracles.
But this wish isn't for a miracle.
That the four of us will be best friends forever!