Morning.
Oh, you're awake?
Yes, I am.
It looks great outside!
I'll wake Saki-chan up next.
She's already awake.
I woke Rin up just now, so...
You should probably wake her up again.
Not enough sleep?
I got nervous and couldn't fall asleep last night.
Actually, I did too.
Hey!
Morning!
Morning.
How can you be so excited this early?
How couldn't I? I've been waiting for this day since forever!
Why don't we go for it?
It'll be our last memory.
An idol audition?
When did you apply for that?
We got through the first round?
Yeah!
Finally! I sent applications everywhere!
Oh, right. I sent everyone's best pictures.
And you didn't tell—
Rin, did you know about this?
I didn't think we would pass.
So we're all going to Tokyo next week.
Of course, we're shooting to win! And be idols!
Five, six, seven, eight!
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight!
One, two, three, four, five, six...
I practiced myself to death!
And with this song...
This one's in the bag!
Oh no! We'll never live normal lives again!
You think it'll go that well?
Having confidence is a good thing.
I guess.
All right, then! All aboard for Tokyo!
Flowing off the edge, the end of a dream
A world where we always search for sensations
What kind of spirit will you glow with as you jump into tomorrow?
Just tell me
The beat of the future, a drumbeat in my ears
Do you hear the start of my melody calling you?
I'm ready! The sky is so blue and so high
I'll never forget this moment as we cried together
I promise that I'll keep on running straight ahead
The moment when we understood
shun
stop
road
is a precious non-stop road
If we could be together,
zu
tto
i
ssho
ni
if I could be with you
ki
mi
to
i
ssho
ni
And be happy it would be the best I think
If we could be together, if I could be with you
zu
tto
i
ssho
ssho
ga
That's the key to the world
Are you ready? So believe in the moment
And be amazed at what you have, your determination
Your smile is just so strong and blindingly bright
shii
I'll look straight ahead and say
shin
wa
I won't give in, I've a non-stop mind
stop
mind
A Summer-Colored Miracle
Give It a Shot!
Tokyo Cinderella Tour
And we're here!
Yuka!
Stop that. It's embarrassing.
We still have time before the audition.
Not that much. Want to head there early?
We can't do that! They say it's bad for your nerves if you go early.
Oh, really?
Then should we find somewhere to relax?
Why don't we go see that thing we didn't get to last time?
The Skytree?
Yeah!
One second!
Let's leave that for after we finish the audition.
Why don't we practice dancing somewhere?
Did Yuka just say something reasonable?
...six, seven, eight!
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight!
One!
That was perfect!
We did practice it every minute we had!
I even practiced it at home.
Actually, I did too.
Same here.
Hey, I just got a great idea!
At the first hook, why don't we do different moves in pairs?
You want to change it now?
Yeah!
It's where the song gets exciting, so we should make it even more exciting!
That's not something you say right before the audition.
Oh, come on. I just thought it up right now.
Listen, Yuka—
What kind of moves are you thinking of?
Saki?!
Okay, so Natsumi and me do what we already had,
but Saki and Rin do this.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
One!
I like having different movements at that part.
It definitely does look better.
Right?
But we already practiced with what we already had.
Well, it's a pretty small change.
Why don't we give it a try?
Sure.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight!
One!
What?
Thanks...
Thank you! Thank you!
Floor 6
Next
Generation
Idol Audition
There are so many people...
Way more than I expected...
Let's see...
Answer the questions as specifically as you can, and try to show them good things about yourself.
I know.
Let's give that last scene another run.
Okay?
All right!
We're here right now, right?
Yuka?
Oh, here's the dressing room.
Huh?
Are you okay?
Should we go now?
I'm fine.
Let's change clothes first.
Oh, sor—
Um...
Something happen, Yuka?
My bag bumped into her...
Sorry! Are you okay?
Did she just ignore me?
Don't take it too hard. We are competition, you know.
Are you okay?
There's no way we can pass this...
You're chickening out now?
Where'd your baseless confidence go?
Why are we even here?
We shouldn't be here.
Yuka, just relax.
A fool of myself...
I'll make a complete fool of myself.
That's totally fine.
If that's how good we are, then that's it.
It's not like it's a professional audition.
I don't think they're just looking for how good we are now.
That's right! Just show them how cheerful you are.
Just go in the way you always are!
I don't know how I always am.
The best thing about you is how you never give up.
How you always look like you're having fun.
How you always make everyone around you have fun.
I think you're cut out to be an idol.
Rin...
Yuka, just think about everything that we've done this summer.
This summer?
We've done all sorts of amazing things.
Saki, what's gotten into you?
It's me, Yuka!
Wha— Me?!
So Saki's here?
Here?
Saki, stand back!
Launch!
After all that, this is just another day.
She's right! We've probably had the craziest summer out of everyone here!
So we're more than special enough.
Yeah! You're right!
That was that girl...
You're friends from back home?
Yes!
In the same class?
We are!
You over there. Could you lift your bangs?
S-Sure!
Okay. Thank you.
How did you four get here?
The train. The first one this morning.
When did you wake up today?
Five o'clock.
Wow, that sounds horrible.
If you pass, you may need to wake up earlier some days.
Is that okay?
Tamaki-san, you don't look like a morning person. Think you can do it?
I have five alarm clocks.
Is there anything you particularly like about your family running an inn?
I like how we get guests from all over who like to talk about all sorts of things.
Is there anything you've learned from playing tennis?
When you start focusing on only one thing, you have to take a step back and see everything...
Tamaki-san, could you briefly describe your friends?
Natsumi-chan has always been about taking action and responsibility.
Saki-chan looks cool and composed, but she's really very passionate.
Yuka-chan is someone who brings us all together.
If you pass this audition, you won't be able to commute from home.
Would you be able to move to Tokyo?
Yes.
I haven't talked with my parents about it, but I think I can convince them.
Saki...
Could you each tell us what you've done since receiving the notice that you passed the first round?
I practiced dancing every day.
I had my brother watch me.
To make my movements softer, I did rigorous stretching every day.
I'm not good at smiling, so I practiced smiling in front of a mirror every day.
I watched Four Season's concert recordings over and over every day.
Why did I think that was good enough?
Why didn't I do more...
Here is the last question.
If only one of you could pass this audition, what would you do?
Only one of us?
For example, if only you passed.
If that happened, I would congratulate the one who passed first.
And while giving her my full support,
I would practice for the next audition so I could keep up with her.
Thank you.
What's wrong, Tsubaki-chan?
Did you have a bad dream?
Who are you? I've never seen you before.
Could you try making Sakura 10 years younger?
Okay. I'll try.
What's wrong, Tsubaki-chan?
Did you have a bad dream?
A Summer-Colored Miracle
hashiru bus no mado kara
Standing with you head outside
kimi wa mi wo noridashi
The window of the bus
zutto te wo furinagara
Waving your hand back at me
nani ka sakebitsudzukeru
And shouting something I can't hear
kimi no mugiwaraboushi
Even if the wind blows strong
kaze ni sarawaretemo
And takes away your straw hat
kitto boku no kokoro wa
I know that at least in my heart
owaranai natsuyasumi
It's an endless summer vacation
umi wo dakishimeta nishimuki no heya
In a room by the sea, door open wide to the west
sukoshi kowarekaketeita senpuuki
With an electric fan starting to break down
akai watermelon hoobarinagara
Stuffing our faces with bright red watermelon
atsui drill wo katadzuketa
And finishing those piles of homework
kimi to futari de totta
Using a picture of the two of us
shashin shiori ni shite
Together as a bookmark
nikki kakikake no mama
Diaries only half done
owaranai natsuyasumi
It's an endless summer vacation
Here.
How long are you going to keep crying like that?
We can't do anything about it now.
Sorry...
I'm so sorry...
It's okay. I made a lot of mistakes too.
We didn't make it, but I think we did really well.
Yeah! I think so too!
Why didn't I practice more?
Changing the dance right before the audition was a great idea.
Yuka, I always thought you were being a kid when you still wanted to be an idol,
but it's something I really wanted to be.
Natsumi...
It's not like this was our last chance.
Let's try harder next time.
But that's too late!
Saki's going to transfer before next time!
If we passed this audition and became idols, we could be with Saki forever.
Yuka...
That's why you...
I mean, we even wished on the big rock!
That all four of us could become idols together!
Yuka!
You're always just so... Yuka!
Of course I am!
Go—
Going to an audition is going to be easy after I transfer!
The island is in Tokyo, after all.
Saki...
It's so tall!
Come on!
Look at this, Rin!
There's a dragon here!
Really?
It's so cool...
We've done so much this summer...
Yeah.
Thanks to the big rock, we flew...
stuck together, switched bodies...
doubled, disappeared...
You're the reason for most of that.
Not all of it!
We definitely did a lot.
Putting down candles, winning the singing competition...
And we went on a trip.
And finally, the audition today.
It's like there's nothing left for us to do.
Really?
I still want to do more.
If only summer vacation could be longer.
It would be so nice if we could get extensions on summer vacation like karaoke.
You live like it's summer vacation every day.
Hey, that's mean!
Come on.
What should I do about my homework? I'm not done yet...
I'm almost done.
Seriously? That's perfect!
You're just going to copy it?
It's hard copying homework, you know.
You have to change the lead in your pencil to make it look like you did it on different days.
Why not use that effort to solve the problems?
Easy for you to say.
You're so lucky. You don't have to do the homework.
Sorry.
I'm doing the homework too.
I don't have anything better to do with my room all packed.
And I don't want to fall behind when I move, either.
When are you moving?
The 30th.
That's right when we get back.
Do you have a lot to move?
We've been sending a little over at a time,
but it might get crazy on the day we move.
I see...
It looks like everything's all set in your mind.
There's less and less stuff in your room every day.
When you move, all I'll see from my window will be an empty room.
I've seen your room every day since I was a kid, but that's going to change.
I'll change the curtains to that color you liked.
Thanks.
Come on! We have cell phones these days, and we can even use them send videos of ourselves to each other!
And with airplanes, we can go back and forth in a flash!
Though it does cost money.
Don't you feel sad, Saki?
What do you mean?
You're going to live on that island,
with Koharu and Chiharu right there,
so compared to us, without you...
Do you really think that?
That I don't feel sad?
I mean...
Stop, Natsumi.
We don't have much more time to be together.
I wish summer vacation wouldn't end.
Okay!
Hey, Saki.
You said that you could go to auditions? I'm serious about this, you know?
I'll text you when we get one.
Okay...
Make sure you practice every day!
That's a promise!
You're our visuals leader, you know!
Since when?
What are you talking about?
You've always been!
It's the first I've heard it too.
And the leader is, of course, me!
It's not as good as my family's inn, but the bath and food were pretty good.
It's always fun as long as we're together.
Where's Natsumi?
She said that she'd go back first.
Hey, they laid out the futons!
Let's see what's on TV!
The channels are different from Shimoda, right?
Natsumi?
What's wrong?
Dizzy from the bath?
Hey, Natsumi!
How's she doing? Did it go down?
No, but I think the medicine should start working soon.
I'll go get something cold.
Let's go, Rin.
Sorry. Of all days, too...
It's been a long day. It probably just caught up to you.
If your temperature doesn't go down, we'll go to the emergency room.
I think I'll be fine after a little rest.
You three are tired too.
Don't worry about me and get some rest.
You're sick, so just stay quiet and listen to me.
My dad's a doctor, you know.
That just means you're unlicensed.
You just have to talk back, even when you're sick.
Sorry about what I said.
You looked so normal even though you're going to move soon,
so I thought maybe I'm the only one feeling sad.
I've been thinking about it for a long time.
Don't go...
Let's say that was the fever talking.
I can't say anything about Yuka.
I wished that summer vacation could just go on like this forever.
I wished for the same thing.
Is Natsumi awake?
Want something to drink?
What do you have?
Tea, sports drinks, and club soda!
Sports drink.
kyuu ni damarikonde
You suddenly stayed silent,
kimi wa te wo tsunaida
And then you took and held my hand
akanezora ni kieteku kyou wo
We watched as our shadows grew taller,
miokuru nagai kageboushi
And the day sank into the orange sky
houkago wa eien mitai ni
After school always seemed like forever
sayonara wo gomakashiteta ne
We would always try not to say good-bye
dakedo kokoro wa tabidachi no yokan wo shitteta
But deep inside we knew that we would have to go our separate ways
hateshinai mirai he no tamerai wo kakushite
Hiding our worries about everything that lay in the future
hohoemu kimi no yume ga mabushii yo
Your smile I saw in my dreams was just so bright
ato sukoshi no kisetsu wo oshimu you ni hashaida
With the season's end coming closer, we played so much to make up for time
ashita he no kaerimichi
The road back home and to tomorrow
Huh?
Morning.
Hey, weren't we at the inn—
Hello?
This is crazy! Today is yesterday, and today is the audition,
and today is yesterday, and yesterday is today!
What are you trying to say?
Today turned into yesterday, and yesterday is today,
Today is yesterday?
and yesterday was the audition, and today... Today is the audition?
Audition
Okay...
Okay... I got it, so just calm down, okay?
It's exactly the same as yesterday!
The town, the sky, and even breakfast!
What'd you have?
An omelette!
The insides were perfect and still liquid—wait!
We should try sleeping.
No way, this is our chance!
We get another chance at yesterday!
And the audition!
You're right, we can try again!
All right!
This time...
The Endless Summer Vacation
Next time, on Natsuiro Kiseki.
Episode 12: The Endless Summer Vacation.
It won't end.
We won't let it end.
Going on forever, our summer.
Going on forever, our miracle.