Mom, juice!
What's he doing here?!
Yuka.
Morning.
Want one?
One.
One, please.
Flowing off the edge, the end of a dream
A world where we always search for sensations
What kind of spirit will you glow with as you jump into tomorrow?
Just tell me
The beat of the future, a drumbeat in my ears
Do you hear the start of my melody calling you?
I'm ready! The sky is so blue and so high
I'll never forget this moment as we cried together
I promise that I'll keep on running straight ahead
The moment when we understood
shun
stop
road
is a precious non-stop road
If we could be together,
zu
tto
i
ssho
ni
if I could be with you
ki
mi
to
i
ssho
ni
And be happy it would be the best I think
If we could be together, if I could be with you
zu
tto
i
ssho
ssho
ga
That's the key to the world
Are you ready? So believe in the moment
And be amazed at what you have, your determination
Your smile is just so strong and blindingly bright
shii
I'll look straight ahead and say
shin
wa
I won't give in, I've a non-stop mind
stop
mind
A Summer-Colored Miracle
You don't usually help with deliveries, Takashi-kun.
Yuka at Full Speed
Sorry.
Sorry?
I should call you "Senpai."
What's so funny?
You don't need to be so formal.
When is Mizukoshi-san moving?
Saki?
Did I tell you she was moving?
Everyone's talking about it.
Maybe around the end of next month.
When, exactly?
Why?
You gave him Saki's phone number?
No, we have to ask Saki first.
Is your cousin going to ask her out?
Did you like Senpai?
I still do!
He said he didn't like younger girls.
Saki is really grown-up.
Yeah, yeah, I'm still a kid.
Try curling your hair?
They won't even hold a day!
Right.
Must be nice being Saki.
Want one?
I wish...
I wish I were more like Saki.
Saki!
Saki! Saki!
What's going on?
Saki, are you okay?
Why are you here, Natsumi?
Huh? Where am I?
Saki?
Who are you talking to?
Where's Saki?
Huh?
Am I... Saki?
Yeah...
Saki, what's gotten into you?
It's me, Yuka!
Huh?
I'm Saki!
You two, again?!
There he is!
Saki, are you sure you're okay?
Should I get the school nurse?
Who?
My cousin, Takashi-kun.
You used to play with him too.
Saki, I didn't know you had a cousin.
I told you, I'm—
Mizukoshi-san!
He saw us?!
How?!
Natsumi, go!
Why?
Mizukoshi-san.
Um...
Wh-What a coincidence.
That was so phony!
I heard you were moving.
Yes.
To Tokyo?
That's pretty far.
Yes.
Could I—
Go ahead.
Well...
Sano!
Coming!
Sorry, talk to you later.
Could I—
Could I text you sometime?
Of course you can't!
Oh, come on, it's just one date!
A date?! That's your plan?!
Come on! I finally get a chance to be Saki!
Can't I have a little fun?
If you want to go out with Senpai, why not just do it?
You don't have to pretend to be Saki!
Pretending is fine by me.
But—
Don't you have one too?
Someone you wish you could be with forever?
Like Akira from Four Season.
Just think about it.
If you were part of Four Season.
Let's say you suddenly became Fuyumi.
Then...
Found you!
That was a short dream.
I wonder how you can switch back.
Maybe if my dreams come true...
You are not going on a date!
Yuka is out of shape.
It's your body!
Rin's mom went inside.
Let's get this over with.
You're not running away.
I won't run...
What are we wishing for?
For us to switch back!
Can you really wish away another wish?
I wonder...
Come on, let's go!
One, two, three!
Did it work?
Did you really wish?
Yeah.
No you didn't!
One more time!
One, two, three!
Wish harder!
Well?
One, two, three!
We can't switch back!
I'm yelling at myself!
I don't want to yell at myself either!
Looks like fun.
Yeah.
I can tell you it's not!
Listen up, Yuka. We're switching back.
You're not allowed to think about anything but that.
My face looks like Saki-chan's...
One, two, three!
That we switch back!
Yuka!
We can't switch back...
No more...
Saki...
What?
This is bad...
Don't tell me...
You two didn't...
I'm Rinko.
One, two, three!
Yuka.
Natsumi.
Saki.
Rin-chan?
Mama.
Mama?
Oh my, Natsumi, this is Rinko's mom.
Who are you supposed to be?!
How can we help you?
I was going to ask if Rin-chan would mind helping me with something,
but she doesn't appear to be well...
Don't worry! Rinko is full of energy! Right?
Make sure she doesn't find out about the big rock.
Guess I have to go on that date!
You!
What now?
Rinko has to go back to Natsumi's too...
Why?
Natsumi always makes lunch for Daiki-kun.
Sano Takashi
Are you free tomorrow?
Can you cook anything?
Namul.
A Summer-Colored Miracle
Namul?
The aquarium?
Yeah!
He said it has a baby dolphin!
We're going to see the penguins and have lunch after.
Then we're going to see the sea lion show, and then the dolphin show, and then...
Kiss?
Not that!
You won't?
In a dark corner of the aquarium,
with no one around you...
Now I'm all nervous because of you!
I hope it goes all right.
Do I really look like Saki?
If he found out that it was really me...
Open your mouth.
That's how you should look tomorrow.
Aren't you going to stop me?
Do you want me to stop you?
Meanie.
Whatever you wish for is my wish too.
I want it to go well.
Rin, I love you!
No... No more...
Good work.
Here's your allowance.
You don't want it? You always beg me for more.
Um...
Yay! Yay!
I want it!
I can't take this anymore.
Honestly... Yuka hasn't changed a bit.
We're definitely going to be idols like Four Season!
We'll have to start practicing singing now, then.
Come on, Saki, do we have to?
If we're going to be idols, we have to!
Yuka...
Oh, it's just a text.
Morning, everyone.
Sorry about all the trouble.
My dream is going to come true soon, so we can switch back after.
I hope you can wait just a little longer.
Morning.
Yuka.
Good morning!
Yuka!
A
Aizawa
Is she still asleep?
Natsumi!
How long do you plan on sleeping?!
Get up now!
Natsumi! Natsumi!
Stop that! It makes it sound like I overslept!
Are you looking for my sister?
Oh, Daiki. Were you out playing?
Could you call your sister for us?
Okay...
Onee-chan! Your friends are here!
Daiki-kun, did Yuka—I mean, do you know where Saki went?
I saw her walking with a guy a few minutes ago.
Where?!
Um... Standing is a bit dangerous. Should we sit?
No, it's fine.
I-I'm sorry!
It's okay...
Just missed it!
We're running there!
It'll take 20 minutes to get to the aquarium.
You don't have to—
I said we're running!
But you can't run anymore.
We have to stop Yuka now!
We don't know what she'll do!
Kiss?
Anything but that!
We still have time before the show.
Want to look around for a bit?
Yes!
Um...
Was today really okay?
Why do you ask?
I thought you had summer school...
Oh.
Yeah.
I have today off, and...
I wanted to see you.
Let's go.
Yes!
donna ima mo egakeru ki ga suru
I feel like I can paint today any way I want
sono iro nara watashi motteru yo
I have all the colors I need to do it
kimi ga iru natsu no keshiki
Every single moment of this summer
ichibyou ichibyou ga mabushii na
That I've spent with you is just so beautiful
kinou nayande eranda skirt wa
The skirt I spent all yesterday thinking to wear
yappa sukoshi mijikasugita kamo
Feels a little short now that it's today
nani mo ittekurenai
But you don't say anything about it
Shoot, I got way too excited.
I'm Saki-chan. I'm Saki-chan.
aruku te to te furesou ni naru
And as we walk, our hands nearly touch
Thanks for waiting.
Yuka?
hajimete no kono omoi wa
It's the first time I've ever felt like this
Oh, sorry.
Yuka does that a lot too.
donna kotoba ni mo dekinai kara
It's not something I can put into words
Oh, really?
keikaku nante iranai yo
I don't need a fancy plan or anything
It's kind of cute.
Cu-Cute?!
futari de itai sore dake nano
I just want to be with you, that's all
I'm so sorry!
Don't worry about me.
Did it get on your clothes?
I-I don't think so.
They make a good couple.
You think?
Leave them alone?
No. If they start with any funny business, we're going to stop them.
sukoshi haneta maegami naoshite
I messed up my hair, so I'll fix it a little
What kind of funny business?
Like... ki-kissing.
mukiatte suwatta cafe de oshaberi
While we sit down at a café to talk a bit
Would they do that on their first date?
nagareteru bossa nova kara
The bossa nova playing in the store
I don't know, but... I don't know!
otona kibun ga todokimashita
Makes me feel a little more grown up
Get down!
cappuccino de yureru heart mark
The cream in my cappuccino, shaped like a heart
Come on, let's go.
kesanai you ni yakedo shinai you ni
So it stays that way, and I don't burn myself
yukkuri jikan wo sugosou
Let's relax and take it slow for now
kimi no koto wo motto shiritai
I want to get to know you better
chikadzuita kono kyori ni wa
As we talked and got closer together
yosougai no doki doki matteta yo
My heart raced faster than I thought it could
tomodachi ni mo hanashitai
I want to tell my friends all about it
dakedo yappari himitsu ni shiyou
But on second thought, I'll keep it a secret
Takashi-kun is right next to me.
hatsu omoi day natsu ni somare
The first I've felt this way, this summer day
It's so strange.
We used to play together all the time, but now...
Thank you for today.
I had a lot of fun.
Yes. I did, too.
If only...
If only time could stop, just like this.
I wish...
Takashi-kun?
It's okay. You can use my first name.
Ta-Takashi-kun.
Yeah.
Um... Then you can call me...
Call me...
by my first name...
Please call me "Saki."
Huh?!
What? Why?
Why am I crying?
Saki-san...
I knew it all along.
Who Takashi-kun likes...
Who Takashi-kun sees right now...
Yuka!
Rinko?!
Excuse us.
Wait!
Rinko!
Yuka?
Wait, who was...
I'm sorry.
Huh?
I got in the way.
Even though I said I wanted it to go well.
Did you want to kiss him?
No...
It's okay.
Thanks.
Welcome back.
Hey, mister, we're closing.
Right...
Mizukoshi-san?
Thank you very much for today.
Hello.
Thanks to Yuka,
I think it will be a good memory.
Thanks to Yuka, I think it will be a good memory.
Thanks to Yuka?
Take care.
"Take care," huh?
What? No emotes?!
You want me to put hearts on a rejection text?
I'll never be able to be Saki.
Isn't that obvious?
You're Yuka.
Because Yuka is Yuka...
Huh? What?
Nothing.
Huh? What did you say?
Come on, tell me!
All right! Race you to the store!
Drinks are on the last one there!
Hey! Wait!
Come on! Why can't I run?!
Yuka's out of shape!
Don't make fun of me!
Come on! Wait for me!
kyuu ni damarikonde
You suddenly stayed silent,
kimi wa te wo tsunaida
And then you took and held my hand
akanezora ni kieteku kyou wo
We watched as our shadows grew taller,
miokuru nagai kageboushi
And the day sank into the orange sky
houkago wa eien mitai ni
After school always seemed like forever
sayonara wo gomakashiteta ne
We would always try not to say good-bye
dakedo kokoro wa tabidachi no yokan wo shitteta
But deep inside we knew that we would have to go our separate ways
hateshinai mirai he no tamerai wo kakushite
Hiding our worries about everything that lay in the future
hohoemu kimi no yume ga mabushii yo
Your smile I saw in my dreams was just so bright
ato sukoshi no kisetsu wo oshimu you ni hashaida
With the season's end coming closer, we played so much to make up for time
ashita he no kaerimichi
The road back home and to tomorrow
Oh, that Yuka!
Using my body to go on a date!
Let it go. It's in the past.
I will not.
I have to get her back for this.
You're going to get even with her?
Of course. Saki-sama doesn't just sit back and let things slide.
Look out, Yuka!
Summer Colds and Whales
Next time, on Natsuiro Kiseki.
Episode 5: Summer Colds and Whales.
Saki, making someone catch a cold is going too far.
Huh? What are you talking about? I haven't done anything yet.