Arm circles, inward!
Five, six, seven, eight!
One, two, three, four, five, six!
Legs, shoulder-width! Swing those arms!
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight!
One, two, three, four, five, six!
Arms up and to one side!
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight!
One, two, three, four, five, six!
Touch your toes and bend back!
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight!
One, two...
What?!
We... really flew...
Onee-chan!
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven...
Flowing off the edge, the end of a dream
A world where we always search for sensations
What kind of spirit will you glow with as you jump into tomorrow?
Just tell me
The beat of the future, a drumbeat in my ears
Do you hear the start of my melody calling you?
I'm ready! The sky is so blue and so high
I'll never forget this moment as we cried together
I promise that I'll keep on running straight ahead
The moment when we understood
shun
stop
road
is a precious non-stop road
If we could be together,
zu
tto
i
ssho
ni
if I could be with you
ki
mi
to
i
ssho
ni
And be happy it would be the best I think
If we could be together, if I could be with you
zu
tto
i
ssho
ssho
ga
That's the key to the world
Are you ready? So believe in the moment
And be amazed at what you have, your determination
Your smile is just so strong and blindingly bright
shii
I'll look straight ahead and say
shin
wa
I won't give in, I've a non-stop mind
stop
mind
A Summer-Colored Miracle
A
Aizawa
Wishing Together
Saki-chan.
What are you doing?
How many times have I told you to knock?!
I'm sorry.
Here. Your laundry.
We're back!
It's so hot!
Your shoes!
Hey, Natsumi.
Are you fighting with Saki-chan again?
Oh, not really...
Saki-chan's mom is worried, you know.
You're not in elementary school anymore! Make up with her already!
I know!
Mom, Keita and Yuusuke say they're coming over after breakfast!
It's all Saki's fault, anyway.
It's way too early for this!
So hot!
Hey, yesterday—
Are you going out like that?
Well, it's hot, so—
We're not friends right now, so don't talk to me!
Can't you tell when people are trying to be nice?
Thanks, but no thanks!
Yuka?
Yuka!
Onee-chan, do you know where Yuka is?
Nope. I haven't seen her all morning.
That girl. She said she would help me during summer vacation.
And you believed her?
Hey, would her sister care to help?
No, thank you.
Here.
Make sure you separate any trash you see.
Mama, the big rock—
Oh, you don't have to sweep around there today.
Is something the matter?
I'll sweep around the big rock too.
That I can become an idol.
That I can become a model.
That I can become a billionaire.
That I can become smarter.
That my homework was all done.
That I won't have to help around the house.
That I can get more allowance.
That I never get fat.
That I can—
Yuka?
Morning, Rin!
Wow, that's a lot.
I started writing these down as soon as I got home!
Has anything worked?
Nothing!
If any of them did, I would be an idol and a billionaire and a model...
Do you think it has to be all four of us?
Maybe.
But you know, with Natsumi and Saki like that...
Are they still fighting?
They're both really stubborn.
I hope they make up soon.
If Natsumi and Saki made up and stuck together, they'd be unstoppable.
If they're together, they're unstoppable.
I hope they make up soon.
Saki-chan?
What's she up to?
Saki?!
Natsumi?!
What are you doing in my room?!
It's not like I want to be in your stupid room!
My room isn't stupid!
Get off of me! It's hot!
Same to you! Get off me!
Same to you!
What is going on?
I can't get off!
Get off of me!
Get off me!
Same to you!
This isn't funny!
What are you doing?! Get off!
What is going on?
It's like I'm stuck to you!
Clothes
Saki
A
What in the world is going on here?
Wait a second...
Maybe the big rock...
Don't be stupid! A rock can't—
But we really flew, you know!
This is just like yesterday!
Or are you trying to stay stuck to me?
Of course I'm not!
See? It's gotta be supernatural, then!
I didn't wish for something like this, though!
Neither did I...
Yuka?!
That girl!
What are you doing?
I'm not doing anything!
One, two!
Now let's go.
Hang on! You're going out like that?
Do you have to wear my clothes?
You want me to go out in my underwear?
It's too hot for this!
My thoughts exactly!
Nothing's happening at all.
Maybe it really has to be all four of us.
I hope they make up soon.
Me too.
A Summer-Colored Miracle
Saki-chan? Is something wrong?
Oh, Natsumi-chan...
Thank you for having me.
Come on, let's go.
Here, use these shoes.
Stomp the heel and I'll kill you.
Don't tell me what to do!
Would you like something to eat?
No, thank you.
I don't want anything.
Good-bye!
Stop that!
It's too hot for this!
Right back at you!
Weren't those two fighting?
It looks like... they made up.
Huh? Nee-chan?
What are you doing?
What am I doing? Why do you ask?
Hey, Daiki!
Never fear, Keita's here!
What was that?
Sounded cool, right?
More like lame.
Hey!
Let's go.
Don't boss me around!
Should I ask Mama more about the rock?
This kind of thing feels like it
wouldn't work if we told someone.
Oh, I see.
It would be nice to ask without anyone finding out,
but your mom has that intuition thing down.
I'll see what I can do.
Is that all you have to do today?
Yeah. For today, at least.
Let's go get some ice cream, then!
Don't you have to help around your house?
Yeah, maybe not today. It's really hot.
Hey!
They're stuck together.
Maybe they made up?
But something isn't right...
They look mad.
Yuka, let's get out of here.
They're running away!
Not from me, they're not!
Wait!
What are you doing?!
Don't just start running!
Let's go!
One, two, three!
Yuka! Rinko!
They're coming after us.
What's going on here?
Come on, let's go.
Don't run away!
Wait right there!
What is it? Why are they mad?
Because they're stuck together.
Because they're stuck together?
You mean...
I mean it! The big rock!
Why are they running away? We told them to stop!
Don't you get it? It means they're guilty!
We don't know that!
It's obvious!
Stop!
Natsumi?
Saki-chan?
Ow!
Turn sideways!
Huh?
I don't see them.
Where'd they go?
They're really stuck together.
Because we wished for it?
Don't all four of us have to wish for it?
Maybe it works with just two?
They're definitely hiding around here somewhere.
Clothes
Saki
A
Natsumi?
Why didn't you tell us you were moving?
Why are you bringing that up now?
Because it's important.
We promised that we—
I told you I never promised anything!
Did too!
Did not!
Did—
There!
They found us!
This way!
They're really mad.
If you were stuck onto me and
couldn't get off, you'd be mad too!
Really?
Come on! Over here!
Stop!
Ow...
We were so close!
Jump!
Wow!
This is no time to be impressed!
Huh? My sister?
Yeah. Right, Yuusuke?
I was in that place by the mountains and looked up,
and I saw four girls flying.
No way!
I really saw them!
I'm sure it was your sister and her friends!
Well, if you say so...
Coming through!
Stop!
They sure flew.
Yeah.
No, it wasn't like that!
Huh?
A
Singing Competition
Yuka, this way!
Oh, no you don't!
Yuka, hang in there!
Get back here!
Do something about this!
I don't... know what... to do!
I can't run anymore!
Yuka, don't stop now!
Give up!
Just a bit more!
Rin, that's dangerous!
What the heck did you two do?
Yuka said...
What'd she say?
If you got together, you'd be unstoppable.
I thought the same thing.
fukinukeru kaze wo oikoshite yukou
We can fly faster than the wind rushing by us
Why is she going there?
yuzurenai kimochi ga hane wo kureta no
Our determination gave us the wings to do so
She's too tired! She's not looking where she's going!
That idiot!
donna mirai ni suru koe ni shita nara
What kind of future do you want? Just tell me
Stop, Yuka!
Yuka!
Yuka said that if you stuck together, you'd be unstoppable.
kasanaru doki doki omou mama ni kakedasou
And we can chase after it, hearts together, let's go
Saki and me, unstoppable?
Well, now...
nee suki na iro ni natte tobou
Hey, let's be the colors we want and fly
...isn't that obvious?
We're stopping Yuka right here.
Grab her from both sides!
Got it!
ima shika dekinai koto bakari da yo
Doing all the things we can only do now
One, two, three, go!
Driving to the Blue Sky
Driving to the blue sky
kono toki wo tomete
I wish now could be forever
arittake no negai wo kaitemitai
So I can write all the wishes I could ever want
I will go ashita he to
But I will move on to tomorrow
mayowanai de tsuki susundekou
Without hesitating, just keep flying on
dare mo shiranai yume no saki wo
To see what no one has seen before, beyond the dream
Looks like you made up.
What do you mean?
Just what I said.
You and I thought the same thing.
We felt the same way.
I think that's why Yuka and Rin's wish ended.
You and I...
Yeah.
Um...
I'm sorry.
Yeah, me too.
Saki, we have club starting next Monday.
Let's play again.
We don't need a goal or a dream or anything.
I just want to play tennis with you.
Okay.
Hey!
You two okay?
She definitely doesn't feel guilty at all.
Hey, let's go to the big rock!
Right now?
Yeah. If we wish for something together, it'll be perfect!
Come on, let's wish for something together!
That all four of us can become idols together!
Count me out!
Hey, don't go to sleep!
Me too!
Hey, wait!
Same here.
What? You too?!
Come on! Why are you three sleeping?!
We're singing at the Taiko Festival, you know!
We're going to win, then we're going to pass an audition, then—
Are you listening?
Did you hear me? Hey!
Aizawa Natsumi
Sorry.
kyuu ni damarikonde
You suddenly stayed silent,
kimi wa te wo tsunaida
And then you took and held my hand
akanezora ni kieteku kyou wo
We watched as our shadows grew taller,
miokuru nagai kageboushi
And the day sank into the orange sky
houkago wa eien mitai ni
After school always seemed like forever
sayonara wo gomakashiteta ne
We would always try not to say good-bye
dakedo kokoro wa tabidachi no yokan wo shitteta
But deep inside we knew that we would have to go our separate ways
hateshinai mirai he no tamerai wo kakushite
Hiding our worries about everything that lay in the future
hohoemu kimi no yume ga mabushii yo
Your smile I saw in my dreams was just so bright
ato sukoshi no kisetsu wo oshimu you ni hashaida
With the season's end coming closer, we played so much to make up for time
ashita he no kaerimichi
The road back home and to tomorrow
Witches of the World
Thanks to Yuka, I had a horrible day.
What'll you do if you become an idol tomorrow morning?
Well, that wouldn't be so...
You're okay with it?!
But you know, if anything can come true,
then I'd wish for something that normally wouldn't happen in real life.
Like what?
Like being able to understand what cats say.
Oh? Saki, that's pretty...
I didn't say that! I did not say that!
Sometimes Girls Fly in Shimoda
Next time, on Natsuiro Kiseki.
Episode 3: Sometimes Girls Fly in Shimoda.
Oh no, Saki! Meow!
It looks like someone saw us flying, meow!
Me-no-w!