Once the cultural festival ends, Shiina's...
Shiina Mashiro
No Subject
Sorata awake?
Shiina Mashiro
No Subject
Sorata awake?
Shiina Mashiro
No Subject
Sorata awake?
Shiina Mashiro
No Subject
Sorata awake?
Shiina Mashiro
No Subject
Sorata awake?
Shiina Mashiro
No Subject
Sorata awake?
Shiina Mashiro
No Subject
Sorata awake?
Shiina Mashiro
No Subject
Sorata awake?
Shiina Mashiro
No Subject
Sorata awake?
Shiina Mashiro
No Subject
Sorata awake?
Shiina Mashiro
No Subject
Sorata awake?
Shiina Mashiro
No Subject
Sorata awake?
Shiina Mashiro
No Subject
Sorata awake?
Shiina Mashiro
No Subject
Sorata awake?
Shiina Mashiro
No Subject
Sorata awake?
Shiina Mashiro
No Subject
Sorata awake?
Shiina Mashiro
No Subject
Sorata awake?
Shiina Mashiro
No Subject
Sorata awake?
Shiina Mashiro
No Subject
Sorata awake?
Shiina Mashiro
No Subject
Sorata awake?
Shiina Mashiro
No Subject
Sorata awake?
Shiina Mashiro
No Subject
Sorata awake?
Shiina Mashiro
No Subject
Sorata awake?
Shiina Mashiro
No Subject
Sorata awake?
Shiina Mashiro
No Subject
Sorata awake?
Shiina Mashiro
No Subject
Sorata awake?
Shiina Mashiro
No Subject
Sorata awake?
Shiina Mashiro
No Subject
Sorata awake?
Shiina Mashiro
No Subject
Sorata awake?
Shiina Mashiro
No Subject
Sorata awake?
Shiina Mashiro
No Subject
Sorata awake?
What?
Shiina Mashiro
No Subject
I want to see you
You...
Stay with me until I sleep.
Keep it down, okay?
Aoyama and Rita'll flip if they find out.
Okay.
Well, good night.
I'll sleep on the floor too.
What? Why'd I give you the bed, then—
Sorata.
Did I hurt you too?
But then you made a huge hit!
I compared myself to Shiina and made myself worry.
But if I hadn't done that, I never would've faced myself.
That's right.
If Shiina goes back to England, I'll...
Nyaboron. We have to make it the best memory.
Mashiro, I need to...
Again with this?
The best memory, huh?
The Power of Love at the Cultural Festival
Galactic Cat
Nyaboron
This is our audience?!
Galactic Cat
Nyaboron
It's only natural, considering how good the staff is.
How humble of you.
That's quite the crowd.
Oh, Student Council President.
I hope the show lives up to the hype.
I jumped through hoops to g—
Attention, overflow guests!
This student council member is in charge of the event! Please follow him!
What?! Mitaka?!
Wh-Why me?!
Stop!
No pushing!
Form a single-file line!
That was mean, Jin-san.
Making the cultural festival run smooth as a whistle is part of the student council's job.
I can see why he looks at you that way now.
Too bad I don't care much for guy love.
It's the look of hate, not love!
Excuse me, personnel coming through.
What's this?
Part of a motion sensor system, I'm guessing.
Long time no see.
What are you doing here?!
Me?
I'm here to see the show.
The fruits of our successors' efforts at Sakurasou.
Nekosuke-san!
Oh man!
My heart's gonna pop outta my mouth!
I'll be sure to push it back down if it does.
Kanda-kun?
Yep.
This is what a catgirl should look like.
You look good.
You finally said it...
Done tuning the sensors.
The guests are all in their seats.
All right! It's assembly time!
Merry friends, assemble!
We're already here.
Now Kouhai-kun will give us a great speech!
Me?!
You're the director.
It's your job.
The game parameters are set the way you wanted.
If they call it shit, it's your fault.
This isn't the time to say that...
Don't worry.
Come on, Kanda-kun.
Let's all enjoy every second of these 30 minutes!
Huh?!
Enjoy? Are you—
I'll enjoy it.
Yeah.
All right!
Let's enjoy!
Galactic Cat Nyaboron!
Galactic Cat Nyaboron
This is the story of those who rose to defend the Earth
from the space invaders known as the Nyangolownians!
A story of love and courage!
Wow...
Damn, Sakurasou is crazy!
This is Nekoko.
I've arrived at the rendezvous point.
You must be Nyaboron's pilots!
You'll be joining me in piloting the feliform robot, Nyaboron!
Light up the glow sticks that were on your seats!
When the time comes for you to control Nyaboron, icons will appear onscreen.
We need everyone to use them as the instructions say!
Raise your right hand.
Raise your right hand!
Ready, go!
Good job, everyone!
Now it's time to save the galaxy!
You're doing great, Aoyama.
You've got it under control.
The enemy space ship is over 5,000 meters long!
Aoyama plays the part of the heroine Nekoko onstage
The United Forces of Earth were wiped out in an instant!
and gets the audience immersed in the story.
Damn you all! Quit your damn meowing!
Aoyama takes the parts of narrator, actress, and game guide.
Here we go.
The first motion sensing part is coming up.
Damn you, Nyangolownians!
I'll send you to the deepest pits of Hell!
Raise both hands.
All right, everyone!
Ready, go!
Good!
All right! It's going great!
The general leading the Nyangolownian invasion is Ein the Catphotic.
Nekoko's lover Nekosuke was one of the millions killed by Ein.
Nekosuke-san!
I can't imagine a world without you!
A life without you is meaningless!
But still, I must defend this planet!
We evoke the audience's emotions by adding flashbacks between battles,
and boost their confidence for the final battle in the fights against the underlings.
Clap. Clap. Clap.
Come on, everyone! Stand up!
And now...
Swing hands down.
Ready, set, go!
And then, the final battle against the Nyangolownian general, Ein the Catphotic.
A surprise attack by Ein!
Nyaboron receives a surprise attack by Ein and takes a lot of damage.
This isn't an audience control mistake; it's part of the story.
Damn you!
Hotter...
Hotter!
Hotter! Hotter! Hotter!
Nyaboron's energy gauge nearly reaches zero.
At this rate, we'll lose!
But how can we fight back? Nekosuke-san...
Crap. What's going to happen now?
We're almost dead.
I know!
Everyone, please!
Give Nyaboron your love!
Shout your love!
The feelings that lie deepest in your heart!
Whatever they are,
just shout them out!
Your passion will become Nyaboron's strength!
Nanami's really into this!
Please...
Please work!
All together, everyone!
Shout now!
All of your love!
Shout my love?
Right?
You gonna do it?
No way.
Why?
It's no good.
The audience is hesitating.
Please! We need your love!
Hey, they need your love.
Then why don't you shout?
Not good.
That was one word too much.
Shout your love!
No matter how well integrated it is, the bar is too high for the audience.
The creators' passion is a definite necessity.
But when they try to force their own emotions on the audience, the audience won't like it.
They lose their audience.
This is my fault...
Sorata?
The best memory...
Shiina wanted the best memory...
I wanted to make it here, together with us...
Shiina?
Thank you...
for everything!
Mashiro?
What was that?
"Thank you"?
That voice...
Mashiro-chan?
All right! Me too!
Jin! Stop looking at Fuuka and look at me!
I want to shout too!
Ryuunosuke! Give me your e-mail address!
You don't need to shout that!
What the heck?
Sounds kinda fun.
Hey, it's the cultural festival!
Let's shout too!
Nyaboron! Hang in there!
Kyousuke-kun, I love you!
Damn it, Matsuri!
Suganuma! Give me my money back!
I love you!
It hurts.
Just a little more!
Shout your love!
Your love is coming through to Nyaboron!
Mashiro.
There's a lot more that I wish I could tell you, but...
No, Mashiro! Thank you!
Energy charge complete!
All right, everyone!
Shout! Meatball Beam!
Ready, go!
Meatball Beam!
And so, the Earth was saved from the evil hands of the Nyangolownians.
Thank you, everyone.
Thank you, Nyaboron.
May this planet and its love live on forever.
The
End
The staff takes a bow on the stage after a performance!
I'll never forget.
I'll never forget this day.
Should've expected as much from your students.
Thanks.
Mind if I stopped by Sakurasou sometime?
Of course. You're not welcome.
Director        Kanda Sorata
Production
The Merry Friends of Sakurasou
Director        Kanda Sorata
Production
The Merry Friends of Sakurasou
Director        Kanda Sorata
Production
The Merry Friends of Sakurasou
Director        Kanda Sorata
Production
The Merry Friends of Sakurasou
Director        Kanda Sorata
Production
The Merry Friends of Sakurasou
Director        Kanda Sorata
Production
The Merry Friends of Sakurasou
Director        Kanda Sorata
Production
The Merry Friends of Sakurasou
Director        Kanda Sorata
Production
The Merry Friends of Sakurasou
Director        Kanda Sorata
Production
The Merry Friends of Sakurasou
Director        Kanda Sorata
Production
The Merry Friends of Sakurasou
Director        Kanda Sorata
Production
The Merry Friends of Sakurasou
Director        Kanda Sorata
Production
The Merry Friends of Sakurasou
Director        Kanda Sorata
Production
The Merry Friends of Sakurasou
Director        Kanda Sorata
Production
The Merry Friends of Sakurasou
Director        Kanda Sorata
Production
The Merry Friends of Sakurasou
Director        Kanda Sorata
Production
The Merry Friends of Sakurasou
Director        Kanda Sorata
Production
The Merry Friends of Sakurasou
Director        Kanda Sorata
Production
The Merry Friends of Sakurasou
Director        Kanda Sorata
Production
The Merry Friends of Sakurasou
Director        Kanda Sorata
Production
The Merry Friends of Sakurasou
Director        Kanda Sorata
Production
The Merry Friends of Sakurasou
Director        Kanda Sorata
Production
The Merry Friends of Sakurasou
Director        Kanda Sorata
Production
The Merry Friends of Sakurasou
Director        Kanda Sorata
Production
The Merry Friends of Sakurasou
Director        Kanda Sorata
Production
The Merry Friends of Sakurasou
Director        Kanda Sorata
Production
The Merry Friends of Sakurasou
Director        Kanda Sorata
Production
The Merry Friends of Sakurasou
Director        Kanda Sorata
Production
The Merry Friends of Sakurasou
Director        Kanda Sorata
Production
The Merry Friends of Sakurasou
Director        Kanda Sorata
Production
The Merry Friends of Sakurasou
Director        Kanda Sorata
Production
The Merry Friends of Sakurasou
Director        Kanda Sorata
Production
The Merry Friends of Sakurasou
Director        Kanda Sorata
Production
The Merry Friends of Sakurasou
Director        Kanda Sorata
Production
The Merry Friends of Sakurasou
Director        Kanda Sorata
Production
The Merry Friends of Sakurasou
Director        Kanda Sorata
Production
The Merry Friends of Sakurasou
Director        Kanda Sorata
Production
The Merry Friends of Sakurasou
Director        Kanda Sorata
Production
The Merry Friends of Sakurasou
Director        Kanda Sorata
Production
The Merry Friends of Sakurasou
Director        Kanda Sorata
Production
The Merry Friends of Sakurasou
Director        Kanda Sorata
Production
The Merry Friends of Sakurasou
Director        Kanda Sorata
Production
The Merry Friends of Sakurasou
Director        Kanda Sorata
Production
The Merry Friends of Sakurasou
Director        Kanda Sorata
Production
The Merry Friends of Sakurasou
Director        Kanda Sorata
Production
The Merry Friends of Sakurasou
Director        Kanda Sorata
I'll never, ever forget this day.
This day that we ran so far to reach.
Every one of us, together.
That was so arousing!
Every inch of my body is still spasming in ecstasy!
My libido just won't stand down!
Then why not use that libido to pack the van?
Okay...
By the way, that thing you shouted...
Fuuka is one of my ex-girlfriends.
At this point, she's just a childhood friend I haven't talked to in ages,
and your sister.
That's all.
This necklace...
You didn't buy it for Mashiron?
Huh?
Nothing! What's this for?
The guys in the class next to mine forced me to buy something.
Jin! Put it on me!
Sheesh, can't you do it yourself?
Huh?
Wait, Misaki!
Isn't that...
Oh, there you are, Kanda-kun!
Gal
actic Cat
Nyaboron
What's up, Aoyama?
I can't find Mashiro or Rita-san anywhere.
Mashiro has people waiting for her.
She's going back to where she belongs.
She's going back to England already?
England?
But she never agreed to go with Rita-san...
No way! Why?
Why didn't you stop her, Kanda-kun?!
It's not up to me.
If Shiina wants to go back, then I can't stop her.
Anyway, I already told her what I wanted to.
What you wanted to?
Just "Thank you"?
You heard that?
That's all you wanted to say?!
I bet it ain't!
What do you really want?!
I wanted to stop her, damn it!
Kanda-kun...
She said she was going to draw manga...
She worked so hard to get that serialization...
What the hell?!
What the hell...
We spent half a year together...
How can she just throw it all away?
Her manga, and all of us!
Kanda-kun, is that what you wanted to shout during Nyaboron?
You'd better tell her that now, then.
Let's find Mashiro!
I'll check inside!
She's not answering...
Nanami?
Miyahara-kun! Have you seen—
Nyaboron was amazing!
You were perfect! I was so moved!
Um, thanks, but I'm—
I shouted at the Meatball Beam part too!
Did you hear me?
No, I couldn't...
Nanami...
I love you.
Fire!
U-Um...
Sorry, I...
I've never thought of you like that, so...
So... Um...
I-I'm really sorry!
I couldn't! Because I...
Mashiro...
I really need to—
Kouhai-kun!
Mashiron and Rittan left!
What? The airport!
Aoyama-san told us everything!
Get in!
Live up your
youth!
Okay, Mashiro.
Mashiro, don't go...
Sorata?
Don't go...
Don't go!
Don't go, damn it!
Don't leave us!
Don't leave me!
Sorata.
I heard you.
Stay at Sakurasou!
I'm not going anywhere.
I just came to see Rita off.
Wh— Wha—
What?!
Hugging at the airport?
I guess it's true that average-looking guys
pull more aggressive moves, Sorata.
Rita?! You tricked me!
Please. Don't make me the villain.
But you said...
You said Mashiro was going back to where she belongs!
And doesn't Mashiro belong at Sakurasou?
Rita-san, does that mean...
I'm glad I came to Japan.
I'm going back to England.
Everyone, I leave Mashiro in your care.
Rittan, it's too soon!
We haven't even had a good-bye hot pot party!
Take this with you, former freeloader.
It's Kanda's e-mail address.
Why mine?!
You're so cold.
What do you think love is?
Love is simply an electrical bug in the human neural circuit.
You can throw your unnecessary emotions into that trash can there.
Looks like I'll need to punish you!
An attack like that won't work on me—
Now then, everyone...
Have a nice day!
Live up your youth!
Rittan!
Rita-san, we'll meet again, won't we?
So you can make a real smile.
What's wrong?
I feel weird right here.
It's throbbing really hard.
Ever since that.
Since what?
When you told me not to go.
Th-That was...
When you held me so tight.
Forget that ever happened!
I can't.
It won't go away.
Your voice is still in my ears.
The feel of your body...
Don't make it sound lewd!
What happened to me?
Is this...
...love?
sugiru dake no jikan ja kuyashii
Watching the days go past makes me feel so empty
kizamanakucha
I need to leave a mark
koko ni iru to kokoro ga sakebu shunkan
I'm here, I exist, my soul is screaming
I'm dreaming
mayoi nagara namida wo nomikonda
Wandering this wide world, I held back my tears
bukiyou da ne yume mo toomawari
I didn't know what to do,
taking the long way to my dreams
oozora wo miage nani mo iezu
Looking up to the sky and not saying anything
mune ga itamu wake kangaeteita
I kept thinking about why
my heart always hurt so much
mune ga itamu wake kangaeteita
DAYS of DASH
Days of dash
kaze wo hashirinukete
We were running against the wind
kimi to boku no naka de
I wonder what started between us
nani ga hajimatta no darou
When we were always running back then
wakarannai kedo
I don't know what it was, but
kirakira hikaru taiyou ga
The sun is shining above us now
terasu basho wo zutto susumou
Let's run forever down the road it shows us
eien nado
Even if I don't know
shiranai keredo
If it goes on forever
Hikari is happy Nyaboron went well too.
Just a Stone's Throw to Winter
By the way, Hikari...
What is love?