itsumo koko ni ite hoshii kuse ni
I want you to stay with me forever,
When she moved into the same dorm as me,
I thought she'd be trouble.
I started talking to him after he picked up an abandoned cat,
itsumo koko ni ite hoshii kokoro kakushita
But I hid that feeling deep in my heart
and we were in the same class for our second year too.
Former Freeloader
Sakurasou, apartments for the school's problem children.
aenakunatta samishii hi mo
Even on days when I can't see you,
kimochi tashikametai
I want to know these feelings are true
But because we were so close, it became even harder for me to tell her.
te wo nobaseba fureau kyori na no ni
We're so close, I could touch you if I reached out my hand
Telling him how I felt became the most difficult thing in the world.
sono ippo ga fumidasenai watashi
But I can't take that one little step
me wo tojitara setsunasa ga koboresou de
When I close my eyes, the sadness overwhelms my heart, so
I call your name again
Kanda Sorata
Could you stay somewhere other than
the dorm on Christmas Eve?
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Why?
Kanda Sorata
Do you really want to know?
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Actually, no. I'm not interested.
Okay.
I'll see what I can do.
A
Could you stay somewhere other than the dorm on Christmas Eve?
Why?
Do you really want to know?
Actually, no. I'm not interested.
What'd he say?
He'll see what he can do.
Do you think he'll really stay somewhere else?
What about Mashiron?
Windows and Lights on Christmas Eve
Oh, yeah. Her publisher is holding a party on the 24th, so...
So we just need to make sure Chihiro-sensei stays out?
And Nanamin and Kouhai-kun are on a date, so...
Oh, wow! This might work!
It's not a date.
Mashiron's Room
Knock,
please!
Then get out of me!
I haven't really talked to Shiina since then.
Sorata
What are you doing?
I'm cold.
Yeah, I'll bet.
Want it?
Is it good?
Yeah.
Want some too?
Is it good?
Is this supposed to be a skit or something?
It's not a skit. It's baumkuchen.
I know that.
What I'm asking is—
Sorata, you're mad.
What does that have to do with anything?
I'm sorry.
About what?
Don't say you're sorry if you don't know why you're apologizing.
Anyway, how's your manga coming along?
Don't you have to draw something for the New Year's issue or something?
Sorata, you're mad.
I told you, I'm not mad!
Did you hear all of that?
From start to finish.
How did I sound?
Would you be happy if I told you that you've got a chip on your shoulder?
That's your chance!
A confession on Christmas Eve...
You're doing it!
Why should I?
"Why"?
There's trouble in paradise for Kanda-kun and Shiina-san!
And you and Kanda-kun are going on a date on Christmas Eve!
Stop that! It's not a date!
Kanda-kun's dropping Mashiro off at a party and picking her up when it ends.
He and I are just going to see a play and have a meal together while we wait for her.
Sounds like a date to me.
I just said it wasn't!
Then what is it?
A date?
Told you.
What're you gonna wear?
I don't know yet.
Make sure you wear a skirt.
Jeans are a horrible idea.
A skirt?
Rumi-san
Delete this entry?
Cancel
Don't study too hard.
You might actually make it into that university in Osaka at this rate.
That's not something you should be saying to a friend who's trying his utmost to get into his reach school.
Since when are you my "friend"?
Oh, my bad. Make that "best friend."
So, what do you need, Student Council President?
Former Student Council President.
Are you serious about going to Osaka?
Hauhau must have told you.
You two get along so—
This isn't about us.
Is it really okay?
You won't see each other every day anymore.
I'm okay with that.
I know you are.
You'll find a woman to fool around with easily enough when you get there.
But Kamiigusa—
I won't find one.
I broke up with all the women I was fooling around with.
And Misaki isn't alone anymore.
The people at Sakurasou?
Yeah.
Still not convinced?
What do you want?
What do you mean?
What do you really want?
Tell me.
I want her to see me as somebody.
What are you talking about?
I think she sees you as more than just somebody.
That's because she loves me.
That's not what I want.
I don't just want to be somebody she loves;
I want her to see me as somebody.
Why?
Because I really love her.
How about this one?
I don't look good in it.
Don't say that! You look so cute!
Let's get hitched, Nanamin—
What? You're taking it off?
Then I'll let you borrow these!
Sexy underwear!
Kouhai-kun won't be able to control himself!
What?! Where does Kanda-kun play into this?!
And I'm not showing anyone my underwear!
You can do it!
I won't!
And are you really going through with this, Kamiigusa-senpai?
With what?
With confessing on Christmas Eve.
Aren't you scared, Senpai?
You'll be laying your feelings bare.
What are you talking about, Nanamin?
Of course I'm scared.
I've been in love with Jin since elementary school.
I didn't really realize it until I was in middle school.
But yeah, I'm scared.
If I think about it even a little bit, I won't be able to confess.
I'll be stuck on the track of terror for another lap!
Track?
It starts when I feel like, "I need to tell Jin how I feel! I can't live like this!"
"But I'm scared! What if he turns me down?!"
"Well, I guess we could stay the way we are. That way, I can stay with Jin forever..."
"But I still want to be more lovey-dovey with Jin!"
"He has other girls that he's going out with; what if he chooses one of them over me?!"
And then I end up back here.
I think I understand.
I've probably done a hundred laps around it since middle school.
A hundred?
Yeah.
I'm getting tired of seeing the same thing over and over.
That's why...
I'm closing my eyes and jumping right out!
What's out there?
Outer space?
That sounds really suffocating.
Nanamin, that's the worst way you could've put it!
No, I mean...
The stars...
I'm sure the stars look really pretty.
Why does she keep doing this?
Sorata
Maybe she's looking out for you in her own special way.
Chihiro-sensei...
I know how you feel, though.
It's only natural to get upset when you're trying to get something done, and you see other people slacking off.
You're a teacher, aren't you? Could you show some tact and not bring up things I don't want to hear?
You don't want to hear it because you know better.
Mashiro hasn't been slacking off.
She's just having trouble adjusting to feelings she's never experienced before.
Mashiro doesn't know how to make up with people.
How the hell are you supposed to bury the hatchet if you keep half-assing your part of the problem?
Are you telling me to apologize to her?
What an idiot. You really are a kid.
How am I a kid?
You see the world in black and white.
But the world isn't that simple.
Everything around you is somewhere in the middle.
They're not black or white. They're gray.
Understand?
Then what should I do?
Hell if I know.
But if you only accept things that meet your ideals precisely,
you'll make yourself and everyone around you unhappy.
But what should I—
Just do something about Mashiro.
That's all.
Because I'm on Mashiro Duty?
Because you're a man.
Oh, right!
Sakurasou's gonna be closed over New Year's.
What?
I'm taking a vacation to Australia.
So pack your bags and go back home.
What? You could've told us ahead of time.
And so, the day came.
Sorata
With feelings that I didn't know what to do with...
...and feelings that I didn't know if I should express...
...and these feelings that I'm sure can't reach him...
...crossing, colliding, compounding...
...and slipping right past each other.
Fresh Baked Cakes
Tirol
So could you pick up the cake?
They said it would be ready at 5:00 pm.
Sure.
Please don't forget.
A sight for sore eyes!
What do you think, Kouhai-kun?
She's so cute that you don't know what to say?
I see, I see!
You look like you're used to wearing them.
I wore dresses to awards ceremonies.
Mashiron, here's your coat.
Okay, Jin-san, make sure you get the cake.
You don't need to run.
Misaki.
What?
Are you coming to the the party too?
Of course I am!
We're exchanging presents too, so make sure you bring something.
This isn't good for me.
Mashiro doesn't know how to make up with people.
How the hell are you supposed to bury the hatchet if you keep half-assing your part of the problem?
Ma—
Sorata.
That envelope...
Results from another competition I entered.
You're not going to read them?
I'll take a look at them later.
Thank you so much, Kanda-kun!
Don't mention it.
I'll be borrowing the princess tonight.
I'll be back by 9:30.
Okay.
Let me take your coat.
Sorata.
What is it?
Say something.
Don't... be mad...
Is something wrong?
N-No, nothing's wrong.
Please keep a close eye on her tonight.
Shiina, remember to mind your manners.
Don't... be mad...
Hey...
What was that for,
Aoyama?!
You don't need to act that surprised!
Sorry, I just wasn't expecting you to look so...
I look weird, don't I?
No, you don't!
You just look really different.
Different how?
How can I put this...
You look pretty nice dressed like that.
Really?
Yeah. I was just shocked, is all.
All right! It worked!
It's snowing!
I give up!
Stupid couples should all just explode!
Don't hang up on me!
Let me talk to Ryuunosuke!
Absolutely not.
Suddenly sending him something like this is beyond common sense!
I don't care! Put him on!
No means no.
Snow?
Wow, it's really starting to come down.
Think it'll stick?
I wonder if my hood is good enough for this much.
Here.
What?
I'll share my umbrella with you, so the least you could do is hold it.
Okay, okay.
What did you think of the play?
The play itself was great,
but I felt really excited and frustrated at the same time.
The acting was incredible.
I know what you mean. I feel the same way when I play a good game.
The way pros enunciate and move is on a whole other level.
Better work hard.
Though, I guess you already are.
You think I'm working hard enough?
Trust me, you are.
Feeling a little insecure?
Is that what it looks like?
Kind of.
I have an audition in February that'll decide whether I get into an agency or not.
I see.
My parents told me to go back home to Osaka if I don't make it.
Huh?
Wait, what do you mean?
Exactly what I said.
If I don't pass the audition, I'm transferring back to Osaka.
If I pass, I'll keep attending Sui High while working with an agency.
Wait, but—
Kanda-kun.
Would you feel sad if I weren't around?
Don't ask questions like that.
You'll make it.
I know you will.
Hey... Could I ask you a favor?
If I pass the audition...
If I pass...
Could you hear me out on something?
What is it?
Only if I pass!
This ain't the time for it!
Ain't no point in the favor if I tell you now!
Really?
Yeah.
Okay, I'll hear you out.
I promise.
And...
If...
And if...
If that time comes, and I have trouble saying it, I want you to tell me,
"Jump into outer space!"
What's that supposed to mean?
That don't matter! Just say it!
I don't really get it, but okay.
Hello?
Kanda-kun?
It's Ayano.
Is Shiina-san with you?
Shiina?
Sorry to bother you, but Shiina-san disappeared from the party.
According to the hotel staff, she went outside.
Do you know where she'd go?
Did something happen?
Aoyama, hold this.
Kanda-kun!
M-Misaki?
Give me an answer. Please.
I love you.
Really?
Yeah.
I've always loved you with all my heart.
The snow... stopped.
Shiina!
You...
Sorata...
What are you doing, you idiot?
Where are your shoes?
They went somewhere while I was walking.
"Went somewhere"?!
This is for you.
It's good.
I wanted you to eat it.
That's why you came out here?
Yeah.
What were you thinking?!
Because...
you've been really mad lately.
I wanted to talk to you so much.
But you looked so mad.
I didn't want that, so I thought about what to do.
About what would make you happy...
About how you could have fun...
But I didn't know.
I...
This is all I could do.
Is it good?
It's hard.
Are you mad?
Yeah. You bet I'm mad.
Sorata?
I was worried sick because you just disappeared without a word.
You just vanished...
They couldn't find you...
I nearly had a heart attack when I thought you might've gotten into an accident!
Sorata?
Don't you get it?
Don't walk around barefoot outside.
Don't hurt your hands.
You're a professional manga artist.
I thought about you, Sorata.
And then I wanted to do it.
To cook for you...
I never thought about it before.
I just don't know.
I've never felt like this before.
I got goosebumps when I saw you drawing your manga.
It was the biggest shock of my life.
You didn't care for compromise or consequences. You just drew and drew.
You dedicated your life to it, like it was only natural.
I haven't been able to take my eyes off you ever since.
And I've loved that side of you ever since.
So don't disappoint me.
I'm watching you.
I'm always watching you.
Sorata...
Are you two just going to stand there all night?
"All night?" Wait, when did you get here?
You'll wish you were dead if I told you.
Then please don't tell me.
Here.
It's important, right?
You dropped it.
Aoyama...
What is it?
Mind helping me practice for another presentation?
Of course not!
Me too!
I want to help too!
All these emotions building up inside me
arifureta kanjou kara
I couldn't get over any of them
sotsugyou mo dekitenakute
So I can't sleep
nemurenai
That pain I felt when it suddenly
totsuzen no ame no karunda
Started to rain disappeared for a moment
ano kutsuu wa mabataki suru
I'm trying to understand a little of your world
kimi no sekai wo chitto uketometeiru
Your reality and what I can see
kimi no riaru boku no shisen
Even if they're a little different
doko ka chigau to shite mo
I won't let it end up like that old, beat-up T-shirt, so
ano kutabireta ti-shatsu mitai ni sasenai kara
Fly into the world of prime numbers
puraimu nanba-sekai ni tobe
You won't get any duplicates when you multiply one
hitotsu to shite onaji mono ga nai
You don't need to fill the holes in your heart
kokoro no kuuhaku wo muri ni
If you don't really want to
umenakutemo ii ne
More than leaving my memory behind
takusan no dareka no kioku ni
In everyone in the world's hearts,
nokosareteiru yori mo
I want to be the sky you see from on top of the roof
yane no ue kimi dake no sora ni naritai
So heavy.
That's mean.
What should we do? All the lights are off.
They might be getting busy as we speak.
Don't say it so plainly!
Either way, I'm going in.
What?!
I'm about to collapse.
Huh?
The door's unl—
Misaki-senpai?
I tried.
I told him I wanted to be boyfriend and girlfriend.
But...
With the way I am now, I can't care for you as well as I should.
That's okay.
No, it isn't.
Then what should I do?
You don't need to do anything.
Just stay the way you are.
I don't get it...
I don't get what you're trying to say.
Just stay the way you are.
Stay the Misaki that I love.
It doesn't make sense.
Jin was so gentle...
But I didn't want that...
I wanted...
I wanted Jin to hurt me!
My son, coming home with three young girls?
Where's Your Usual Self?
A son grows up so fast with only the slightest stimulation.
Honestly.