Wait...
I said that Sakurasou will be demolished at the end of this school year.
You'll be moving to the regular dorms in April, so start packing.
Wh-Why—
Isn't it great, Kouhai-kun?!
Weren't you listening?!
They're gonna rebuild Sakurasou! Aren't you happy?
I'm so excited I could burst!
I won't be able to sleep tonight! I'd better sleep now!
Rebuild?
Is the end result really something positive like that?
No.
It's just getting demolished; nothing more.
No remodeling, no rebuilding. Just poof.
Chihiro-chan!
I never heard anything about this, and I never voted for it!
Who decided on this?
A construction company came through to inspect the building over winter vacation.
Over winter vacation?
Oh, right!
Sakurasou's gonna be closed over New Year's.
What?
I'm taking a vacation to Australia.
So pack your bags and go back home.
You lied to us?!
Calm down, Sorata.
Something about this doesn't feel right.
Sakurasou is a bit worn down,
but it's not so bad that we need to pack up and leave right away.
They could at least wait for the
second-years to graduate, right?
I mean, even Chihiro-chan knows that we'd fight back if they suddenly announced the demolition.
The board decided on it.
They even gave permission to keep those cats in the regular dorms for a while.
That's all. Dismissed.
Sensei!
Sakurasou is still livable.
I'll go convince the principal otherwise!
Don't.
The principal'll be down for
the count if you did that.
We don't want to bring Sakurasou's reputation down any further.
But they can't just do that!
They didn't even ask our opinion!
Yeah!
And they practically tricked us—
Sure you don't want out?
Misaki and I may be graduating,
but you won't get another chance to go back to the regular dorms.
But...
The regular dorms are built properly.
You won't feel drafts there.
The cafeteria ladies also provide the meals.
So you'll be living a chore-free
life there, unlike here.
That's not—
For you, it'll mean having more time to prepare for the final round.
Akasaka, are you okay with this?
They're tearing down Sakurasou just like that!
I'm being logical and breaking down the pros and the cons.
Look—
At any rate,
it'd be best to think things through before doing anything rash.
harewataru sora wa aoku
p
The clear sky shines so blue
chikadzuitekuru ashioto
v
I can hear your footsteps coming closer
hikaridashita kaze ni osareru you ni
n
Almost like the shining wind pushed me there
hora deatteshimatta
That's when I met you
sorezore no yume
a
Each of our dreams
sorezore no mirai
Each of our futures
matenai you ni hashiri
p
We ran because we couldn't wait
kidzuitara zutto issho ni itan da
Before I knew it you were always there with me
dare yori mo
More than anyone
nayande ochikonde naite waratte
Worrying, falling, crying, laughing
kasokushiteku
And running faster
kimi ni todoke
a
I want to reach you
sora wo kakete
Fly through the sky
massugu na omoi gyutto dakishime
a
Holding tight to my honest feelings
kitto umaretate no tsuyosa wa mune ni
y
I know this newborn strength will be part of my soul
kono kimochi ga tsubasa ni nari
These feelings will become my wings
watashi wa watashi wo tameteyuku
I'll grow to be more like myself
I finally come home,
and it's getting demolished.
Jin, are you really okay with this?
Sakurasou's gonna be gone forever!
Of course not.
They've done a lot for us.
We need to do what we can to return the favor.
Yeah.
I can't convince the principal, so what should we do?
I still don't understand why they suddenly want to demolish it.
If the reason were something acceptable,
then they would've told us.
What do we do?
First off...
Yeah, don't worry.
I'll take care of you guys no matter what happens.
You understand what's going on, right?
Sakurasou's going to go away.
Yeah.
And you understand what that means?
I'll live with everyone in the
regular dorms starting April.
Huh? You really do understand?
You'll take care of me no matter what happens.
Nope, never mind.
I can't do that in the regular dorms.
Why not?
The boys' and girls' dorms are separate buildings.
And boys aren't allowed in the girls' dorm.
I can't wake you up and cook your breakfast every morning.
That's a problem.
I...
like Sakurasou.
Me too.
I had planned on leaving when
I found her an owner, but...
Oh, that's the picture we took when I first came here.
Everyone's in it.
I still remember when the
principal told me to move here.
Principal
Kanda Sorata-kun.
You know why I've called you here, don't you?
Principal
Yes.
It's about the cat.
Principal
I've let it slide for a month,
but keeping pets is against dorm policy.
You can either get rid of that cat,
or move to Sakurasou.
The choice is yours.
I'll move to Sakurasou.
Kanda-kun?!
Are you sure about that?
Of course!
You really went with it?
Yeah.
I'm at that age where I have to rebel against the authorities.
You're just stupid.
What else can I do?!
I can't keep her in the regular dorms!
Are you really moving to Sakurasou?
Once you're cast away to Sakurasou,
you'll never live a normal life again!
Stay away from Sakurasou!
Don't you listen to what everyone says?!
Don't worry!
I'll find an owner for Hikari,
and I'll be back in the regular
dorms by the second term.
It's at least three times more
worn down than I imagined.
Don't worry.
It's not like aliens and ghosts live here.
Nothing to be scared of.
Excuse me!
Kind of lax...
Pardon me...
My room is...
Kanda Sorata
Room 101?
It's pretty big!
They've kept it clean too.
Looks great.
The closet's big too.
I must be tired.
Thief!
What now, thief?!
No, I'm a first—
Huh?
Are you Kamiigusa-senpai in second year?
How do you know my name, thief?!
B-Because you're famous!
You're a second-year on full scholarship who
made a huge hit with her self-produced anime...
Judgment!
N-No! I'm living here starting today!
I-I'm Kanda Sorata, a first-year!
That's what all thieves say!
No, they don't!
This is Hikari.
They kicked me out of the regular dorms for keeping a cat.
Oh, okay.
Soratan and Hikarin, huh?
Soratan, you like dogs more?
Cats more? Cats more, right?
Huh?
Yeah...
I like bears more!
That wasn't one of the options.
So, Soratan...
Soratan!
Hold on, could you not call me that? Do you think I'm some cutesy little girl or something?!
So, Sorapyon...
I'm a goofy mascot now?!
So, Solanine...
An organic compound?
What's wrong with it, Soranyan?
Nicknames are the first thing you decide as friends!
I think I'm getting a headache.
So, Tantan...
It's lost all semblance to my name.
The president of a certain company would go jogging through the park as part of his morning routine.
Okay...
That park had tons of empty cans littered about.
The president decided that he would pick up each can he saw on his morning jog.
But there were more cans than the president could pick up.
And the number of cans just grew each day.
But the president kept picking up cans.
And soon, he noticed that the number of cans littered through the park was decreasing!
And that was because the other joggers in the park saw the president picking up cans
and started picking up cans on their jogs themselves!
The End
Th-That's a great story...
You bet it is!
It's about how people are inherently good!
Though some people might litter!
So why'd you suddenly break into story?
No reason!
There's an alien here!
Where?!
Right there!
You're so weird, Sorachin!
A weirdo just called me weird...
Could you keep it down?
What's with all the racket?
Sensei, help me!
Who're you?
I'm moving in here today—
Huh?
Oh, right. I vaguely remember the principal spewing
some stupid crap about a loser moving to Sakurasou.
Hold on, spewing stupid crap?
And why are you dressed like that, Sensei?
I'm going speed dating tonight.
I don't have time for students.
What'd you say?!
Why does summer have to be so damn hot?
Freaking summer.
My heart's breaking...
What's going on out here?
Jin, it's Solon!
He's moving into room 101 today!
I'm guessing his last name's Athinaios.
It's not!
I'm Kanda Sorata, a first-year!
And this is Hikarin!
Oh, so you're the guy keeping
a cat in the regular dorms?
I'm Mitaka Jin.
I'm in room 103.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too, Mitaka-senpai.
Drop the respect. Just call me Jin.
Okay, Jin-san.
Would you mind helping me out here?
Don't go too hard tonight, Misaki.
That's it?!
I'm sorry, Jin, but I'm afraid
I can't do that for you!
I wanna get to know him even better!
Huh? You're on a first-name basis?
Misaki and I are childhood friends.
We're not in a dirty relationship, though.
My girlfriend's a married woman.
We're going on a date tonight.
See you.
What? What?
Jin, what'd you tell him?
Come on, snap out of it, Soranyan!
You're scaring me!
Victory!
That's 98 straight victories!
Two more until 100!
I kind of want to unpack...
You can do that anytime!
You're here forever, Sora-chan!
As soon as I find an owner
for Hikari, I'm out of here!
You can say that after you've beaten me!
99 straight victories!
I played this game a lot too...
I believe that wrestling is the greatest martial art!
Wrestlers are the strongest!
You're too strong!
Could I at least take a bath?
Are you a little girl who doesn't want the guy she likes to smell her sweat?
Why're you way over there?
N-No reason.
Just stay away.
What the heck? Fine!
He's gonna get the wrong idea.
You know I'm a guy, right?
I'm gonna take a bath now, 'kay?
What about 100 straight victories?
Maybe a glass of water will calm my nerves.
Who's up at this hour?
Sensei?
Or Jin-san?
Are you back?
A gh-gh-gh-gh—
The room next to mine?
It's a living human, right?
What's the fuss?
A crazy old lady?!
You got a death wish, kid?
Oh, it's you, Sensei?
You're back from speed dating?
Been back for a while.
Freaking dicks.
Ugly shits got no right to tell me I've got attitude or drink too much!
Fuckin' retards!
More importantly, just now we had a... hag a—
Who're you calling a hag? I'm still in my twenties!
I didn't call you one!
A ghost passed through the hall!
It had hair down to its hips!
And it went into the room next to mine!
Oh, yeah, he comes out sometimes.
He comes out?! So it really is a ghost?!
He's Akasaka Ryuunosuke, from room 102.
Huh?
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
I completely forgot he lived here.
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
I've only seen him three times before.
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Wait, Sensei, aren't you the supervisor?!
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Akasaka's a total shut-in.
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
He's a first-year like you, but he hasn't come to school since it started.
Aren't you lucky, though.
Getting to see Akasaka as soon
as you came to Sakurasou.
Please don't treat a shut-in
like a luck-bearing fairy!
I'm impressed.
I'm more impressed by your reaction!
And shouldn't you get him to go to school?
You'll start hating life if you do what you hate.
So you had your own ideas about it?
I'm sorry.
That's why I don't do any work around Sakurasou.
I hate doing it.
You were talking about yourself?!
Here.
If you need anything from Akasaka, drop him an e-mail.
That's his e-mail address.
I have to send e-mails next door?
Well...
Guess I'll drop him a "Nice to meet you."
My name is Kanda Sorata. I moved into room 101. Nice to meet you.
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Sending
That was fast!
What the heck?
Ryuunosuke-sama is currently developing a motion engine...
"Daa"?
No Subject
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Ryuunosuke-sama is currently developing
a motion engine. Daa.
So he cannot answer your email
at the moment, Sorata-kun. Daa.
So he cannot answer your email at the moment, Sorata-kun. Daa.
Ryuunosuke-sama is currently developing
a motion engine. Daa.
So he cannot answer your email
at the moment, Sorata-kun. Daa.
Ryuunosuke-sama is currently developing
a motion engine. Daa.
So he cannot answer your email
at the moment, Sorata-kun. Daa.
Sincerely, Maid-chan, who was
recently born.
Ryuunosuke-sama is currently developing
a motion engine. Daa.
So he cannot answer your email
at the moment, Sorata-kun. Daa.
Sincerely, Maid-chan, who was
recently born.
Ryuunosuke-sama is currently developing
a motion engine. Daa.
So he cannot answer your email
at the moment, Sorata-kun. Daa.
Sincerely, Maid-chan, who was
recently born.
So he cannot answer your email
at the moment, Sorata-kun. Daa.
Sincerely, Maid-chan, who was
recently born.
So he cannot answer your email
at the moment, Sorata-kun. Daa.
Sincerely, Maid-chan, who was
recently born.
Sincerely, Maid-chan, who was recently born.
Uh...
How am I supposed to respond to that?
You're a pretty funny guy, Akasaka.
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
What's so funny?
Maid-chan is doing her job as best she can. Daa.
Sincerely, Maid-chan
Sincerely, Maid-chan.
Fine, whatever. Can we just
have a normal conversation?
I'm talking normally.
Daa.
Are you hard of thinking,
Sorata-kun? Daa.
Sincerely, Maid-chan
Look, Akasaka-kun,
could you stop with
the "daa"?
It's getting on my nerves.
What is with this conversation?!
I'm not Ryuunosuke-sama.
Daa.
Sincerely, Maid-chan
Like I'll believe that!
Quit screwing around,
damn it!
Quit screwing around, damn it!
Maid-chan is an automated AI e-mail
responding program that I developed myself.
She can write an appropriate response to any e-mail in less than a second.
Don't tell me you didn't realize that.
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
What's so funny?
Don't make me laugh.
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
What's so funny?
Don't make me laugh.
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
What's so funny?
Don't make me laugh.
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
What's so funny?
Don't make me laugh.
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
What's so funny?
Don't make me laugh.
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
What's so funny?
Don't make me laugh.
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
What's so funny?
Don't make me laugh.
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
What's so funny?
Don't make me laugh.
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
What's so funny?
Don't make me laugh.
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
What's so funny?
Don't make me laugh.
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
What's so funny?
Don't make me laugh.
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
What's so funny?
Don't make me laugh.
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
What's so funny?
Don't make me laugh.
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
What's so funny?
Don't make me laugh.
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
What's so funny?
Don't make me laugh.
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
What's so funny?
Don't make me laugh.
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
What's so funny?
Don't make me laugh.
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
What's so funny?
Don't make me laugh.
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
What's so funny?
Don't make me laugh.
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
What's so funny?
Don't make me laugh.
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
What's so funny?
Don't make me laugh.
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
What's so funny?
Don't make me laugh.
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
What's so funny?
Don't make me laugh.
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
What's so funny?
Don't make me laugh.
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
What's so funny?
Don't make me laugh.
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
What's so funny?
Don't make me laugh.
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
What's so funny?
Don't make me laugh.
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
No sane person would think there's some
automated e-mail responding program behind a personal e-mail address!
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
I see
I never thought that
there were people who
wouldn't realize it
in this world.
I apologize.
That's all.
I never thought that
there were people who
wouldn't realize it
in this world.
I apologize.
That's all.
I never thought that there were people who wouldn't realize it in this world.
I apologize.
That's all.
That wasn't an apology, damn it!
Thanks for waiting!
I wasn't waiting for you!
Sorachin, let's play Metal Cross next!
Wait, isn't that a single-player game?
We'll play one at a time, higher score wins!
It takes about three hours to complete. Watch!
That'll take all night!
And what do you think you're wearing, Senpai?!
Don't sweat the little things!
Come on. Sit here, Sorapun!
Fine, then.
If you won't get out, I will!
I can't stay here any longer!
Come on, Sorapin!
What do I do now?
No, I can't!
I can't do it!
There's no way they'll let me keep another!
I'm back...
Just keep quiet.
What're you doing?
Jin-san?!
Did you just get home?
Meiko-san wouldn't let me sleep.
Sounds pretty adulterous.
Is Meiko-san the married woman?
Yeah. I've got three more girlfriends too.
Four girlfriends?!
So, who's the cutie you got there?
Well...
I picked her up in the park...
Oh? What's her name?
I think I'll call her Nozomi.
So the next one you pick up's Kodama, huh?
I'm not picking up a third.
I don't even know if they'll let me keep a second—
Welcome to Sakurasou!
What the hell is this?!
Duh! It's a welcome party for our newest resident!
It's six in the morning!
Misaki insisted on having one.
That's why I came home early too.
Thanks for leaving, Sorakyun!
It's a surprise party now!
You did this by yourself?
Misaki was really excited to have a new resident.
She cleaned this room herself
so that anyone could move in anytime.
So that's why it was so clean?
But why a hot pot?
It's a Sakurasou tradition to have a hot pot for welcome parties.
But in the middle of summer—
Don't sweat it, just sit down!
Huh?
Who's that?
Another new resident?
I picked her up in the park.
Think it'll be okay for me to keep another?
We'll need to hold a Sakurasou meeting to find out!
Sakurasou meeting?
Whenever we need to decide on something,
we hold a meeting with all of the residents.
Oh, and her name's Nozomi.
All in favor of keeping Nozomin, raise you hand!
Ryuunosuke doesn't have any objections either.
Isn't that great?
Can we really just decide like that?
What about Sensei's permission?
Don't need it.
That's the kind of place this is.
All right, let's keep the party rolling!
Nozomin, Hikarin, Kouhai-kun!
Eat up!
Oh, let's go with that one.
My nickname.
Let's go with "Kouhai-kun," Kamiigusa-senpai.
You can call me by my first name too!
We're friends, after all, Kouhai-kun!
Okay.
How about "Misaki-senpai"?
Could you move in a bit closer?
What about Akasaka?
Don't worry! I'll shop him in later!
Shop him?
I get the feeling we'll be together for a long time.
That wasn't funny.
I'm going to find owners for the cats
and leave this place before the second term starts!
It's shooting, Kouhai-kun!
On your mark, get boom, pose!
I'm definitely getting out of here!
At first, it was just Hikari.
Komachi made these scratches.
I've fallen down these stairs a few times.
And I've had to fix the entrance a bunch of times.
Sure, Sakurasou's old and worn down.
The winters are cold, and the summers are hot.
The floorboards sometimes break when you step on them.
The lock on my door is broken,
so I've got no privacy or anything like that.
We've got leaks on the second floor too.
But...
Yeah.
Before you know it, all the things you hated become memories too.
Like when the bath broke, and we all went to a public one.
Or when we got rid of the wasp nest.
Yeah.
My diary's filled up so fast since I moved here.
If Sakurasou gets torn down,
it'll be like losing all those precious memories.
I don't want that.
Well said, Kouhai-kun! That's it!
Like when we had a hot pot party on the roof!
Or when we turned Sakurasou
into a haunted house
and invited all the kids
around here that summer!
Or when I played dead every
time you came home!
They're all awesome memories!
All your awesome memories involved people getting mad at you.
It's got its share of problems,
but I think that this is where we belong.
What do you think, Akasaka?
Setting aside the pros and cons for now,
Inbox
From:
Mitaka Jin
Real Reason Behind the Demolition
Details
Mind checking their servers to find out?
I don't like how they aren't giving us a reason.
I like Sakurasou.
Me too! So...
Let's stop the demolition!
Thought so.
Yeah!
All right!
Time for a Sakurasou meeting!
It's the first meeting of the
Sakurasou Defense Brigade!
Home Is Where Sakurasou Is
Are you ready, men?!
Yeah!
All these emotions building up inside me
arifureta kanjou kara
I couldn't get over any of them
sotsugyou mo dekitenakute
So I can't sleep
nemurenai
That pain I felt when it suddenly
totsuzen no ame no karunda
Started to rain disappeared for a moment
ano kutsuu wa mabataki suru
I'm trying to understand a little of your world
kimi no sekai wo chitto uketometeiru
Your reality and what I can see
kimi no riaru boku no shisen
Even if they're a little different
doko ka chigau to shite mo
I won't let it end up like that old, beat-up T-shirt, so
ano kutabireta ti-shatsu mitai ni sasenai kara
Fly into the world of prime numbers
puraimu nanba-sekai ni tobe
You won't get any duplicates when you multiply one
hitotsu to shite onaji mono ga nai
You don't need to fill the holes in your heart
kokoro no kuuhaku wo muri ni
If you don't really want to
umenakutemo ii ne
More than leaving my memory behind
takusan no dareka no kioku ni
In everyone in the world's hearts,
nokosareteiru yori mo
I want to be the sky you see from on top of the roof
yane no ue kimi dake no sora ni naritai
Yeah, we can't get discouraged!
Life is full of highs and lows!
So We Can Keep Calling It Home
I ain't never feelin' down ever again!
Great things're gonna happen next week!
Stop right there, Ponytail.
You'll turn next episode into a downer.
Wha—?