Login successful. Permission granted.
I'll go take a look!
We're against Sakurasou's demolition!
Please sign our petition!
According to school regulations,
the administration must respond if we can collect signatures from two thirds of the student body!
Please...
...sign our petition!
It's a lot harder than I thought.
Well, it doesn't really affect anyone but us.
Yo, I hear you're in a bit of a bind.
Miyahara-kun...
I'll sign it.
Keep at it.
Um, Miyahara-kun...
Hm?
Well...
Thank you very much.
I'll ask my friends if they'll sign it too.
Oh, would you?
See ya.
Thanks a bunch, Miyahara!
We're against Sakurasou's demolition!
Please sign our petition!
harewataru sora wa aoku
p
The clear sky shines so blue
chikadzuitekuru ashioto
v
I can hear your footsteps coming closer
hikaridashita kaze ni osareru you ni
n
Almost like the shining wind pushed me there
hora deatteshimatta
That's when I met you
sorezore no yume
a
Each of our dreams
sorezore no mirai
Each of our futures
matenai you ni hashiri
p
We ran because we couldn't wait
kidzuitara zutto issho ni itan da
Before I knew it you were always there with me
dare yori mo
More than anyone
nayande ochikonde naite waratte
Worrying, falling, crying, laughing
kasokushiteku
And running faster
kimi ni todoke
a
I want to reach you
sora wo kakete
Fly through the sky
massugu na omoi gyutto dakishime
a
Holding tight to my honest feelings
kitto umaretate no tsuyosa wa mune ni
y
I know this newborn strength will be part of my soul
kono kimochi ga tsubasa ni nari
These feelings will become my wings
watashi wa watashi wo tameteyuku
I'll grow to be more like myself
We spent all morning in front of the gate and only got three signatures...
So We Can Keep Calling It Home
Mitaka-senpai and Kamiigusa-senpai are checking the third-year classrooms, but...
Kanda.
Akasaka?
Where were you this morning?
We decided that we'd all help collect signatures, didn't we?
What's this?
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School - Board Meeting Proceedings (2012)
As you can see, it's the proceedings of the school board meetings.
Mitaka-senpai wanted me to get these.
Now we know why they're tearing Sakurasou down.
Wait, you hacked them?!
Are you sure it's okay to do that?!
Do I look like the type to leave a trail behind?
Well, that's not the—
Read the first page.
It's a report from the construction company that inspected Sakurasou.
From a safety perspective, we highly recommend moving its residents and having the building demolished in five years.
From a safety perspective,
we highly recommend moving its residents and having the building demolished in five years.
From a safety perspective, we highly recommend moving its residents and having the building demolished in five years.
Five years? That's still a long ways off.
In other words, there's no
reason to demolish it this year.
Keep reading.
Vice Principal
Agreed. Shiina Mashiro should be moved to the regular dorms as soon as possible.
She should focus on her paintings.
Vice Principal
Agreed. Shiina Mashiro should be moved to the regular dorms as soon as possible.
She should focus on her paintings.
Vice Principal
Agreed. Shiina Mashiro should be moved to the regular dorms as soon as possible.
She should focus on her paintings.
Vice Principal
Agreed. Shiina Mashiro should be moved to the regular dorms as soon as possible.
She should focus on her paintings.
Vice Principal
Agreed. Shiina Mashiro should be moved to the regular dorms as soon as possible.
She should focus on her paintings.
Vice Principal
Agreed. Shiina Mashiro should be moved to the regular dorms as soon as possible.
She should focus on her paintings.
Vice Principal
Agreed. Shiina Mashiro should be moved to the regular dorms as soon as possible.
She should focus on her paintings.
Shiina?
Vice Principal
Agreed. Shiina Mashiro should be moved to the regular dorms as soon as possible.
She should focus on her paintings.
Vice Principal
Agreed. Shiina Mashiro should be moved to the regular dorms as soon as possible.
She should focus on her paintings.
Vice Principal
Agreed. Shiina Mashiro should be moved to the regular dorms as soon as possible.
She should focus on her paintings.
Vice Principal
Agreed. Shiina Mashiro should be moved to the regular dorms as soon as possible.
She should focus on her paintings.
Vice Principal
Agreed. Shiina Mashiro should be moved to the regular dorms as soon as possible.
She should focus on her paintings.
Vice Principal
Agreed. Shiina Mashiro should be moved to the regular dorms as soon as possible.
She should focus on her paintings.
Vice Principal
Agreed. Shiina Mashiro should be moved to the regular dorms as soon as possible.
She should focus on her paintings.
Vice Principal
Agreed. Shiina Mashiro should be moved to the regular dorms as soon as possible.
She should focus on her paintings.
Vice Principal
Agreed. Shiina Mashiro should be moved to the regular dorms as soon as possible.
She should focus on her paintings.
and Shiina Mashiro grows famous as a manga artist, we, as her alma mater, will
However, if her serialization continues
Vice Principal
Agreed. Shiina Mashiro should be moved to the regular dorms as soon as possible.
She should focus on her paintings.
Vice Principal
Sengoku-sensei is Shiina Mashiro's cousin.
That is why we have thus far maintained Sengoku-sensei's opinion
and allowed things to unfold as they would.
and Shiina Mashiro grows famous as a manga artist, we, as her alma mater, will
However, if her serialization continues
Vice Principal
Agreed. Shiina Mashiro should be moved to the regular dorms as soon as possible.
She should focus on her paintings.
Vice Principal
Sengoku-sensei is Shiina Mashiro's cousin.
That is why we have thus far maintained Sengoku-sensei's opinion
and allowed things to unfold as they would.
and Shiina Mashiro grows famous as a manga artist, we, as her alma mater, will
However, if her serialization continues
Vice Principal
Agreed. Shiina Mashiro should be moved to the regular dorms as soon as possible.
She should focus on her paintings.
Vice Principal
Sengoku-sensei is Shiina Mashiro's cousin.
That is why we have thus far maintained Sengoku-sensei's opinion
and allowed things to unfold as they would.
and Shiina Mashiro grows famous as a manga artist, we, as her alma mater, will
However, if her serialization continues
Vice Principal
Agreed. Shiina Mashiro should be moved to the regular dorms as soon as possible.
She should focus on her paintings.
Vice Principal
Sengoku-sensei is Shiina Mashiro's cousin.
That is why we have thus far maintained Sengoku-sensei's opinion
and allowed things to unfold as they would.
and Shiina Mashiro grows famous as a manga artist, we, as her alma mater, will
However, if her serialization continues
Vice Principal
Agreed. Shiina Mashiro should be moved to the regular dorms as soon as possible.
She should focus on her paintings.
Vice Principal
Sengoku-sensei is Shiina Mashiro's cousin.
That is why we have thus far maintained Sengoku-sensei's opinion
and allowed things to unfold as they would.
and Shiina Mashiro grows famous as a manga artist, we, as her alma mater, will
However, if her serialization continues
Vice Principal
Agreed. Shiina Mashiro should be moved to the regular dorms as soon as possible.
She should focus on her paintings.
Vice Principal
Sengoku-sensei is Shiina Mashiro's cousin.
That is why we have thus far maintained Sengoku-sensei's opinion
and allowed things to unfold as they would.
and Shiina Mashiro grows famous as a manga artist, we, as her alma mater, will
However, if her serialization continues
Vice Principal
Sengoku-sensei is Shiina Mashiro's cousin.
That is why we have thus far maintained Sengoku-sensei's opinion
and allowed things to unfold as they would.
and Shiina Mashiro grows famous as a manga artist, we, as her alma mater, will
Sengoku-sensei is Shiina Mashiro's cousin.
Vice Principal
That is why we have thus far maintained Sengoku-sensei's opinion
and allowed things to unfold as they would.
and Shiina Mashiro grows famous as a manga artist, we, as her alma mater, will
However, if her serialization continues
and allowed things to unfold as they would.
and Shiina Mashiro grows famous as a manga artist, we, as her alma mater, will
However, if her serialization continues
That is why we have thus far maintained Sengoku-sensei's opinion
and allowed things to unfold as they would.
and Shiina Mashiro grows famous as a manga artist, we, as her alma mater, will
However, if her serialization continues
That is why we have thus far maintained Sengoku-sensei's opinion
and allowed things to unfold as they would.
and Shiina Mashiro grows famous as a manga artist, we, as her alma mater, will
However, if her serialization continues
That is why we have thus far maintained Sengoku-sensei's opinion
and allowed things to unfold as they would.
Shiina...
and Shiina Mashiro grows famous as a manga artist, we, as her alma mater, will
However, if her serialization continues
That is why we have thus far maintained Sengoku-sensei's opinion
and allowed things to unfold as they would.
and Shiina Mashiro grows famous as a manga artist, we, as her alma mater, will
However, if her serialization continues
That is why we have thus far maintained Sengoku-sensei's opinion
and allowed things to unfold as they would.
and Shiina Mashiro grows famous as a manga artist, we, as her alma mater, will
However, if her serialization continues
I'm seeing Shiina's name a lot here...
They're going about it in a roundabout way,
but basically, they're saying that having Shiina live at Sakurasou is bad for them.
They feel threatened because Shiina's artistic talent is being used to create manga.
They need to do something before people start saying the school is what destroyed her talent.
So they decided to demolish Sakurasou,
which they assume influenced her to draw manga.
Wait, hang on.
She wanted to draw manga before she even came to Sakurasou!
That's not what the board thinks.
I'm gonna give the principal an earful.
Wait, Kanda-kun!
If I were the principal, I'd ask you,
"Where did you find the proceedings of the board meeting?"
I hope you don't plan on saying,
"We hacked the school's servers."
That'd put us in an even worse position...
Besides, Sengoku-sensei already explained that Sakurasou had no bearing on her decision to draw manga.
Sengoku
As I have said twice before, Sakurasou is not the reason why Shiina Mashiro started drawing manga.
She had started before she came to Japan.
Principal
However, her manga was only good enough to be put in a magazine after she moved into Sakurasou.
I also hear that there is an apartment similar to Sakurasou in her manga.
We cannot say that Sakurasou had no influence on her drawing manga.
Vice Principal
Sengoku-sensei is Shiina Mashiro's cousin.
That is why we have thus far maintained Sengoku-sensei's opinion
and allowed things to unfold as they would.
However, if her serialization continues
and Shiina Mashiro grows famous as a manga artist, we, as her alma mater, will
He's right.
She did everything she could to stave off demolishing Sakurasou.
What should we do, then?!
We can't just sit around and let this happen!
What should we do?
I think the answer is obvious.
Sakurasou is being demolished
because Shiina is staying there.
The solution to this problem is as bright as day.
Am I wrong?
Shut up.
Kanda.
Your time is more valuable
than anyone else's right now.
Are you ready for the final round of the competition?
It'd be wise for you to solve this as quickly
as possible, so you can focus on your competition.
I told you to shut up!
Mashiro?
Did you hear all that?
No, never mind.
Did you need something?
I asked Shiho to sign it.
Oh, wow.
So there are people in your class who'd help us?
How many more do I need to get?
A ton more.
Enough to fill this notebook.
I'll go ask more.
Most of the third-years aren't coming to school right now.
This means we would need to collect signatures from the entire first- and second-year classes to meet the quota.
I know that.
And, even if we do manage collect them all,
there's no guarantee that we can change the board's decision so long as Shiina stays at Sakurasou.
I'm having difficulty understanding you.
The quickest solution is
right under your nose.
Why don't you take it?
Do you think it's a good thing
if Shiina leaves Sakurasou?
It isn't a matter of good or bad.
It's a matter of what's the more logical and definite solution.
But that—
How is it Sakurasou if someone who should be there isn't?!
I don't want anyone to leave!
2012 School Year Sakurasou Residents
Supervisor: Sengoku Chihiro
Room Number
Name
Class
Kanda Sorata
Akasaka Ryuunosuke
Mitaka Jin
Kamiigusa Misaki
Shiina Mashiro
Aoyama Nanami
Regular Year 2
Regular Year 3
Art Year 3
Art Year 2
Regular Year 2
Not Shiina, Aoyama, Misaki-senpai, Jin-san, Chihiro-sensei...
Or even you, Akasaka!
I want you all at Sakurasou!
We're all friends!
Well, allow me to retort.
Is this friendship you speak of so weak that it would disappear with the demolition of a single building?
No...
If what's keeping us together
is something so superficial,
then it's only a matter of
time before it crumbles.
That's not it!
Even if we manage to keep Sakurasou from being demolished,
half of its residents will
leave before next school year.
I think you should keep that in mind.
Well, Kamiigusa-senpai and
Mitaka-senpai are graduating, but...
You're forgetting someone.
You'll be leaving too, Ponytail.
Your audition results are
coming back soon, aren't they?
If you pass, you'll be part of an agency.
That means that your
financial difficulties will disappear,
and so will the need
for you to stay at Sakurasou.
Sakurasou isn't a place to live by choice.
If you no longer have a
problem, then you move out.
You don't have much time left.
It may be better spent making more memories than collecting more signatures.
If I pass my audition, I'll move
back to the regular dorms...
I completely forgot.
You'll be getting the results
back any day now, right?
Yeah.
That's why I'm always so nervous when I'm heading back to Sakurasou.
Yeah, I know how you feel.
I promised my dad that I'd go back to Osaka if I didn't make it.
So whether I pass or not,
I'll be leaving Sakurasou come spring.
Aoyama...
I'll still help out with
collecting signatures.
No way I want to see
Sakurasou to get demolished.
Does voice-acting school
only go for two years?
Yeah. Whether you pass or not,
you're out in two years.
I see.
That's a bit short.
It'd be nice if you could stay
there as long as you wanted.
I think it's easier to give up
if there's a firm deadline.
Telling someone they aren't cut out for something when it's true might be the nicest thing they can do.
My Beloved Ryuunosuke
Mashiro told me about Sakurasou being demolished.
Is there anything I can do to help?
---Rita
Ryuunosuke-sama is currently at school.
Ryuunosuke-sama
is currently
at school.
He has no time to deal with a former freeloader such as yourself.
He has no time
to deal with a
former freeloader
such as yourself.
Wait.
Mashiro told me that Ryuunosuke isn't collecting signatures for your petition.
Why isn't he?
That is none of your business.
Please, just tell me why.
I'm worried.
If Sakurasou disappears,
then Ryuunosuke will feel even more alone than he does now.
Aren't you worried about him too?
A security flaw has been detected.
There is risk of a data leak.
Ryuunosuke-sama was in middle school.
He and his friends decided to make a game.
At first, the work progressed peacefully.
But his skills were already
far superior to his peers.
After a while, the other developers were unable to meet his demands.
It frustrated him.
Sometimes he became so infuriated
that he could not withhold his anger.
They shunned and removed him from the project.
His friends never came back to him.
The issue has been resolved.
The issue has
been resolved.
Please do not
contact us
again.
Please do not contact us again.
Good-bye.
Shiina-san? You're still here?
Shiho.
Thank you for the signature.
That's a big canvas.
What are you painting?
The final review will be held on March 7th.
There will be no presentation this time around.
The meeting begins at 11 am,
and should end within 30 minutes.
I'll try to call you as soon as possible.
Sakurasou is being demolished
because Shiina is staying there.
How many more do I need to get?
I'll be leaving Sakurasou come spring.
Are you ready for the final round of the competition?
Kanda-kun?
Looks like it's going in
one ear and out the other.
I... I'm sorry.
Are you worried about something?
Apart from the final round, that is.
N-No, nothing really.
Shall we take a break?
No, you...
Two coffees, please.
I'm sorry.
I see.
A similar thing happened to me before.
Huh?
Back when I was finishing college,
I had to prepare for my current job.
And around the same time,
Rhythm Action Battle!!
A Whole New Game:
the woman I loved didn't know
what to do with her future.
Continue trying to be an artist?
Or become an art teacher?
I didn't have the time to help her.
If you can't choose one over the other,
then you can always choose neither and try to make both happen.
It doesn't matter which you choose.
So long as you think about what you want and need to do, and reach your own conclusion.
What I want to do?
Yes.
So, what now?
Should we go on with the meeting?
Yes.
Thank you very much.
Final Review
March 7th...
The day before the graduation ceremony.
Today was your last lesson?
Yeah.
Two whole years of taking lessons, and now it's over.
Two years...
Yeah.
Two years, huh?
Why'd you say it twice?
No reason.
I was just thinking how long that is.
Yeah, I guess it was pretty long.
Hey.
What?
What made you want to be a voice actress?
It was back in elementary school.
I had to read aloud once in language arts, and the teacher complimented me.
That's what started it.
I got interested in voice acting,
and at some point, I worked up the courage to try doing it myself.
But when I told my dad,
he wouldn't let me do it.
So I got really mad and ran out.
Sounds stupid, right?
But you kind of need momentum like that when you're doing something.
Yep.
The same goes for getting those signatures.
Let's work up some momentum
and try everything we can!
If we can both pass and stop Sakurasou from getting demolished, it'd be the best.
Yeah!
Welcome back.
Thanks.
What were you doing?
Looking at Sakurasou.
This came in the mail.
All right.
I didn't make it.
No way...
I did everything I could.
I'm satisfied.
Well, looks like that's it.
Aoyama—
I'm okay.
I'm not crying.
Don't push yourself.
If I cry now, I won't be
able to do anything else.
Sakurasou might get torn down,
but I'd just give up on collecting
signatures and everything.
I don't want that.
Kamiigusa-senpai and
Mitaka-senpai are graduating soon.
I don't want them to worry about me.
I want to see them off with a smile.
Don't worry.
I'll wait until the graduation ceremony.
After that, I'll cry my eyes out.
Listen, Kouhai-kun!
What are you wearing that for?
I got a nice idea for collecting signatures!
I call it "Operation: Animal Suit!
The Friends of the Forest Were Watching!"
Wait, you don't expect us to collect signatures in them, do you?!
Bullseye!
I'm definitely not wearing one!
I'm definitely wearing one!
Please sign our petition!
Don't interrupt their practice!
It's gotten pretty crazy.
Nanami's really energetic.
Yeah.
Looks like it's getting even crazier.
I bet she said, "I'll stop chasing them if you change into one too, Nanamin!"
"You said you'd stop!"
Don't let it get to you, Sorata.
But if you think about how Aoyama feels...
Yeah, I think Aoyama-san's pushing herself too.
But she wants to act bright and cheerful for the rest of us at Sakurasou.
We have to do everything we can.
If we can't stop Sakurasou
from getting demolished,
then everything she's done
will really be for nothing.
Incoming Call
International
Former Freeloader
Reject
Answer
Ryuunosuke-sama, you have an international call from one "Rita Ainsworth-sama."
I'm busy. Let it ring.
What?
Reject
Answer
I think it might be important.
I recommend that you answer it.
It's me.
We're against Sakurasou's demolition!
Please sign our petition!
Please!
Jin-san's right.
Please sign our petition!
Aoyama's working herself to death.
We can't just give up.
Please!
I don't waste effort on pointless acts.
That's all.
I know what you think.
But I'm asking about how you feel.
I heard that you experienced something horrible in middle school.
I gave up on painting and tried to get away from Mashiro once before,
so I completely understand.
If you're just going to be
disappointed, it's better not to try.
It's completely natural to feel that way.
But...
Even now, I'm painting pictures.
I still think of Mashiro as my friend.
That's because of Sorata, Nanami, Misaki, Jin...
and you, Ryuunosuke.
It's because you were there for me.
Ryuunosuke...
Sakurasou is a very important
place for you as well.
You have true friends who will
never desert or betray you now.
They're worth fighting for.
All right, let's give it our all today too.
Yeah!
Oh, that first-year!
He filled out a survey about
Nyaboron at the cultural festival!
Maybe he'll sign our petition!
Um... Do I have to sign here as well?
Huh?
I signed the notebook in the computer lab...
It was on the homepage.
Here.
It was in this classroom.
And look at this!
There's a link from the school website!
It even has a simple explanation
about the demolition!
Could it be...
Obviously!
There's only one guy we know who could do this!
Dragon!
Stay away from me!
What are you doing?!
The notebook in the computer lab!
Thanks!
Thanks a bunch!
Dividing an impossibly large task into smaller, solvable problems is a programmer's job.
Just get off me!
arifureta kanjou kara
All these emotions building up inside me
You should've told us
you were doing that!
sotsugyou mo dekitenakute
I couldn't get over any of them
Yeah! Why didn't you tell us?
nemurenai
So I can't sleep
A programmer doesn't
talk when he's working.
totsuzen no ame no karunda
That pain I felt when it suddenly
All right!
Now we've got a hope!
Dragon, you're wearing an animal suit and collecting signatures starting tomorrow!
ano kutsuu wa mabataki suru
Started to rain disappeared for a moment
Not a chance!
kimi no sekai wo chitto uketometeiru
I'm trying to understand a little of your world
Your reality and what I can see
kimi no riaru boku no shisen
Even if they're a little different
doko ka chigau to shite mo
I won't let it end up like that old, beat-up T-shirt, so
ano kutabireta ti-shatsu mitai ni sasenai kara
Fly into the world of prime numbers
puraimu nanba-sekai ni tobe
You won't get any duplicates when you multiply one
hitotsu to shite onaji mono ga nai
You don't need to fill the holes in your heart
kokoro no kuuhaku wo muri ni
If you don't really want to
umenakutemo ii ne
More than leaving my memory behind
takusan no dareka no kioku ni
In everyone in the world's hearts,
nokosareteiru yori mo
I want to be the sky you see from on top of the roof
yane no ue kimi dake no sora ni naritai
And...
100.
Sorata.
What is it?
What are you doing?
Counting signatures for the petition.
We've got nearly 300 so far.
We're still a long ways off from
two thirds of the school, though.
What's up?
I like Sakurasou.
Me too.
We all do.
Jin-san and Misaki-senpai, Aoyama
and Akasaka, and even Chihiro-sensei.
That's why they're protecting it.
Yeah.
I'll protect Sakurasou.
We all will.
Yes.
It's better when we're together.
Who knew getting
signatures would be so hard?
No One's To Blame When It Rains
Can we sign the petition too?
If we can, I'll get Jin to sign a marriage registration form while we're at it!
Yeah! That's a great idea!