Eat up, girls.
Real works of art.
Misaki-senpai spent all night working on them.
Today is Valentine's Day.
And...
Good morning!
O-Oh, morning.
You're up early.
Yeah.
I was feeling really nervous, so I thought I'd just leave early.
Oh...
I'll be going, then.
Aoyama!
See you later!
Thanks.
...the day of Aoyama's audition.
Iida Ayano
Hello?
The artist we asked to draw the cover got sick!
And Nanohanasou's gotten pretty popular, so...
Yeah.
Could you fill in and start working on a cover? And make it color.
Color?
Right. Color.
Is yellow okay?
Yellow?
I know one color might be avant-garde and all, but no.
It's the front cover! A showdown!
A showdown?
Was, "See you later," the best I could come up with?
Why couldn't I come up with something more inspiring?
Shiina! Time to get up—
Shiina...
you got dressed all by your—
I-Is that supposed to be some kind of fashion statement?
I picked one up, but another didn't come with it.
A single sock isn't supposed to form a pair on its own!
Wait...
Please tell me you're not going commando under that skirt.
Are you wearing panties?
One with a lot of colors—
A simple yes or no would've sufficed!
All right, now let me see what's in your—
You're horrible for trying to search through a girl's bag.
Oh, come on.
What if you forgot—
I put something important inside.
Something important?
And fighting spirit too.
I don't get it, but whatever.
I won't try to look inside.
I'll let you see tomorrow.
Huh? Tomorrow?
I hope you're not so uncouth as to continue pressing for answers, Sorata.
Rita?
You should've told us you were coming!
We would've picked you up if you called ahead of time!
You didn't tell anyone?
No.
I'm rather busy with my paintings right now,
but I made sure to set aside time for today.
Today is Valentine's Day!
A showdown for us girls!
Showdown?
I wish we could spend some time together, Mashiro,
but that will have to wait.
Now then, I'm off to battle!
You're not getting away, Ryuunosuke!
Wh-Why?! Why are you here, former freeloader?!
Well, let's go to school.
Yes.
Kanda! Kanda!
Come on, Ryuunosuke!
harewataru sora wa aoku
p
The clear sky shines so blue
chikadzuitekuru ashioto
v
I can hear your footsteps coming closer
hikaridashita kaze ni osareru you ni
n
Almost like the shining wind pushed me there
hora deatteshimatta
That's when I met you
sorezore no yume
a
Each of our dreams
sorezore no mirai
Each of our futures
matenai you ni hashiri
p
We ran because we couldn't wait
kidzuitara zutto issho ni itan da
Before I knew it you were always there with me
dare yori mo
More than anyone
nayande ochikonde naite waratte
Worrying, falling, crying, laughing
kasokushiteku
And running faster
kimi ni todoke
a
I want to reach you
sora wo kakete
Fly through the sky
massugu na omoi gyutto dakishime
a
Holding tight to my honest feelings
kitto umaretate no tsuyosa wa mune ni
y
I know this newborn strength will be part of my soul
kono kimochi ga tsubasa ni nari
These feelings will become my wings
watashi wa watashi wo tameteyuku
I'll grow to be more like myself
Morning!
Valentine's Is a Day for Chocolate
It's so cold!
Aoyama?
Dad
The audition is today.
Aoyama, I thought you'd be at your audition.
I can still make it in time after school's out.
No reason to skip.
O-Oh, really?
Yeah.
Um...
Sorry.
Earlier this morning...
I didn't know what to say.
Don't worry.
I wasn't expecting any words of encouragement from you in the first place.
Besides, you already gave me plenty of confidence.
Dad
The audition is today.
Sending
I did?
Yeah.
You showed me that hard work really can pay off.
Aoyama...
Kanda-kun, remember that promise?
What promise?
Well, once the results get back...
Good morning!
Sorata! Nanami!
Miyahara?
I heard you've got an audition today!
Y-Yeah.
Don't let us down, Nanami!
You're the star of the Regular Division!
You're just saying that, Miyahara-kun!
Work hard now!
The word "chocolate"
Chocolate
comes from the Aztec "chocolatl," which means "bitter water."
So listen closely, everyone.
Shiina Mashiro
No subject
I'll be on the roof after school.
Don't give chocolate to anyone you like.
Shiina?
Because whatever sweet feelings you have
Kanda-kun?
I-It's nothing.
were originally bitter water!
Does that mean...
I put something important inside.
Shiina's planning to give me chocolate?
And if your efforts pay off, that's just hmph!
Just give up already!
Normally, if a man were chased after so aggressively by a woman as beautiful as me,
he'd be shedding tears of joy.
What don't you like about me?
Everything!
Regardless, please accept my chocolate.
I already told you, no!
If I give in to one demand, who knows what you'll ask for next?!
You're making me sound like a terrorist.
That's exactly what you are!
On Christmas Eve...
I was very happy to receive that e-mail.
Was that—
That was me paying my respects to you at the end of the year.
We Japanese are big on respect.
To
Mizoguchi
Former Freeloader
Araki
Adachi
Subject
It meant nothing else.
Mizoguchi
Former Freeloader
Araki
Adachi
Mizoguchi
Former Freeloader
Araki
Adachi
Mizoguchi
Former Freeloader
Araki
Adachi
Mizoguchi
Former Freeloader
Araki
Adachi
Subject
Mizoguchi
Former Freeloader
Araki
Adachi
Subject
Mizoguchi
Former Freeloader
Araki
Adachi
Subject
Mizoguchi
Former Freeloader
Araki
Adachi
I see...
Okay, that's all for today!
Well, I'd better get going.
Yeah. Take care—
Kanda-kun, you're on cleanup duty today.
Here you go.
Bye!
Aoyama!
Come on, get to work!
I've got my hands full at Sakurasou,
and I can't catch a break at school either.
Misaki-senpai?
Senpai!
Hey, Kouhai-kun!
What are you doing?
Is that for Jin-san?
Us third-years don't need to come to school right now,
but Souichirou-kun said he'd bring Mitaka here.
The student council president?
Yeah! So I'm waiting for Jin here!
I see.
I noticed you made all sorts of chocolate,
but the one you brought with you is pretty small.
Did I screw up?
My love won't reach him with this much?
N-No, it's more like, you're really serious about it.
Give it to him, Misaki-senpai.
I'm rooting for you.
Okay! I'll do it!
Good junior you've got there.
Yeah. Kouhai-kun's the best.
There we go.
I hope I haven't kept Shiina waiting too long.
Incoming call...
Aoyama Nanami
Aoyama?
Incoming call...
Aoyama Nanami
Hello—
What do I do, Kanda-kun?!
This is awful!
Just awful!
Calm down. What—
The trains ain't movin'!
They're sayin' there was an accident!
They ain't got no idea when they'll be runnin' again!
I'm done for!
Calm down, Aoyama!
Have you called your voice-acting school?
I'm sure they'll understand if you explain what happened.
I called. They can push back my turn, but they can't change the date!
If I don't get there by six, the audition'll be over!
Aoyama, what station are you at?!
Huh? The next station down...
Can you get off the train?
Yeah. I'm on the platform now.
Wait for me by the station entrance!
I'm on my way!
Shiina, sorry! I'm gonna be late—
We're sorry, but the subscriber you have dialed is unavailable.
Please leave a message after the tone.
I'm gonna be late!
Aoyama's in trouble!
It's cold today, so wait in the classroom!
Man, that was close!
Sorata?
Miyahara, lend me your bike!
What?
Aoyama!
Trains stopped!
Audition today! Next station down!
Anyway, I'm in a hurry!
Nanami's...
Got it! Get on!
Miyahara?
No, just lend—
Just get on!
Hey, you!
That's not a two-seater!
We'll come back so you can give us an earful later!
Just let us go for now!
You damn kids!
Miyahara, let's just switch.
Don't underestimate me!
Behold the power of love!
Love?!
That's it!
She's all yours!
You go alone from here!
Hey, Miyahara...
The power of love...
Correction!
The power of a loser's love!
I got rejected!
By Nanami!
Wait... Hold—
Rejected?!
Here! Just go, damn it!
Thanks!
Make her fly, Sorata!
When she needed help the most, Nanami called you!
Aoyama!
Kanda-kun!
Aoyama, here! Get a taxi!
I can't! Everyone's been tryin' to get one!
I won't get one for a while!
Get on!
But we can't make it on a bicyc—
You've been busting your ass for two years!
We said we'd work hard together!
We said we'd chase our dreams together!
I'll never forgive you if you throw in the towel without me!
Kanda-kun!
Take me, Kanda-kun!
Get me to that audition!
It's almost time for my flight.
I was really busy,
but I wanted to see you, if only for today.
Tell the other residents of Sakurasou that I'm sorry I couldn't see them.
Tell Mashiro I'm sorry too.
P.S.
That kiss at the airport
was my first kiss.
P.S
That kiss at the airport was my first kiss.
I knew he wouldn't come.
Sorry to make you wait with me in the cold.
Hold on.
He still might show up.
I'll tell Souichirou-kun to give Mitaka a call.
No, no, it's okay!
I've still got plenty of chances to go on the offensive!
Oh, I know!
How about a bun on me as thanks for waiting?
It could be meat, bean, or even pizza!
All right, everyone! Let's bun!
Forward bun-ch!
Misaki...
He did something like this for me before.
Aoyama!
Y-Yeah?!
Want to go through the script again?!
Huh?
It's hard to hear each other when you're on a bicycle!
It might make good practice for the audition!
Kanda-kun is always so kind.
Okay!
All right!
You've got something to tell me?
What is it?
Yeah.
I guess it's... kind of important.
He always comes so close to my heart.
Actually, it's something I've wanted to tell you for a while.
Really?
Yeah.
I've...
always...
I've always...
I've always loved you.
I love you!
A-Aoyama, I...
Um...
What'd you think?
Did I get your heart racing?
Y-Yeah, you gave me a shock.
Yeah...
You'd never actually...
It's just a stone's throw from here.
I'll make it in time.
Thanks, Kanda-kun.
Bye!
Aoyama...
I left Shiina waiting!
I can't go on.
My legs feel like they're made of jelly.
One last spurt!
If she's still waiting for me...
Today is Valentine's Day.
Shiina!
Yeah, she probably already went home.
Sorry I'm late!
You always break our promises, Sorata.
I know! I'm sorry!
"Mashiro" when it's just the two of us.
S-Sorry, Mashiro.
I'll give this to you.
Ch-Chocoshoots?
Valentine's is a day for chocolate.
Th-Thanks.
But you could've given it to me at Sakurasou...
I wanted to do it the normal way.
Normal?
Lots of girls gave their chocolate on the roof.
That's how it happened in the manga Ayano gave me too.
But I'm not normal.
That's why I can't understand you lately.
Me?
You're so far away.
Far away?
Can you really say—
You get along really well with Yuuko.
That's because she's my sister.
Then what about Nanami?
Aoyama?
You went to Nanami today too.
Of course I would.
It's an important day for Aoyama.
It's an important day for me too.
You didn't say it to me.
That we'd work hard together.
Together?
But you're a pro. You're way ahead of us—
I see.
Shiina's always been running way ahead of me.
So far ahead that I can't even see her.
But I'm not the only one who can't see.
Even if Shiina turns around,
she can't see me.
I was looking forward to it too.
CHOCOSHOOTS
Sorata?
I thought that, just maybe, you'd give me some chocolate.
CHOCOSHOOTS
I couldn't wait for school to end ever since you sent me that text.
Really?
You're happy about the chocolate?
I like shoots better, you know.
That's good.
Mashiro...
We can't have you catching a cold now. Let's go home.
Sorata.
Can I hold your hand?
Actually, no.
Huh?! Wh-Why not?!
Because...
It feels weird.
It's beating so hard.
Mashiro...
You were always so far from me.
But now...
Sorata?
It's beating because you're alive.
What about you, Sorata?
I'm living even harder than you!
All these emotions building up inside me
arifureta kanjou kara
I couldn't get over any of them
sotsugyou mo dekitenakute
So I can't sleep
nemurenai
That pain I felt when it suddenly
totsuzen no ame no karunda
Started to rain disappeared for a moment
ano kutsuu wa mabataki suru
I'm trying to understand a little of your world
kimi no sekai wo chitto uketometeiru
Your reality and what I can see
kimi no riaru boku no shisen
Even if they're a little different
doko ka chigau to shite mo
I won't let it end up like that old, beat-up T-shirt, so
ano kutabireta ti-shatsu mitai ni sasenai kara
Fly into the world of prime numbers
puraimu nanba-sekai ni tobe
You won't get any duplicates when you multiply one
hitotsu to shite onaji mono ga nai
You don't need to fill the holes in your heart
kokoro no kuuhaku wo muri ni
If you don't really want to
umenakutemo ii ne
More than leaving my memory behind
takusan no dareka no kioku ni
In everyone in the world's hearts,
nokosareteiru yori mo
I want to be the sky you see from on top of the roof
yane no ue kimi dake no sora ni naritai
We're home!
Welcome back!
Aoyama? You're back already?
How'd the audition go?
Good.
I think I did everything I could.
Oh, dinner's ready.
Kamiigusa-senpai wanted to have a Valentine's Day dumpling party.
Dumplings? On Valentine's Day?
She forced Akasaka-kun to help wrap them too.
Nanami.
Where's Rita?
Huh? Rita-san?
The former freeloader went home.
Rittan was here?!
Why didn't you stop her, Dragon?
She was busy.
She had to leave.
But she came all the way to Japan.
It must have been for something important, right, Akasaka-kun?
Well, I guess everyone has a thing or two they can't say.
Huh?
No, Rittan'll be back to play soon enough!
For now...
Let's have a delicious dinner!
Chomp, chomp, chomp!
Chew, chew, chew!
Misaki-senpai?
Oh, right. I wonder if she gave her chocolate to Jin-san.
Maybe.
There are some things you can't say to someone, no matter how close you are.
Oh yeah...
That promise Aoyama mentioned this morning...
Kanda-kun, remember that promise?
If I pass the audition...
If I pass...
Could you hear me out on something?
I love you!
What's the matter, Kanda-kun?
N-Nothing!
No way! I must be overthinking it!
Aoyama would never...
I mean...
But...
I want to know for sure.
Is it sweet or salty?
A dumpling with chocolate inside?
Mashiron, you hit the jackpot!
Didn't your mother ever teach you not to play with your food?!
But it's got garlic in it!
That sounds so gross!
It's not good.
So this is a Valentine's Day dumpling...
We are aliens!
Space is full of bright, shining stars!
Love for an Alien
And full of dark matter.
Feelings you just can't put into words.
Hey, am I shining right now?