29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
29th Annual
Graduation Ceremony
Suimei University for the Arts Affiliated High School
Yeah, we're fine here.
Graduation Ceremony
See you there, then, Sorata.
Jin!
How'd it go?
Perfectly!
Your last day in that uniform, huh?
Getting turned on?
Wanna touch me one last time?
Hm, maybe for good luck.
Wait, Jin!
You're supposed to say no!
Oh?
So your the type who gets flustered when someone comes on to her?
No, I mean, I'd be okay with
it after the ceremony, but...
Have one!
What's going on?
Here you go.
Have one!
Pin it on your blazer.
What's this?
Good morning.
Here you go, Senpai.
Here you go!
A cherry blossom?
What's this? A pin?
You didn't hear about it?
I heard it was an idea from Sakurasou...
From Sakurasou?
No!
I don't care if we're in a hurry, you're not running a red light!
Even at a time like this?!
Maybe now's a good time, then.
I made some for you too.
They're cute.
Rita, what are these?
I heard that cherry blossoms are a celebratory symbol of departure for the Japanese.
So I thought that if all of the Sui High students could wear one at the ceremony...
You made enough for the entire school?!
Yes.
It was Ryuunosuke's ide—
Former Freeloader asked me to ask the student council about it.
They're probably being distributed now.
Wow!
Thanks, you two!
Everyone'll have a cherry blossom on their chest.
It sounds nice.
Yeah!
Stop squirming.
No! Get away from me!
All right! Let's go!
Yeah!
The graduating class.
Ryuunosuke...
You should get some more exercise.
Shut up.
Do you think they'll still let us in?
I'm not sitting in on something as tedious as a graduation ceremony. I'm listening from outside.
What's so funny?
Oh, nothing.
I don't like these tearjerker things.
I bet Ponytail's already crying her eyes out.
And we first met our upperclassmen at the freshman welcome party.
At first, we were anxious,
but our upperclassmen soon
gave us a warm welcome.
That's right.
I had nowhere to go...
We will defend and maintain the Sui High spirit
that our upperclassmen have given us.
I couldn't defend it.
Once the graduation ceremony
ends, Sakurasou will be...
Today is cherry-blossom-colored.
Next, a speech from the graduating class.
Representing the graduating class,
Kamiigusa Misaki.
Here!
Oh, it's Kamiigusa-san!
Hey! Why isn't it Tatebayashi?!
I, uh... I don't...
The cherry blossoms have yet to bloom,
and the spring sun shines warmly upon them,
inviting them to open their petals.
We can already feel the beginning of a new season upon us.
We, the third-year class,
thank you all that we may hold this graduation ceremony on such a day.
I decided to apply to Sui High
so that I could make friends.
When I was in middle school, I had no one I could call a friend.
But at this school...
At Sui High...
I might be able to find friends.
One of my teachers strongly recommended I apply for this reason.
And over the last three years here at Sui High,
I've made many dear friends.
And what allowed me to meet them
was a student dorm called Sakurasou.
Less than a week after entering the school,
I was evicted from the regular dorms,
and moved to Sakurasou alone.
At first, it was only the supervisor, Chihiro-sensei, and myself.
It was a very quiet and dreary place.
There wasn't a laugh to be heard.
There wasn't even a whisper.
That was how my high school life started.
On my first night at Sakurasou,
I looked at each of the empty rooms
and drew in my heart a dream.
And that dream...
was for all the rooms at Sakurasou to be filled.
For it to one day be filled
with warm light and laughter.
And that dream came true.
One after another,
the empty rooms were filled.
I would wish everyone a good morning,
announce that I was back when I got home,
and whenever someone came back, I'd welcome them home.
It was scary how happy I was.
The dream I drew in my heart when I first came to Sakurasou...
had finally come true.
Misaki-senpai...
Ryuunosuke?
This year was a constant stream of dreams coming true for me.
In the spring, we had a new resident move in.
There's a tradition at Sakurasou, where we have a hot pot party for anything special.
Last year, we only had two or three,
but this year, we kept having more and more.
Before we knew it, we were having a hot pot almost every week.
When we were all together around the hot pot, it made me think...
maybe this was the taste of happiness.
Misaki...
In the summer, we all
snuck into the school pool.
We played around in our swimsuits
until the security guard found us,
and we ran away in a panic.
I was running at the front,
and everyone followed right behind.
I'll never forget the
fireworks we saw that night.
Me too!
I ain't forgettin' that no matter what!
At the cultural festival in the fall,
we decided to produce and present something as Sakurasou.
While I've always wanted friends,
I have this feeling that, up until this year,
I hadn't thought of making
something with someone else.
Galactic Cat Nyaboron was better than anything I'd ever made before.
It was the ultimate masterpiece
we'd ever made at Sakurasou!
In the winter,
we found ourselves in conflict with each other many times.
The skies over Sakurasou
were not always sunny.
There were hard times when we
wanted to run away or give up,
but it was only because that rain fell
that the seeds of our emotions could sprout,
and the flowers of deeper
friendship could bloom.
Chihiro-sensei!
We know you did all sorts of things so that our hearts wouldn't be weighed down.
You were like a sister and a friend.
I'm proud that I can
call myself your student.
Mashiron!
I loved your eyes. I fell in
love with them at first sight.
You always saw me the same
way you saw everyone else.
I want to be proud of the me
you saw through your eyes.
I look up to you, Mashiron.
Misaki...
Nanamin!
Ever since you started voicing my anime,
I wished that you could move to Sakurasou to fill the last room.
And you granted me that wish.
Senpai...
Dragon!
You were hurt because people kept their distance from you,
and you tried your absolute hardest so it wouldn't happen again.
I saw part of myself in you sometimes.
You are a dear friend to me.
And if you feel that way about me, even in the slightest, I'm happy.
I hope you'll keep getting
along with Rittan forever!
And finally, Kouhai-kun.
You always listened to everything I had to say until I was finished.
You'd even play video games
with me until morning too.
No matter how many times or how high I drove you up the wall, you never ran away from me.
That made me so happy,
I couldn't help but get so excited.
I'm sorry I gave you so many headaches.
To all my schoolmates here at Sui High,
to all the teachers who supported me,
to all the people who live in this city,
and,
last but not least,
to all the friends
I met at Sakurasou,
I have only this to say:
Thank you for staying with me to this day.
It meant more to me
than thanks could express.
With more happiness than
these two hands can hold,
today, I...
I graduate from Sui High.
But...
The school is planning
to demolish Sakurasou.
My...
Our dearest...
Please don't tear down our Sakurasou!
Please!
Please give us your support!
Don't take Sakurasou away from us!
Misaki-senpai...
Please!
Don't take Sakurasou away from us!
Senpai hadn't given up.
Please give us your support!
Senpai...
Stop this at once!
You will not do more than your part!
What are you doing here?
Back to your seat!
This isn't more than her part.
I'm sure you know very well
that the speech from the graduating class is given by a representative from the class.
That does not give you a right to change the speech into your own!
And the representative was supposed to be Former Student Council President Tatebayashi—
He gave you the manuscript for your approval.
I believe he asked for your
approval to change the speech.
It was a manuscript for a
very important speech,
so naturally, you wouldn't not give it a look because it was too much work.
Don't just sit there!
Get her off the stage!
Yes, sir!
Kamiigusa!
Get off the stage now!
Misaki!
Misaki-senpai!
We should be thanking you!
Kouhai-kun?!
I was anxious when I was
kicked out of the regular dorms!
But you and Jin-san made
a place I could belong!
A place called Sakurasou!
That's why we—
Stop right there, Kanda!
Like hell I'd stop!
Kouhai-kun!
Senpai—
Shut up!
Senpai!
You stood in the line of fire
whenever anything happened!
Whenever we hesitated, you'd do something crazy and pull us forward!
Hey, you too?
Aoyama!
I like Sakurasou.
Don't take Sakurasou away from us!
Nanamin... Mashiron...
Do it, you guys!
This ain't all Sakurasou's got, is it?!
Miyahara-kun?
Hang in there, Nanami!
Do it!
Sh-Shiina-san, you can do it!
Keep it down!
You can do it, Sakurasou!
Sakurasou!
Hang in there!
You can do it!
That's what makes you Sakurasou!
Bring 'em down, Sakurasou!
We couldn't reach two thirds of the student body...
But...
We've reached them now.
Even though I turned it
into something personal...
Even though it's everyone's graduation...
It's not just Sakurasou...
Sui High! You're the best!
Misaki-senpai!
Kouhai-kun!
I wish...
I wish I could stay with you guys longer!
Kouhai-kun...
I wanted to fool around
with you guys more!
There's so much we still haven't done!
I don't want you guys to graduate!
I wanna be with you forever!
Don't worry.
You still have a year of high school left.
But you two won't be there.
That's why you need to make it a year just as awesome as ours was!
Live it up with the juniors
you're going to be getting!
All the things we couldn't do...
All the stuff we haven't done...
You can do it with them!
Senpai...
Come on, quit crying!
I'm rooting for you, Kouhai-kun.
I'm rooting for all of you!
I'm rooting for Sakurasou!
What do you say?
Yeah...
I can't hear you!
Yeah!
Cut it out!
Come on, just relax!
Same to the rest of you!
Back to your seats!
What are you doing?!
Good grief.
Why does everyone have to be so stupid?
This is why I don't care to listen in class.
What'd you say?
Don't you get it?
The audience is on our side.
Perhaps the faculty should admit it.
Tatebayashi?
Sakurasou was originally founded so that students in the art program
could explore their talents without concern for the critical eye of society.
I have no intention of saying that these rule-breaking problem children are doing the right thing,
but they are living their
lives true to their hearts,
with their eyes open to all possibilities,
and they are bound tightly
together in camaraderie.
I admit that I am
somewhat jealous of them.
I doubt that I was alone
in feeling this way.
Principal.
How about we take a vote right now?
What do you mean?
Fortunately, all the students
are gathered here today.
Are you for or against
Sakurasou's demolition?
Principal...
I'll let you take it from here.
Why me?
Kanda-kun!
Aoyama!
Ryuunosuke!
Now then, will those against
the demolition raise their—
That's no fun!
What should we do?
Now then, will those
against the demolition...
fill the air with cherry blossoms!
Nice blue sky today, huh?
Yeah.
What's wrong, Kouhai-kun?
You look kinda grumpy!
Of course I'd be grumpy!
Why do we have to stand outside on the day of the graduation ceremony?!
You're telling me.
I'm holding it against them if I don't get to pick on Kanda enough later.
Okay, you deserve to stand outside!
When'd you get the idea for that speech?
You could've told us, you know.
If we did, Aoyama-san
would've been against it.
Of course!
But you would've done it anyway.
Of course.
It was a very well-calculated plan.
Manipulating the audience's
emotions with the speech
and showing how poorly
the faculty react and treat us.
You made a situation where you had to be against the demolition before taking it to a vote.
Even those who wouldn't sign the petition would throw their flower on the spur of the moment.
When you say it like that, it sounds like I tricked them into doing it.
Sounds like? You co—
But all's well that ends well, Nanamin!
Sakurasou will never die!
Yeah! Sakurasou'll never—
Keep it down out there!
They got mad at us because of Sorata.
Kanda, keep it down!
Kanda-kun, shh!
No one's saying anything
about Misaki-senpai?
Don't you find that strange?
Oh, this song...
I put in a special request to Hauhau!
itsu made mo taeru koto naku
Let's all stay friends forever
Isn't this a song for
elementary school graduations?
tomodachi de iyou
Nothing will tear us apart
It's a nice song, though.
asu no hi wo yume mite
We'll dream of what tomorrow might bring
kibou no michi wo
As we walk down the road full of hope
sora wo tobu tori no you ni
Let's live our lives free like the birds
jiyuu ni ikiru
Flying through the sky
kyou no hi wa sayounara
Today we have to say good-bye
mata au hi made
Until the day we meet again
shinjiau yorokobi wo
Let's keep the joy of trusting one another
taisetsu ni shiyou
Deep within our hearts
kyou no hi wa sayounara
Today we have to say good-bye
mata au hi made
Until the day we meet again
Welcome to Sakurasou