Our 15th Summer Vacation
Four years, huh?
This year's been way hotter than usual!
You say that every year.
Hey, don't just—
Saki!
You're back already? You should've called.
I wanted to take a look around town by myself.
They changed a few things around the station.
Yeah. They did that this year.
Saki-chan, is it just me or did you get even more beautiful since I last saw you?
Y-You think so?
Maybe it's because the food on the island is fresher.
They're calling you "The Anonymous Beauty" on Yuka's blog.
Oh yeah!
Don't just put my picture on your blog!
Let's not talk about that.
Oh, right!
Did you call Natsumi yet?
Yeah. I texted her a couple minutes ago.
Hello!
She's already on her way over.
Yuka's getting a lot of fans from that TV show.
You said that you're on it every week, right?
It's just a local thing for this city, though.
That's still really good!
I mean, two years ago, when you passed that major audition,
the training was too hard, and you...
I don't want to remember!
Didn't we tell you about that?
I asked Yuka to come back home on the phone.
Honestly, I thought you might have given up,
but you're still going for it.
Stop it!
Saki!
Natsumi!
Welcome home, Saki!
Good to be home.
Looks like you're doing pretty well in tennis, too.
Well, I guess you could say that...
Come now, don't be so modest!
A university scouted you for their tennis team, right?
Wow, that's great!
Yeah, I guess.
But I don't really know if I should...
Natsumi, come here.
There.
Thanks.
Did you grow a bit taller?
Yeah, a little.
Hey, don't you think Natsumi looks pretty cool?
Really?
Natsumi's really popular at school.
What are you talking about?
Not just with just the guys, but with the girls as well!
The girls in lower grades absolutely love her.
Don't help her, Rin!
They're lying! It's not like that at all!
Going to high school together sounds like fun.
What about you, Saki? Having fun at school over there?
Of course. Chiharu and Koharu are there, too.
You're going to medical school, right?
Yeah.
After watching my dad treat patients for so long, I kind of want to do the same thing.
Won't it be really difficult?
Well, yeah.
But I can do one-on-one lessons online,
and I'm already signed up for an intensive course in the city this year.
Saki, you're amazing!
Everybody else is doing it, so...
I heard you're going to a university, too, Rin.
Yeah. I kind of want to study folklore.
She developed a knack for it after investigating the big rock!
And I've always liked it.
What was that thing you wanted to be? A mystery hunter?
Chasing mysteries across the globe!
Who's that supposed to be?
You all know what you want to do...
Natsumi?
My mom told me I should go to college and all that,
but I still don't know what I want to do.
I want to keep playing tennis, but a university tuition is pricey.
I think your mom took that into consideration before encouraging you to go.
I mean, parents are always thinking more about us kids than we could possibly know.
"Go to college and find what you really want to do."
I think that's what your mom is saying.
You really think so?
Oh, I know!
I just got a brilliant idea!
Natsumi, you can be an idol with me while going to college!
What?
Be a celebrity as a side job!
It'll pay off the tuition, too! It's perfect!
It's not as easy as you think!
Why not?
I mean, Rin got an award, too.
An award?
Huh? Didn't we tell you?
Rin got a something-or-other award! It's a big one!
It's just an honorable mention.
Wow!
Oh, I read it!
Yuka was the main character, right?
It was really good!
Yuka's the main character?
Well, it's more like the four of us are main characters.
I'm in it, too?
Yeah.
I based it on that summer four years ago.
But it was raw talent that won it.
Can I read it, too?
Yeah. I'll link it to you now.
It really feels like it was all just a dream now.
Yeah.
Oh, hey! Why don't we all go on TV?
Huh?
Why?
The producer for the show saw my blog and asked if we could all go on the show!
What? We can't go on just like that!
Relax! Relax!
If the need for it arises, I'll take the lead.
If everything goes well, we might even become an idol unit!
A handsome, sporty girl.
An intelligent, mysterious beauty going to medical school.
A mystery hunter and award-winning novelist.
And the cute and pure idol-type, me!
We've got all the bases covered!
We can do this!
I never said that I'd do it!
Saki.
We haven't wished on the big rock since then,
but do you think that it'll grant anything else?
Huh?
I attached the manuscript for my book.
This?
That's right! That's it!
The title of the story is...
A Summer-Colored Miracle!
A Summer-Colored Miracle
kyuu ni damarikonde
You suddenly stayed silent,
kimi wa te wo tsunaida
And then you took and held my hand
akanezora ni kieteku kyou wo
We watched as our shadows grew taller,
miokuru nagai kageboushi
And the day sank into the orange sky
houkago wa eien mitai ni
After school always seemed like forever
sayonara wo gomakashiteta ne
We would always try not to say good-bye
dakedo kokoro wa tabidachi no yokan wo shitteta
But deep inside we knew that we would have to go our separate ways
hateshinai mirai he no tamerai wo kakushite
Hiding our worries about everything that lay in the future
hohoemu kimi no yume ga mabushii yo
Your smile I saw in my dreams was just so bright
ato sukoshi no kisetsu wo oshimu you ni hashaida
With the season's end coming closer, we played so much to make up for time
ashita he no kaerimichi
The road back home and to tomorrow
kitto juunengo wa
Maybe, ten years from now,
nanigenai nichijou
Our lives won't be as full
tatoe chigau sora no shita demo
But even if we live under different skies
bokura wa daijoubu da yo ne
Even then, we'll still be all right
te wo futta kousaten kara
As I'd walk from the place we'd wave good-bye
ie made no mijikai saka wo
On the short road up the hill and back home
furimukinagara chiisaku naru senaka tookute
I'd stop and turn around to watch as you walked home so far away
wasurenai to chikatta
We swore that we'd never forget each other
kodomoppoi yakusoku
We were just kids making a promise
shinken na kimi no kao ga ureshikute
But I could see you were serious, it made me so happy
taisetsu ni yakitsukeru ima ga itsuka kanata de
Even if someday, somewhere, these moments we shared so preciously
omoide ni kawattemo
Turn only into memories
hateshinai mirai he no tamerai wo kakushite
Hiding our worries about everything that lay in the future
hohoemu kimi no yume ga mabushii yo
Your smile I saw in my dreams was just so bright
ato sukoshi no kisetsu wo oshimu you ni hashaida
With the season's end coming closer, we played so much to make up for time
ashita he no kaerimichi
The road back home and to tomorrow
kitto juunengo wa
Maybe, ten years from now,
nanigenai nichijou
Our lives won't be as full
tatoe chigau sora no shita demo
But even if we live under different skies
bokura wa daijoubu da yo ne
Even then, we'll still be all right
bokura wa hitori ja nain da
Even then, we'll never be alone