Someone who could stick with a liar?
That's totally obvious.
A partner in crime.
Hey there, everyone! What you've all been waiting for, the Miss OreDere Contest, is about to begin!
First up is entry number one: Harusaki Chiwa-san!
A War Zone for a Whole New World
She's tiny!
She's cute too!
Just like a Chihuahua!
They're starting with Chiwa?
Hi there, Chiwa-chan.
Why don't you introduce yourself to everyone?
M-My name is Harusaki Chiwa.
I'm a first-year in high school.
M-My hobbies are skirt steaks and tripe.
And I've been reading a lot of shoujo manga lately, I guess.
Her hobbies are meats?
Next, I'd like you to show everyone just how head-over-heels you are.
Um... Sure!
Is the guy you're head-over-heels for here today?
Yes, I think so.
Could you tell us what he's like?
Well, I guess you'd call him
"too freaking serious."
All he's done since he got
into high school is study.
He has the highest grades in our year, but he won't stop.
He says he's shooting for a higher goal.
Yeah, I'd call that "too freaking serious."
That's why I just can't leave him alone.
We've been together since we were kids.
Oh, so he's your childhood friend?
That's right!
He's almost like a cute little brother!
Also, he's really, really kind to me.
I can't do anything for him, and I'm always causing trouble.
I always get jealous too.
The things he's done for me mean more to me than he'll ever know.
I don't know how I could ever repay him.
The best I can do is tell him, "Thank you."
That's our situation right now, but I hope to become a better woman
and someone who can better complement my childhood friend.
Ei-kun, I love you!
That was Harusaki Chiwa-san, everyone!
You go, girl!
Now for our next contestant,
entry number two: Akishino Himeka-san! Come on up!
Akishino-san?
Akishino Himeka-san, please come out.
Did Hime get stage fright or something?
I wouldn't be surprised.
Eita, hold me?
Yeah, if I could just be with her and hold her—
Wait, you're here!
I can't do this.
Yes, you can.
You're a member of the society, remember?
Come on.
Hey, Hime-chan! Get up here!
You've been working harder than anyone else in our club!
If you run away now, all that hard work'll be for nothing!
As your master, I can't let that happen!
How can I stop being so scared?
Hime, let's drown out that scared with love.
What do you love the most?
Eita.
Huh? O-Okay, that works.
Now, say you love me ten times.
I'm not sure what you mean.
I-It's like an incantation invoking black magic.
By calling upon the elements that reside within the power words of the name of what you love,
Wait, I'm not done yet!
you can charge yourself with vital energy,
Hime-chan! Hime-chan!
like, whoosh, and boop boop boop beep!
Understood.
I love you.
Eita, I love you.
I've changed since I met you, Eita.
I love you.
I can greet my classmates when I walk into class.
I've made three friends.
I love you.
I thought I'd never get to see a beach.
Eita, I want to be your number one.
But if that means I'll eventually be cast away, I can settle for second.
I love you.
Even if I'm only third or lower,
I'll be happy so long as you just smile at me now and then.
I love you.
Hime...
Even if you ever come to hate me,
I'll always love you.
Eita, I love you.
Eita?
I'd never hate you. You know that.
I'm so happy.
'Sup, Eita?
Eita, I love you.
And that was entry number two, Akishino Himeka-chan, showing off her head-over-heels level!
Next up, we have entry number three: Mizunoe Satsuki-san!
Ei-kun, what was that all about?
When did I say you could
hold Hime-chan, Takkun?
Cheater
Lewd
And that was Suzumiya Yoshino-san's head-over-heels display!
That girl wasn't half bad.
She knew what she was doing.
Master knows all.
Fat lot of good that did her. She was disqualified.
I'm so disappointed.
BAM
They can't even rate my
lovely preaching technique?
BAM
POUT
This contest is a joke.
That was entry number eleven,
Kawaji Rin-chan, showing how much she loves her daddy!
And here's entry number twelve:
Natsukawa Masuzu-san!
Masuzu...
Is she a foreigner?
Wow, look at her hair!
She's gorgeous!
Her skin's so white...
She doesn't even compare...
Is that her natural hair color?
Look at those long legs.
Natsukawa's getting the same response she always does.
She's a "jewel," after all.
Let's have you start off with an introduction!
I must apologize to our kind host and to those here in the audience.
Huh? Why's that?
I do not have the right
to participate in this contest.
More precisely, I lost that right last night.
Could you elaborate?
My boyfriend broke up with me.
Is this a prank?
Ei-kun, is she serious?
Eita, what happened
between you and the president?
Does this mean you're single now? Does Ai-chan epic win again?
Did you really break up with her?
Ei-kun!
Takkun!
Eita!
Did she plan this?
Man, she's a total bitch.
What's going on? She doesn't look happy.
Why'd she have to ruin the mood?
Bring out the next girl!
Um, Masuzu-chan?
She looks like she's about to cry.
She looks like a bitch to me.
What are you getting all depressed for?
I guess even hot girls get dumped if they get too conceited.
Why enter the contest if you don't have the right?
What are you getting depressed for, Masuzu?
You're the president of SAMEFAG!
You're the biggest samefag of us all!
So finish it!
What's wrong with you?
Keep playing Natsukawa Masuzu!
Keep acting!
Keep playing Natsukawa Masuzu
to the bitter end!
Eita...
What did you come here for?
I came here to play your boyfriend.
Let's start over, Masuzu.
It'll be the same no matter how many times we do this.
We'll end up twisted, not right for each other.
No matter how close a fake gets, it'll never be the real thing.
But two fakes may be right for each other.
It won't work.
You have genuine "reals" all around you.
Yeah.
Reals that are way too good for me.
Then why do you want to stay with a fake?
Isn't it obvious?
It's because I love you, Natsukawa Masuzu!
The first time we met, I assumed you were a bitch because of how beautiful you were.
And I couldn't have been more right.
I thought all you had going for you was your looks.
You were such a bitch that I just had to laugh.
But that's why I love you. I'm in love with you.
You're not making any sense.
The only person who could stick with a total bitch like you...
is a total bastard like me!
You know better than anyone just how terrible and embarrassing I really am!
That's why you're the only one for me!
Don't make me laugh.
I've always hated you, Eita.
I hated the fact that you
had better grades than me.
I hated the fact that you didn't talk to me, even though I sat next to you.
I hated the fact that you were so close to your childhood friend.
I've always loathed you
from the bottom of my heart.
I kept telling myself that I'd make sure you got your just deserts.
I was overjoyed when I got my hands on you-know-what,
but I was sad too.
Because it meant you'd see my true colors.
That you'd hate me.
And yet...
And yet, you were nice to me.
You were even nicer to me after you got to know me.
Are those tears real?
Or are they fake?
I don't know.
I don't even know what I...
I'll decide for you, then.
You're my girlfriend.
Stay my girlfriend, Masuzu.
In the end, the winner
of the head-over-heels contest
was a ten-year-old girl who talked about how much she loved her dad.
As for the participating SAMEFAG members,
Chiwa received an honorable mention, but that was all.
No one came to dinner that night.
Wh-What are you doing, Masuzu-san?!
Just watching the man
who tricked me as he slept.
I was thinking about killing you.
Just to be sure,
you were lying when
you said you loved me, right?
You don't really love me, do you?
Of course not. I hate you.
I'd have broken up with you long ago if I had my notebook back.
I'm the biggest bitch in the world.
I'm shameless, merciless, and can't control my tongue.
I'm arrogant, disrespectful,
pathetic, tragic, wretched,
and someone who loves you very much.
That's the type of woman your girlfriend is.
Eita!
Eita! Eita!
Such a wonderful man is my boyfriend!
Snuggle, snuggle, snuggle.
M-Masuzu-san?
Masuzu's snapped!
I can hear the waves.
Huh? Oh...
When I do this, I feel like I'm rotting from the inside out.
But if I am to rot and return to the earth with you, then so be it. I wouldn't mind at all.
Eita, you awake?
Y-Yeah.
I have something to talk to you about before I go back to work. Can you come downstairs?
Sure.
It'll be fine. You can trust your boyfriend.
I know.
After what you did yesterday, there's no going back now.
You're totally bound for the war zone route now.
I'm not sure what to think. I'm worried.
Sorry.
You might still have a chance.
I know of a third route that avoids the war zone and doesn't go down the harem route.
That sounds like a dream.
Do the opposite of winning.
If winning is getting the girl
to fall in love with you,
then you just have to do the opposite.
Get everyone besides your girlfriend to hate you.
Hime, it's me.
Could you let me in?
My memories from my past life have returned in their entirety.
I need to talk to Burning Prin Princess right now.
Is that true, Eita?
That kiss yesterday was a real shock.
Yeah.
I know you're dating the president in this life,
but it still was hard for me to see you two kiss in front of my eyes.
I said I would be fine with being second, but...
Sniff.
Eita, what memories did you get back?
Are they memories of me?
The truth is, I wasn't Burning Fighting Fighter after all.
I was Villager A, and I had no powers at all.
I had false memories planted in me to divert the attention of the Wyverns.
How did you find out?
I heard God's voice.
The real Burning Fighting Fighter has reincarnated somewhere on this planet.
I have fulfilled my duty.
Surprise!
I'm sorry. I guess I gave
you the wrong impression.
But now, you can search for your real lover—
Wonderful.
Huh?
I think that backstory is absolutely wonderful.
Did you just say "backstory"?!
That sad legend is wonderful.
No take backs!
Eita, Villager A is even better!
Hey!
This whole time, I only had you hold me,
but if you're really Villager A, then I can protect you too!
That means...
I can hold you, Eita!
Hold on a second! Isn't Burning Fighting Fighter the one you love?!
I'll figure out who I'll choose later.
Failed with the first one.
Open up, A-chan. Please.
Could you show me the marriage registration?
Why?
I want to see it. Please.
What are you going to do?
Once I rip this paper up,
everything will be over between us.
Do it.
Do it, Kidou Eita!
It's Murata.
Murata the Bear.
I was worried about sleeping away from home, so I brought him with me.
Murata...
Why don't you remember?
Huh?
I introduced you back when
we were in the star class.
As my best friend.
Why? Why don't you remember?
Takkun, you big dummy!
Wait a second.
A handkerchief...
Huh? Er...
You stamped it...
Huh?
You stamped it!
What the—
What's that?!
What's this?!
Oh my God, he really stamped it!
Ai-chan, epic win!
Wait, it was an accident!
Listen to me!
Thank you, Takkun!
I was stupid for worrying
about Natsukawa Masuzu!
I mean, a kiss isn't legally binding!
Just listen!
Hold on... A-chan...
Nothing tops a marriage registration!
Ai-chan's gonna go run outside!
Once we graduate high school,
we're taking this to city hall!
Epic fail with the second one.
Chiwa...
Yeah?
Masuzu and I are... well, we're like that.
I know.
You're boyfriend and girlfriend.
Of course you'd kiss.
You're not mad?
Why would I be mad?
You're always trying your hardest.
You're always studying so hard to be a doctor.
I don't have the right to be angry.
Still, I cried a little last night.
It felt like you'd gone far away.
I mean, I'm really small, right?
I don't act like it bothers me, but it does.
I've always wished I could be tall like Natsukawa,
or that my butt and boobs could be bigger.
I've always wished that,
hoping I could get you to look at me.
Bigger...
Get... bigger...
Don't cry, Chiwa.
You didn't think I could reach you, did you?
I grew a bit taller recently.
We're always together,
so I bet you didn't notice.
I've told you so many times.
Make sure you listen this time.
Ei-kun, I love you.
If things could be settled with a simple
"I love you," we wouldn't need the police.
You seem to be enjoying yourself there, childhood friend.
Mind letting me join in on the fun?
Masuzu...
Take a hint, girlfriend.
How about you come back in nine years?
Chiwa...
One, two, three!
isse-no
One, two, three
okaeri
Welcome back
saa dekakeyou
Now, let's go out
nukegake rendezvous
I'm stealing you for a rendezvous
Friends are important
kizuna ga daiji
koibito ga daiji
But a girlfriend is the most
Girlish Lover
kono itami kimi no sei
This pain I feel is your fault
mune no tokimeki uso no tsumori
This feeling in my chest is supposed to be a lie
ima made no position wo
What would happen if tomorrow
koeta ashita wa dou naru no
I tried being more than what I am to you now?
nee motto issho shiyo
Hey, let's spend more time together
dame
Can't we?
dame watashi dake
You can't, he's mine
yudan mo suki mo nai
You can never be too careful with me
kimi to no border koetai
I want to jump the border between us
sou motto
Now, I'll be
daitan de chotto gouin
A bit bolder, maybe even aggressive
suki wo misetai
I want to show you all my love
yasashii kimi mo
I want you when you're nice
ijiwaru na kimi mo
I want you when you're mean
hitorijime
You're all mine
kidzuite
Please realize
yappa yamete
Never mind, just stop
urahara fall in love
It's the wrong way to fall in love
tomodachi ijou
I'm more than just your friend,
honmono miman no
But less than a real
Girlish Lover