Call me Masuzu from now on.
Wh-What are you two doing?!
Look at you, with your arms linked!
Lewd! That's so lewd!
Ch-Chiwa...
Eita-kun, who is this little girl?
D-Don't call me little!
I'm Ei-kun's childhood friend!
Harusaki Chiwa!
Ei-kun, how come you didn't tell me you got yourself a girlfriend?
Well, it all happened so fast, and...
Do I need your permission to date Eita-kun, Harusaki-san?
Y-Yeah, you do.
I know everything there is to know about Ei-kun.
Like how he left milk in his locker back in third grade, and it went bad!
And how during the school marathon, he stepped in poop, and was called "Poop Bulldozer" for a while!
How interesting. "Poop Bulldozer," you say?
Kill me now.
That's why anyone who wants to date Ei-kun needs to go through me first.
I understand.
Starting today, I, Natsukawa Masuzu,
will be dating Kidou Eita-sama.
It is my sincerest wish that you give us your blessing.
Now, Eita-kun, let's continue with our date.
Ei-kun...
Ei-kun, you...
Ei-kun, you traitor!
isse-no
One, two, three
okaeri
Welcome back
saa dekakeyou
Now, let's go out
nukegake rendezvous
I'm stealing you for a rendezvous
kizuna ga daiji
Friends are important
koibito ga daiichi
But a girlfriend is the most
Girlish Lover
kono itami kimi no sei
This pain I feel is your fault
mune no tokimeki uso no tsumori
This feeling in my chest is supposed to be a lie
ima made no position wo
What would happen if tomorrow
koeta ashita wa dou naru no
I tried being more than what I am to you now?
nee motto issho shiyou
Hey, let's spend more time together
dame
Can't we?
dame watashi dake
You can't, he's mine
yudan mo suki mo nai
You can never be too careful with me
kimi to no border koetai
I want to jump the border between us
sou motto
Now, I'll be
daitan de chotto gouin
A bit bolder, maybe even aggressive
suki wo misetai
I want to show you my love
yasashii kimi mo
I want you when you're nice
ijiwaru na kimi mo
I want you when you're mean
hitorijime
You're all mine
kitsui tte
Too much for you?
yappa yamete
You really want to stop?
urahara fall in love
It's the wrong way to fall in love
tomodachi ijou
I'm more than just your friend,
honmono miman no
But less than a real
Girlish Lover
One... two...
Chiwa, are you sure you can practice your swing?
Forming a New Club Results in a War Zone
You're not supposed to do any kendo.
I just can't... compete in any... matches.
That's what... the doctor said.
All right.
Ei-kun!
Hm?
I'm gonna...
I'm gonna get myself a really cool boyfriend!
I'll be the most popular person ever!
Whatever you say.
I wasn't expecting this from you.
You always went on and on about being "anti-love,"
and now you're dating Natsukawa-san. It's a bit of a shock.
Believe me, I'm shocked, too.
That's the guy?
The whole school's talking about it.
Isn't he top of the class?
That's who she chose?
I think I'm finally beginning to understand how Natsukawa felt.
Shouldn't you be eating lunch with Natsukawa-san?
Though it seems she's not here.
I've never seen her in the classroom at lunch.
Me neither.
Did you come to school with Chiwawa-chan today?
No, she's been keeping her distance since yesterday.
I heard she came to school late with bread hanging from her mouth.
What?
What's she up to now?
I also heard that she's tacking "meow" onto the end of her sentences.
Any clue why she'd suddenly start doing that?
Yeah.
So you know.
Eita, if you're going to date Natsukawa-san,
I think you'd better sort things out with Chiwawa-chan first.
Why?
I mean,
Chiwawa-chan's like family to you, isn't she?
Hey, Natsukawa...
Oh, come on.
Hey, Masuzu—
No.
Huh?
"Hey, Masuzu, can I at least tell Chiwa that this whole thing's fake?"
That's what you wanted to ask, right?
Your kind-heartedness has left you
feeling responsible for Harusaki-san's odd behavior, hasn't it?
Yeah. I'll make sure she keeps it a secret, so—
No.
As soon as you say, "Just between you and me,"
or, "Keep this a secret," a secret ceases to be a secret.
The moment someone finds out you're a fake, you will lose your ability to function as my shield.
Sorry, my mistake.
You apologize so sincerely.
I like that.
In short, Harusaki-san is acting strangely because she wants to be "the most popular person ever," correct?
I think so.
Does Harusaki-san have her sights set on anyone in particular?
No way.
Are you sure?
What do you mean?
Well, that's fine.
Bring Harusaki-san to me after school tomorrow.
What are you going to do?
You'll have to wait until tomorrow to find out.
Woof! Woof! Woof!
Don't try to bite me!
Why did you bring me here, meow?!
Tea Club
Meow?
Now I'm not sure whether you're a cat or a dog.
I called you here today to invite you to join our club, Harusaki-san.
Club?
Harusaki-san, I hear you've been having trouble becoming popular with guys.
What's it to you?! ...Meow!
I don't mean to brag...
but I'm popular.
I'm incredibly popular.
I'm so popular that it's become burdensome,
but I can't stop attracting the attention of anything male.
However, despite my current status,
I haven't always been popular.
It took a great deal of sustained effort and repeated trial and error,
but I'd say that this is what helped me the most.
I owe my phenomenal popularity to this notebook.
W-Wait!
Ei-kun, I can't see!
Are you telling the truth?
It's all thanks to that notebook?
This is full of memories left behind by my first love.
It contains informative lessons, in the form of a journal,
on exactly what it means to be attractive to the opposite sex.
Using this as our textbook,
our club conducts resarch and experiments on how an individual can gain popularity.
A-And what happened to your first love?
This past March,
he left for the store and never returned. His last words were,
"Our fight has only just begun."
Real Man
No. No, he didn't. He definitely didn't.
If you ever come across someone who's suffering from being unpopular,
you simply must help them.
Earth to Chiwa...
I believe that's what he would have said.
That's why I created this club.
Please, Harusaki-san, let me help you become insanely popular!
I understand how you feel,
but I can't just turn to you for help without giving anything in return.
Turning tail, are we?
I-I'm not turning tail...
Oh, and Eita-kun will be participating in this club as an advisor.
If you don't join us, then it'll just be me and him, all by ourselves.
I'll do it! I'll join!
I'll fall for your sweet talk!
Good!
H-Hey, Chiwa...
What now, Ei-kun?
You wanna be alone with her that bad?
N-No, not that...
I can do this, too!
This club is going to be fun.
But don't we need permission to form a club?
This room belonged to the Tea Club, which no longer exists.
I asked the the former Tea Club's moderator to be the moderator for our club.
For "a club that helps people get insanely popular"?
I chose my words with a little more tact.
"A club for young women to consider what being a Japanese woman truly means
and to learn the appropriate etiquette and decorum
to be a prim, proper, and elegant maiden."
Well, I guess that was eloquent.
The Society Advocating Maidenly Elegance For All Girls.
Society Advocating Maidenly Elegance For All Girls
Maidenly elegance...
That name sounds pretty good!
Yeah, I like it!
Or, for short...
SAMEFAG.
Get it?
Th-This girl...
SAMEFAG
Ei-kun, I'm definitely gonna get more popular than Natsukawa
and totally show her up!
Good for you.
So Chiwawa-chan's really serious about the club?
Yeah.
I think she's needed another way to release all her pent up energy
ever since the doctor said she couldn't do kendo anymore.
You look pretty happy for her, Eita.
Come on, don't be stupid.
Still, you must feel smothered, sandwiched between those two.
You got that right. You're the only one who understands my pain.
We are best friends, after all.
First, we need a target.
A target?
A person you're going to make your boyfriend.
In short, the guy you'll be seducing.
Yeah, I think it'd be better if you had a goal.
That's how it works when you study.
Do you have anyone you sorta like?
Of course I don't.
How about... I think his name's Sakata-senpai?
He's on the basketball team.
All the girls in my class were going on about how cool he is.
You mean Sakagami-senpai? The third-year?
Yeah, yeah, that's the guy.
Oh, him.
The star of the basketball team with the pretty face, right?
He definitely seems like he'd be popular.
Well... It might not be a very good idea...
What? Is there something wrong with him?
No, it may actually be a good idea.
His younger brother is in our class.
It should be easy to get his attention.
Okay, so I'll aim for Sakashita-senpai for now.
His name is Sakagami.
Oh, right. Sakagami-senpai.
Something wrong? You don't sound very excited.
Don't worry. This will get her excited.
Your attention please.
I'm going to read a passage from my first love's diary.
"September 28th. Sunny."
"I leave home today with my buddy on my back."
"I can't go anywhere without him."
"He is an irreplaceable part of me."
"He is my very soul: my guitar."
"With him on my back, I am an artist."
"My buddy and I are feeling the heat again today,
under the passionate gazes of those around us."
Ei-kun, what's wrong?
"But I keep a cool, composed expression on my face."
"You know how it is."
"A cool face and a hot soul know no bounds."
"Now, let's get today's gig started."
Ei-kun, what's gotten into you?
"I'll rock this gray stage red hot!"
I can't believe hearing my entries hurts so much!
The lesson within:
People in bands are popular.
Especially people who play the guitar.
Male high school students who start playing the guitar do so to become popular.
Any detective worth his salt would tell you the same.
But I can't play the guitar.
That's fine.
You won't get a chance to play it in school, anyway.
Here, take this.
Huh? It doesn't feel like there's anything in this.
It'd be too heavy if there were.
Walk around with that case at all times.
A guitar is a part of a guitarist's body.
If anyone tries to touch the case,
just yell, "Don't dirty my soul with your filthy hands!"
A short fuse is another trait of the guitarist.
Also, be sure to rant incessantly about how terrible Japanese music is.
That's another basic trait a guitarist must have.
Someone's got a lot of prejudices.
I've never listened to any Western music.
I don't know any musicians, either.
Not musicians. Artists.
Don't worry.
The notebook mentions that if you're asked who your favorite artist is,
you can just say one of the names of the stands that appear in JoJo's Bizarre Adventure: Part 4,
and it'll all work out fine.
Right, Eita-kun?
Don't ask me.
Is JoJo's some sort of BBQ place?
You don't know JoJo's Bizarre Adventure?!
I don't...
Now I see why you aren't popular.
Hey!
It's because you're a Peking Man who's never heard of JoJo!
I'm Japanese!
If you really want me to believe that, read all of JoJo first.
At the very least, read Part 4. That's volumes 29 to 47.
We can talk about your popularity after.
I have to read that much?!
Come, let's flesh out the details of how we're going to get this guy.
Sakagami's brother hasn't left yet...
H-Hey there, Ei-kun.
H-Hey, Chiwa.
Got another gig today?
Oh man, this isn't gonna work.
Chiwawa-chan, you play guitar?
Are you in a band?
N-No, I just play it solo in front of the station sometimes.
Cool!
So you're like one of those street performers?
What type of music do you listen to?
Uh...
Chili Peppers.
Who?
You've never heard of the Red Hot Chili Peppers?
They're a really famous band.
Right, Harusaki-san?
Are we talking food?
If you're a fan of theirs, I bet you've got a Strat.
Frusciante's totally awesome.
Whose stand is that?
She's so confused!
Ah, the clouds are stained red as blood.
Ragnarok must be drawing near.
You're acting like this has nothing to do with you?
You're awful!
Hey, can we see your guitar?
N-No! My guitar is part of me!
It isn't something I can show to just anyone!
Come on! Play something for us!
My brother's got a collection of old guitars.
Sakagami's brother enters the fray!
His room is full of them.
You two might get along pretty well.
I'd like to hear you play, too.
I need this cane to get home.
Yeah!
She's done for!
Fine... I'll show you guys!
Dora!
Dora! Dora! Dora!
Rock and roll! Thank you!
I love you guys!
Okay, later!
I've never seen someone so cruel.
Oh, you two sure took your time.
You were way too rough on your body back there.
You shouldn't have swung that huge case around like that.
Really? I don't think you have to worry so much.
They said that if the pain starts up again,
there's no telling what might happen, right?
Sorry.
I got carried away.
Man...
Anyway, I bet they got a kick out of that, at least.
W-Well, if your goal was to get them to remember you,
then you succeeded, all right.
They might remember her name, but it won't be associated with anything good.
The opposite of love isn't hate, but rather, disinterest.
The path to dating starts from making someone take an interest in you.
Then tell me something, Natsukawa.
What part of Ei-kun interested you?
Why are you dating him?
My panties...
Eita-kun saw my... panties.
Ei-kun?
Come on, stop making things up!
A maiden had her underwear seen,
and when that happens,
she has no choice but to offer herself to that person for the rest of her life.
That's not what happened, Chiwa!
The wind blew her skirt up!
So that's what happened... I see...
I saw nothing! She had nothing on!
The panties that should've been there weren't!
Now, it's possible that they had bunched up or something, but...
Hane High! Fight! Fight! Fight! Hane—
It may be quite effective to show your panties, actually.
You could even do a little acting and say, "Oh no, you saw them!"
Society Advocating Maidenly Elegance For All Girls
Then they won't know it was intentional.
I'm not going to act like a slut!
It's not happening!
What's wrong? Not confident in your choice of underwear?
What is it, Ei-kun?!
N-Nothing.
Shut up!
Did you see?
I don't know...
Then maybe I should pull it a little higher...
Stop! I won't see any panties under there!
What is it?! Why are you two staring into each other's eyes?!
N-No special reason.
That's right.
It's only natural for two people who love each other to stare into each other's eyes.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Quit messing around!
Society Advocating Maidenly Elegance For All Girls
You know you liked it.
Sure, but—no, I didn't!
Chiwa was in the room!
Why would you pull a stunt like that?!
You're an honor student with the best grades in our year,
but your childhood friend has you under her thumb.
Would you mind if I asked you the same question that Harusaki-san asked?
What question?
Why are you always with Harusaki-san?
Because we're childhood friends.
Then why is Harusaki-san, out of all the friends you made as a child,
the only one you still spend time with?
Because we're neighbors...
After what happened in the classroom,
I thought Harusaki-san might quit our club,
but she was already here in the clubroom,
calmly drinking tea,
showing no signs of feeling dejected whatsoever.
Oh, that?
I don't know how dejected Chiwa felt,
but I do know Chiwa won't quit this club just like that.
At least not until she's achieved her goal.
Why's that?
She was the star of the kendo team during our last year of middle school, but during the summer,
she got into an accident.
Her lower back was severely damaged.
She underwent major surgery and rehabilitation,
and recovered to the point where the injury doesn't affect her everyday life,
but she'll never be able to participate in any kendo matches again.
She lost the goal she once had.
But now she's found something she can pour her heart into again.
That's why she won't quit.
That answered my question.
Huh?
I now understand why your friendship with Harusaki-san is still ongoing.
But don't forget...
What?
Don't forget, Eita-kun.
You're my boyfriend now.
Aren't I just a fake?
You are.
But that doesn't change the fact that you're mine.
So...
don't pay attention to any other girls when you're with me.
Just... Just how far are you going to take this thing?
All the way.
It's all a lie.
mirai he to futari no Wonder tale
Unfolding into the future, a wonderful tale about us
senaka ni sasayakitai no
I want to whisper to you,
mune no naka sotto misete
Secretly show me what's in your heart
hontou wa ienai kikenai kara
But because I can't say it, I can't ask you,
ijiwaru shitakunaru
I just have to pick on you
konna hazu ja nai
It wasn't supposed to be this way,
watashi no kokoro ga
But my heart just can't help but sing,
shiranai tokimeki mo utaidasu
Skipping beats that it never knew could be,
girigiri no atsusa de
With a passion, about to explode
mirai he to futari no Wonder tale
Unfolding into the future, a wonderful tale about us
hajimari ga kowai no ni tomaranai
I'm afraid that it might start, but I can't stop it
kimi no hitomi ga watashi no tame ni
I wonder why I want your eyes
kagayaite hoshii no wa naze kashira
To start shining for me
koi na no oshiete yo
Is this love? Can't you tell me?
Next Episode
The popucute item for next week is...
Yup, homemade Salisbury steak!
Use the illusions of warmth and love associated with homemade food to brainwash him!
A Childhood Friend's Tears and a War Zone
Isn't homemade food scary?