I wish I wasn't your childhood friend!
We should have met as normal classmates!
Being your childhood friend sucks so much!
Chiwa!
isse-no
One, two, three
okaeri
Welcome back
saa dekakeyou
Now, let's go out
nukegake rendezvous
I'm stealing you for a rendezvous
kizuna ga daiji
Friends are important
koibito ga daiichi
But a girlfriend is the most
Girlish Lover
kono itami kimi no sei
This pain I feel is your fault
mune no tokimeki uso no tsumori
This feeling in my chest is supposed to be a lie
ima made no position wo
What would happen if tomorrow
koeta ashita wa dou naru no
I tried being more than what I am to you now?
nee motto issho shiyou
Hey, let's spend more time together
dame
Can't we?
dame watashi dake
You can't, he's mine
yudan mo suki mo nai
You can never be too careful with me
kimi to no border koetai
I want to jump the border between us
sou motto
Now, I'll be
daitan de chotto gouin
A bit bolder, maybe even aggressive
suki wo misetai
I want to show you my love
yasashii kimi mo
I want you when you're nice
ijiwaru na kimi mo
I want you when you're mean
hitorijime
You're all mine
kitsui tte
Too much for you?
yappa yamete
You really want to stop?
urahara fall in love
It's the wrong way to fall in love
tomodachi ijou
I'm more than just your friend,
honmono miman no
But less than a real
Girlish Lover
A Man's Struggle Is a War Zone
What the heck's wrong with that Chiwa?
Crap! I overslept!
What the heck's wrong with me?
Good morning.
M-Masuzu?!
No need to act so surprised, Eita-kun.
Are you here to check up on Chiwa's date too?
Perish the thought.
I'm here as the president of SAMEFAG.
I want to see my brave club member in action.
We see them meet up, and that's it.
I'm going to the library to study after this.
Of course. That's fine.
I don't need to pretend to be your boyfriend right now, do I?!
Of course you do.
You'll be pretending to be my boyfriend at all times.
Chiwa... Chiwa's actually wearing something nice?
Do you like it? I chose it for her.
You did?
So you can be nice sometimes.
Yes, those clothes I wore back in sixth grade fit her perfectly.
Those clothes I wore back in sixth grade fit her perfectly.
I heard you the first time.
He's late for their first date?
Isn't the guy supposed to
show up early for these things?
Yeah...
No New Messages
Sorry I'm late.
What am I gonna do with you?
The train was late.
Chiwa...
Come on, Chiwa, just go home already.
Told you she'd wait till eleven.
I win.
Huh?
Sakagami-senpai?
Damn, I can't believe you waited. Can't you take a hint?
Look at what she's wearing.
Like, she's trying so hard to be what she's not.
So what? Isn't that cute?
She really thought she could get a date with Sakagami-kun.
What's going on?
Take it.
Thank you.
Anyway, you can get lost now, Chiwawa-chan.
Hate to break it to you, but this was all just a prank.
You really thought I'd go out with you?
You never had a chance.
Hope you learned your lesson, poor, little Chiwawa-chan.
But damn, she's tiny.
You sure she's not in elementary school?
I know a guy from middle school who's into little girls.
Want me to hook you two up?
Come on, leave her alone. I'm feeling bad for her.
She's shaking.
Sakagami acts like a charming, personable athelete at school,
but now you see his true colors.
He's always two- or three-timing.
When he gets bored of one girl,
he finds another, and it all repeats.
You knew this would happen!
Stop.
Let go of me!
Matters of love are inconsequential to us.
Soon, Harusaki-san will understand too.
Just how pointless love really is.
She may even become anti-love, just like you and me.
I... won't be able to do kendo anymore.
Cut it out!
Are you telling me our club was all one big act?
Weren't you having fun?!
There's a reason why it's called SAMEFAG.
Everything I say is a lie.
Fabrications without a shred of truth.
What?!
You said so yourself.
I'm...
a bitch.
Quit acting all twisted, Natsukawa Masuzu!
B-But you're just like me, aren't you?
That's right. We're the same. I'm twisted too.
And I'll always be your partner in crime!
But...
But that doesn't mean you can force others to feel as hopeless as we do!
Chiwa isn't like us.
I'll be back.
Hey...
Don't leave me.
I don't want...
to be alone anymore.
Silly.
Keep your chin up.
If you don't, you won't see your boyfriend saving the day.
You really don't get it.
Get away from Chiwa!
Ei-kun?
Who the hell're you?
Chiwawa here's childhood friend. Got a problem with that?
Yeah? And what do you want, Mr. Childhood Friend—
They've returned.
They've returned to me!
My memories from my previous life!
What?
My true name is Burning Fighting Fighter.
My true power is that of a ZZZ-rank,
dwarfing even the elite S-rank demons,
but I'm not giving it my all yet, so I'm still at D!
If I released my true power,
I could destroy countless parallel universes with just one hand.
Wyverns! You thought you could conceal your presences with Illumination,
but you cannot fool my crest!
No matter where you hide,
this pain shall realitize your real forms!
This guy got a screw loose or something?
Dragoon Secret Technique:
Violent Hawk Stance!
Taste my ultimate attack: Fate Dark Black Flame!
Something's wrong with this guy.
He's nuts. Just look at his eyes.
What a freak.
Hey, let's get out of here.
This guy isn't worth the trouble.
He might infect us with his crazy.
Yeah.
Fool! Turning your back on me...
has left you wide open!
Apologize!
What are you doing?!
Apologize now!
Getting a little cocky, aren't we?!
Apologize.
Apologize to Chiwa!
What?
You think you're in a position to boss me around?
Apologize for leading her on!
You're so damn annoying. Shut the hell up!
And get your hands off him already.
We're kicking your ass till the cops show.
Ei-kun...
Not so cocky now, are ya?
Where's your burning whatever now?
The fuck?! He bit me!
She's watching...
She's... She's watching me!
She...
She?
You look so lame right now.
What're you standing for?
How 'bout a little nap!
How do you like that?!
That's enough, Ei-kun!
You don't have to fight those creeps!
Who're you calling a creep?
Chiwa!
Stop!
Huh?
And what're you gonna do with that?
Men!
You bitch!
Dou!
Dora!
Kote! Men!
Dou!
Looks like you've still got it, Chiwa.
Fucking kid!
Men!
Kote!
Dou!
I'm sorry.
I was lying to you too.
Huh?
I don't like you, not even a little bit!
I got into a fight with my stupidly dense childhood friend
and said that I'd get a boyfriend on the spur of the moment, so I just picked someone at random!
So, can we just act like none of this ever happened?
Y-Yeah, sure.
I don't want to see you guys ever again.
Thanks! I feel the same way!
L-Let's go!
W-Wait!
Ow...
You're heavy!
Look at you.
Yo.
The blood's practically squirting from your nose, Ei-kun.
You know how you yelled that "she" was watching?
D-Did I really?
You sure did.
I heard you loud and clear with my own two ears.
Natsukawa didn't come here with you, right?
Y-Yeah.
Then does that mean you were talking about me?
O-Of course not!
Ei-kun, hang in there!
Ei-kun!
Ei-kun, are you okay?
Ei-kun?
Way to go, Eita.
You've certainly made a name for yourself.
It's like I became a celebrity overnight.
Well, you did make a huge scene in front of the station.
But thanks to you, it looks like the whole school knows the truth about Sakagami-senpai now.
I'm sure Chiwawa-chan's happy about it too.
She said the old, stupid Ei-kun she knew in middle school was back.
It's not like I'm the same guy I was in middle school, though.
Natsukawa-san's absent today.
I bet she's upset.
Why?
Because you left her behind to go be
another girl's knight in shining armor yesterday.
I wasn't trying to be anyone's knight in shining armor.
...don't pay attention to any other girls when you're with me.
Park
Here
Hane River
Her house and mine are in
completely opposite directions.
We went towards my house whenever we walked home. Was that for me?
I will hug you very tight!
That will be your punishment, okay?
Y-You look just fine.
I am. Thanks for noticing.
You're the one who threw that pole yesterday, aren't you?
Thanks.
I just did what any girlfriend would.
So, why did you skip school today?
I played the part of a sick Natsukawa Masuzu.
Meaning, you played hookie?
No, it was a club activity.
Then, are we going to keep SAMEFAG going?
I intend to.
You and I, who both abhor love, will try to think of ways
for people who still believe in love to become insanely popular.
Doesn't it sound exciting?
We can remove Harusaki-san's
brainwashing after we're done.
You haven't given up yet?
Well, I am twisted.
What? You're still holding what I said yesterday against me?
Not really.
Sounds good to me, anyway.
I'll hang around until Chiwa stops causing problems.
She did get rejected in the end.
She'll keep coming to the club.
You seem to know everything about Harusaki-san.
We are childhood friends, after all.
You haven't kissed Harusaki-san yet, have you?
O-Of course not!
Then remember this:
Your first wasn't Harusaki Chiwa. It was me, Natsukawa Masuzu.
So, what do you think?
You're as bold as ever.
That's not what I meant.
Are you okay with this?
With what?
Well, the person you kissed was a fake.
You really are dense.
It had to be you.
Rumble
That was one of the best scenes from JoJo Part 1.
A parody of when Dio steals a kiss from Erina.
Rumble
I could only enjoy it with a fellow JoJo fan as yourself.
That was supposed to be a parody?
I thought you'd realize what was going on right away.
Now...
Hurry up and wash your mouth out with dirty water.
Like I'd act out that part of the scene!
Sorry!
Wh-Why are you here?!
I texted you last night!
I said that my shower was broken,
so I was coming over in the morning to use yours!
Huh? You did?
You didn't even read it?!
Sorry. My bad.
Are you really sorry?
Yeah, it's all my fault.
Then, do me a favor to make it up to me.
Huh?
Let's walk to school together again.
Okay.
Really?!
Then let's start today!
I'll get dressed in a minute!
Gotcha.
I'm definitely not letting Natsukawa have you.
Eek! You pervert!
Wh-Why are you here?!
To make breakfast for my boyfriend, in an apron.
Would you expect anything less from a maiden playing the part of a girlfriend?
I texted you.
I told you I'd be here this morning.
So you texted me too.
How'd you even get inside?
I came in through the front door.
I thought you left it open for me.
Must have been Chiwa.
What's the matter?
Wait, did you want to see me in nothing but an apron?
No!
Fine...
Where's the hair dryer?
Who was that?
M-My aunt, Saeko-san!
Well, since I'm already here, perhaps I should introduce myself.
No!
Stay here.
I don't care if a new Stand user appears. Stay put.
Chiwa, I'm coming in.
Okay.
Here.
Why are you covered in sweat?
A new Stand user appeared.
I was thinking of changing my hairstyle. What do you think?
N-No, I think it's fine as it is—
Which of these buttons is the reheat setting?
Was that Saeko-san?
She always gets home in the morning.
I'll go say hello. I haven't seen her in a while.
Wait! Saeko-san doesn't
feel well and she's pretty tired.
Let her sleep for today.
Oh. I'll use the hair dryer as quietly as I can, then.
Thanks.
You're sweating bullets.
I... I just saved all of mankind.
I can't find the reheat setting on the microwave.
Hey, the hair dryer's broken!
Hold on, I'll be right there!
Eita-kun.
Ei-kun!
Eita-kun?
Ei-kun?
Hey!
Oh?
What are you doing here, Natsukawa?!
I should be asking you the same question, Harusaki-san.
It's... a war zone.
mirai he to futari no Wonder tale
Unfolding into the future, a wonderful tale about us
senaka ni sasayakitai no
I want to whisper to you,
mune no naka sotto misete
Secretly show me what's in your heart
hontou wa ienai kikenai kara
But because I can't say it, I can't ask you,
ijiwaru shitakunaru
I just have to pick on you
konna hazu ja nai
It wasn't supposed to be this way,
watashi no kokoro ga
But my heart just can't help but sing,
shiranai tokimeki mo utaidasu
Skipping beats that it never knew could be,
girigiri no atsusa de
With a passion, about to explode
mirai he to futari no Wonder tale
Unfolding into the future, a wonderful tale about us
hajimari ga kowai no ni tomaranai
I'm afraid that it might start, but I can't stop it
kimi no hitomi ga watashi no tame ni
I wonder why I want your eyes
kagayaite hoshii no wa naze kashira
To start shining for me
koi na no oshiete yo
Is this love? Can't you tell me?
Next Episode
The popucute item for next week is...
the Hebrew language.
If you use this language, memories of his previous life shall return to him,
and the flames of his love for you shall reignite.
The Truth Behind a Love Letter Creates a War Zone
Retend to the love which once bore fruit, even in your present life.