Perhaps...
we should fight against something.
Huh?
But meowhy? Do we have a reason to?
Who are we supposed to fight, anyway?
Our parents? Our teachers?
A gang of hoodlums?
Not very sharp, are you, Eita-kun?
If you're going to fight anything,
it should be supernatural or extraterrestrial.
Don't humans shine brightest when fighting against such mysterious opponents?
And why do we need to shine?
To become insanely popular.
An excerpt from the Book of
Promised Victory, Chapter 47:
"The True Me."
Stop!
"My true name is Burning Fighting Fighter."
"My true power is that of a ZZZ-rank,
dwarfing even the elite S-rank demons,
but I'm not giving it my all yet, so I'm still at D."
"I was a dragon in my previous life."
"I was the last of the Dragoons, and prince of the planet Valhalla."
"After my defeat in the Thousand Wars at the hands of the Wyverns,
I was reincarnated on this planet."
"The Wyverns detected my reincarnation."
"They have opened a gate to this planet to search for me."
"With the power of Illumination, they hide their presences and move about freely."
Destroy
"However, they cannot escape my eyes."
"The crest in mine right hand throbs when they are near, alerting me to their approach."
Destroy
Kill
"I will use my special finishing move, the Fate Dark Black Flame, to destroy them!"
Destroy
Kill
"I will collect the Seven Dragons that fell to this planet,
Destroy
Kill
and restore my home planet to its former glory!"
Destroy
Kill
No!
isse-no
One, two, three
okaeri
Welcome back
saa dekakeyou
Now, let's go out
nukegake rendezvous
I'm stealing you for a rendezvous
kizuna ga daiji
Friends are important
koibito ga daiichi
But a girlfriend is the most
Girlish Lover
kono itami kimi no sei
This pain I feel is your fault
mune no tokimeki uso no tsumori
This feeling in my chest is supposed to be a lie
ima made no position wo
What would happen if tomorrow
koeta ashita wa dou naru no
I tried being more than what I am to you now?
nee motto issho shiyou
Hey, let's spend more time together
dame
Can't we?
dame watashi dake
You can't, he's mine
yudan mo suki mo nai
You can never be too careful with me
kimi to no border koetai
I want to jump the border between us
sou motto
Now, I'll be
daitan de chotto gouin
A bit bolder, maybe even aggressive
suki wo misetai
I want to show you my love
yasashii kimi mo
I want you when you're nice
ijiwaru na kimi mo
I want you when you're mean
hitorijime
You're all mine
kitsui tte
Too much for you?
yappa yamete
You really want to stop?
urahara fall in love
It's the wrong way to fall in love
tomodachi ijou
I'm more than just your friend,
honmono miman no
But less than a real
Girlish Lover
Now we know who you need to fight, Harusaki-san.
A Childhood Friend's Tears and a War Zone
Huh?
You need to fight your enemies from your previous life!
My previous life?
Don't you remember it?
I was a princess in a foreign land?
I see. Most people were born into nobility in their past lives.
I lived in a white castle,
loved by all of my loyal subjects.
And then, one day, a prince rode in
on a Kobe cow and proposed to me.
He said, "Be my queen, and you shall eat the highest-quality meat for the rest of your days!"
Take this seriously!
A past life needs to be more than just flowery, sappy stuff!
You need strife and conflict!
You need drama that forces you to escape to your present life!
What the hell do you think a past life is?!
Your identity as a princess was fake!
An illusion! Just a front!
You were a legendary princess-warrior who, in the shadows, battled the Outer Gods!
You were a Newtype that the military placed under house arrest
and kept a mobile suit hidden under her castle! Something like that!
Uh... I mean...
Crap! My eighth-grade blood started boiling!
You're exactly right, Eita-kun.
Huh?
Drama is a necessity when it comes to past lives.
You'll be a warrior, fighting in the shadows to settle a score from her previous life.
That will make you popular. I guarantee it!
I'm not so sure... But Ei-kun agreed, so I'll give it a chance.
So, who do I have to fight?
Well, I'm not really sure who...
It's not like I was really fighting the Wyverns.
It's all right. You don't actually have to fight anyone.
You just have to pretend.
Pretend you're fighting someone.
It's not the fight scenes that make battle manga interesting.
It's the drama leading up to those scenes.
It's the exchanges between people that give them life.
I will write a script.
All you have to do is act it out, Harusaki-san.
Eita-kun, you'll be a supporting character.
Huh? O-Okay...
Will this really make me super popular?
Of course.
My first love's notebook is never wrong.
I'll give you the script tomorrow.
You'll be acting it out three days from now.
Got it?
Got it!
They really get along, don't they?
Gaia cries for fear!
Do you feel it, Ei-kun?
Do you feel that foreboding spirit energy thirteen kilometers to the south?
Its power level has to be over a million!
N-No, I don't feel it!
I do.
Two large spirit energies,
and two even larger spirit energies!
One small spirit energy.
W-Wait, this last spirit energy is fading! Could it be...
What's wrong, Chiwa?!
This spirit energy belongs to my best friend from my previous life,
with whom I had strong ties.
You've recovered those memories?!
It all came back to me last night as I was cleaning mold off the bathroom floor.
I must go.
If you go now, you'll be killed!
There comes a time when
every warrior must fighet... I mean, fight.
I must fight. The pride of my warrior race is at stake! And who says I'll lose?
Just take a look at my power level!
Her power level is at 10,000...
12,000... Unbelievable! It's still rising!
Has the power she had in
her previous life returned to her?!
Pew-pew! This is my true power!
Pow! Pow!
That's amazing, Chiwa!
Indeed, but my power level can rise even higher in bursts. Pew!
Amazing! You're so cool! Let's get married!
Try to hold out until I return for you!
Fwoosh!
Don't die, Chiwa.
That was great!
That was a great performance, Kidou-kun!
I never knew you did stuff like this!
H-Huh? Really?
So, what's the title of the sketch you did just now?
Huh? Sketch?
Yeah, are you going to perform the rest on stage somewhere?
I really wanna see it again!
Yeah!
A sketch, huh?
A sketch...
They're calling the script I poured my heart into...
a sketch.
The time has come!
Yes, the time is now!
Oh, it's finally time for you to get over what happened?
That's not what I meant!
Then, meowhat?
I obviously meant that it's time for
Harusaki-san to ask Sakagami-senpai out.
What?!
Huh?
Thanks to our two attempts to attract his attention,
I'm sure his love points have risen quite high.
According to my calculations, I believe he's entered
a state of complete love, blushing whenever he thinks of you.
Don't you think we're jumping the gun?
They just called that performance a sketch.
A sketch?
They called the performance I poured my heart into... a sketch.
It's fine. I hear Sakagami-senpai's a big comedy fan.
I'm sure he would've loved to see the guitar thing and the past life thing for himself.
Slow down.
People may have liked our sketch,
but that doesn't mean it's gonna make him fall in love.
You have a point.
Okay, let's put together another plan for a final push and—
Wait.
I'll try it.
I'm gonna ask him out.
Y-You serious?
If he says no, then he says no.
I'll just give it a shot.
You almost sound like you
want him to turn you down.
Th-That's not true.
How are you going to ask him out?
How about using the traditional method of putting a love letter in his shoe locker?
Okay.
What is it?
Chiwa, are you sure about this?
Asking him out, I mean.
Are you sure you want to do it now?
I'm sure.
All right.
Good luck.
If you get the okay, we'll celebrate with all the stuff you like.
We'll celebrate, huh?
Hey.
Saka...
Sakagami-senpai.
Sure.
Huh?
I've always thought you were kind of cute.
Seriously?! Is he being serious here?!
I heard you play the guitar.
A little, I guess.
I also heard that you're fighting
a monstrous enemy in the shadows.
I-I've already sealed them all away, so not anymore.
I like girls with a mysterious side.
So, how about this Sunday?
Sunday?
Yeah. Let's see a movie together this Sunday.
What do you say, Chiwawa-chan?
Sure...
An epic win!
Our first victory was an epic win.
As president of the Society Advocating Maidenly Elegance For All Girls,
I couldn't be happier.
You're the president?
It doesn't really matter.
Anyway, this shows just how attractive Harusaki-san is.
It also goes to show how reliable my first love's notebook is.
You should be happy too, Eita-kun.
Th-This has nothing to do with me!
Yeah...
I think the guy who wrote that notebook is pretty amazing.
What? How is a guy who wrote
all that delusional crap amazing?
Guitars and past lives? How're they supposed to be cool?
If you ask me, there's nothing cool about them.
Maybe, but...
I think it's pretty cool that he wholeheartedly believed in all of that without fear or hesitation.
You can't be serious.
How is that cool?
It's a stain on my past.
But you can't relax yet, Harusaki-san.
The battle really begins with your date on Sunday.
Yeah.
Thanks, Natsukawa.
You don't seem all that happy about it.
Huh?
That's not true!
Hey, Chiwa!
Ei-kun?
Dinner's ready.
Oh... Okay.
We've got beef and garlic stir-fry and Szechuan chicken salad.
Salisbury steak, too.
All the things you love.
We're celebrating your success.
I told you yesterday, right?
Yeah... I remember.
You got yourself a popular, good-looking, older guy.
You're the epitome of popular!
Why... Why are we celebrating?
Once word gets around school, all the girls are going to wish they were you.
The guys'll see you in a new light.
But all the girls who like him might hate you for it.
They might even start bullying you.
I'm sure you'll be fine, though.
You could just beat them up.
I... I...
Chiwa?
Are you okay with it?
Are you really okay with me dating him?
What? Isn't that why we made the club and did all that stuff?
You poured your heart into it, didn't you?
Yeah, I did. I poured my heart into it.
And now that's paid off, so—
It hasn't paid off!
Stupid...
Stupid!
You're so stupid, Ei-kun!
Chiwa...
I wish I wasn't your childhood friend!
We should have met as normal classmates!
Being your childhood friend sucks so much!
You wish we weren't childhood friends?
We've been together since first grade!
You're like a little sister to me!
No! I'm three months and ten days older than you!
Fine, a big sister. My point is, you're like family to me!
That...
That's what I don't like!
D-Don't cry!
Stupid!
Chiwa!
What the hell...
Hey, Ei-kun!
Chiwa?!
I'm back.
But you shouldn't be!
You're supposed to still be in the hospital!
Can you walk all right?
Yeah. I decided to come by to get some practice walking.
I really missed the smell of your house!
You really do whatever you please, don't you?
Well, at least it looks like you're recovering smoothly.
They're going to take my cast off next month.
That's when they'll start me on some real physical therapy.
They said I'll be able to walk again without
any problems by the end of the year.
So Kendo Master Chiwawa should be back in action when we start high school.
I... won't be able to do kendo anymore.
They told me I can't do any strenuous activity.
Something's wrong with some bone in my hip.
So the doctor told me to quit kendo.
That can't be true.
The doctor must be an idiot.
They say he's the best doctor in the city.
But I'll be okay. What about you?
What are you going to do?
You heard what happened?
Yeah, my mom told me today.
It's such a ridiculous story.
Both my parents cheated on each other,
ditched their son in his last year of middle school,
and faded into the woodwork.
What are you going to do?
I have an aunt who might look after me,
but I'm not holding out much hope.
None of my other relatives want to take me in.
I might just have to live on my own.
You're not going to move away, are you?
Did you sneak out of the hospital just to...
You won't go anywhere, right, Ei-kun?
Do you even need to ask?
I don't have anywhere to go! This is the only place for me!
I knew it.
I knew you wouldn't.
Oh, hey.
You haven't eaten yet, have you?
I'll make you something.
Let's eat together.
Why is the Salisbury steak all green?
I figured I'd add some green peas into the mix.
This isn't even Salisbury steak anymore.
Just watch. If I put my mind to it, cooking'll be a piece of cake.
Okay, then. I'll look forward to the day you make me a good Salisbury steak.
Cheers!
When we start high school, I'm going to find something more fun to do than kendo.
Something that I'll love even more.
Yeah, go for it.
How about you, Ei-kun?
Do you have something you want to do in high school?
Me? Nothing really.
It's fine. I'm not all that smart or athletic.
Setting goals for myself sounds
like more trouble than it's worth.
The only things I really love doing are watching anime, reading manga,
and writing out fantasies and daydreams in my notebook.
Fantasies and daydreams don't do anything for you in real life.
But if I was smarter, I'd try to be a doctor.
A doctor?
Maybe I'd even be able to fix your hip.
Just kidding.
Hang on a sec...
Yeah.
Wh-Why are you crying?
Stupid!
It's because of what you said!
Ei-kun, you're so stupid!
What can I do for her?
All right. I've got it.
I'm going to be a doctor!
I'll study as hard as I can and become the top student at Hane High!
I'll get into the best medical program!
But all you get are C's.
I-I'll start applying myself in high school!
With the right grades and qualifications, it'll be a cinch, even without my parents.
I'll fix your hip!
Really?
Yeah, really!
Medical science advances really fast!
They'll make great strides by the time we're adults!
No, I'll be the one to make those strides!
Thank you, Ei-kun.
I'll...
I'll wait for you, no matter how long it takes.
I'd advance medical science?
I can't believe how stupid I was.
Stupid Ei-kun...
You're stupid...
aren't you, Eita-kun?
mirai he to futari no Wonder tale
Unfolding into the future, a wonderful tale about us
senaka ni sasayakitai no
I want to whisper to you,
mune no naka sotto misete
Secretly show me what's in your heart
hontou wa ienai kikenai kara
But because I can't say it, I can't ask you,
ijiwaru shitakunaru
I just have to pick on you
konna hazu ja nai
It wasn't supposed to be this way,
watashi no kokoro ga
But my heart just can't help but sing,
shiranai tokimeki mo utaidasu
Skipping beats that it never knew could be,
girigiri no atsusa de
With a passion, about to explode
mirai he to futari no Wonder tale
Unfolding into the future, a wonderful tale about us
hajimari ga kowai no ni tomaranai
I'm afraid that it might start, but I can't stop it
kimi no hitomi ga watashi no tame ni
I wonder why I want your eyes
kagayaite hoshii no wa naze kashira
To start shining for me
koi na no oshiete yo
Is this love? Can't you tell me?
Next Episode
The popucute item for next week is...
a traffic pole!
One wave, and you'll feel like a precocious little magical girl!
You could even fly straight to the guy you like!
A Man's Struggle Is a War Zone
Popucute, popucute, pop-u-cute!