The Start of a New World Order!
All right, let's get this meeting started!
Who put you in charge?
It's all thanks to me that you managed to avoid being shut down by the skin of your teeth.
And it's all thanks to you that we were in that predicament in the first place!
I have a name, you know.
The Start of a New World Order!
Call me Ai, you pitiful Chiwawa.
It's "Chiwa," written "thousand" and "calm"!
Call me Chiwa! Chiwa, Chiwa, Chiwa!
Love Cloth!
Who are you calling Love Cloth, Thousand Japan?!
Japan?!
Chiwawa, don't raise your voice at Master.
I'm sure that she will guide us on the path to popularity.
You seem to have great potential, Akishino-san.
Please, call me Hime.
Okay, Hime-chan.
I'll guide you on the path to being a prim and proper maiden.
I'm so happy, Master!
Pet, pet.
What the hell?
I agree. I believe that Fuyuumi-san will be an excellent coach.
She has a rich and handsome boyfriend, after all.
Th-That's right!
I have way more feminine appeal and experience than any of you!
Then maybe you can show us...
how to ask a guy you like out!
Don't look at me.
I want to know too.
How to convey my feelings.
I told you, don't look at me.
Stop right there! You're
already doing it wrong!
You don't ask a guy out!
You make the guy ask you out!
Oh!
Then, Eita-kun,
perhaps you could ask Fuyuumi-san out right now?
What?!
We'll have Fuyuumi-san act out how one should properly react when being asked out.
W-With Kidou-kun?
You can't be serious!
I should have a say
in who's gonna do it!
Then again, I am the coach,
so I guess it has to be me.
I'll do it, but only reluctantly.
Reluctantly, got that? Re-luc-tant-ly!
All right, Kidou-kun! Bring it!
isse-no
One, two, three
okaeri
Welcome back
saa dekakeyou
Now, let's go out
nukegake rendezvous
I'm stealing you for a rendezvous
kizuna ga daiji
Friends are important
koibito ga daiji
But a girlfriend is the most
Girlish Lover
kono itami kimi no sei
This pain I feel is your fault
mune no tokimeki uso no tsumori
This feeling in my chest is supposed to be a lie
ima made no position wo
What would happen if tomorrow
koeta ashita wa dou naru no
I tried being more than what I am to you now?
nee motto issho shiyo
Hey, let's spend more time together
dame
Can't we?
dame watashi dake
You can't, he's mine
yudan mo suki mo nai
You can never be too careful with me
kimi to no border koetai
I want to jump the border between us
sou motto
Now, I'll be
daitan de chotto gouin
A bit bolder, maybe even aggressive
suki wo misetai
I want to show you all my love
yasashii kimi mo
I want you when you're nice
ijiwaru na kimi mo
I want you when you're mean
hitorijime
You're all mine
kidzuite
Please realize
yappa yamete
Never mind, just stop
urahara fall in love
It's the wrong way to fall in love
tomodachi ijou
I'm more than just your friend,
honmono miman no
But less than a real
Girlish lover
Truth is, I've loved you this whole time.
A Meeting About a Summer Trip Turns into a War Zone
I knew that.
I love you. Please go out with me.
Sorry, but I've never thought of you as a man.
Let's stay friends.
Okay. I give up.
You can't give up!
Huh?
You have to explode
with love and desire for me!
What?!
If you give up, your chance at love is over!
But I'm just going to get
shot down at this rate.
Well, duh!
I'm not going to just fall
into your arms that easily.
What a pain in the ass.
I guess it's time to consult this.
What's that?
It's the diary that my first love left behind.
Inside are secrets on how to become popular with the opposite sex.
How-to-be-popular notes?
Sounds good.
Try some of the "100% Pure Awesome from Concentrate Pick-up Lines."
No way in hell! Why don't you do it, you freaking bitch?!
Fuyuumi-san, allow me to correct myself.
You see, this notebook is actually Eita-kun's—
I'll do it!
I'll do it, Masuzu-san!
Wh-What is it?
"I'm sorry, but you're going to be falling for me."
As if! Trying to seduce me
by force won't work.
"Were you aware that I'm so popular that I'm a social phenomenon?"
You idiot! You're not making any sense!
"Watch yourself."
"They call my kiss the 'Wind Slash.'"
Th-That's not true.
You're lying. You have to be...
Now!
"Wind Slash! Wind Slash! Wind Slash!"
"Wind Slash!"
Hane High!
Fight! Fight! Fight!
Hane—
I-It didn't work?!
If... If you're that serious...
I'll go out with you!
Yes!
With that, Takkun and I are now a couple!
Ai-chan, epic win!
How does that even work?
I'm not really following here.
Master, are you betraying us?
Are you betraying us?
You see, Ai-chan wuvs Takkun!
We're gonna get married after we graduate!
I want three kids!
H-Hey, calm down, A-chan.
Get a grip! You're a hall monitor, remember?
Anyway, I'm done pretending to be seduced.
Pretending?
So you're saying you weren't really seduced?
Of course not.
Why would I fall for him?
Kidou-kun's small fry!
Eita-kun, do it again.
"Wind Slash."
I wuv you, Takkun!
Get your hands off him!
What are you doing?!
You could've hurt someone!
You were all over Ei-kun!
What, so I can't touch him?
Do I need your permission or something?
You do!
Because I'm his childhood friend!
Pain, pain, go away.
Well, I'm his childhood friend too!
What?
I first met Kidou-kun in our last year of kindergarten. We were in star class.
I called him Takkun, and he called me A-chan.
Back in kindergarten would be...
Ten years ago.
You met him, when? Nine years ago?
Hey, Ei-kun...
Is this true?
Why didn't you tell me?
I'd forgotten.
I didn't remember about it until recently.
You've known her longer?
You met her first?
Yeah.
But...
I met Eita first.
Past lives come before elementary school and kindergarten.
I'm his ex-girlfriend, and I met him first.
Past life?! Ex-girlfriend?!
What are you talking about?!
Eita and I were lovers in a past life.
That makes me his ex-girlfriend.
What?!
We've gotten way off topic.
Let's get back to the issue at hand.
The Society Advocating Maidenly Elegance For All Girls
has five members now that Fuyuumi Ai-san has joined.
We've risen in status from a simple gathering to an official club.
Now that we're an official club, why don't we discuss our plans for the summer?
Our Summer Trip
That's a great idea!
So where are we going?
The beach? The mountains?
I've got summer classes, so...
We're on break for those starting tomorrow.
I want the beach!
I've never been to one before!
I want to go!
You've never been to the beach before?
In my present life, my family runs a bed and breakfast.
We are very busy during the summer.
So they won't take me.
Then this trip will be your maiden voyage.
That doesn't mean what you think it does.
We'll need swimsuits if we're going to the beach.
Swimsuits?
What kind? What kind?
Wanna go shopping for some tomorrow?
I'll help you pick one out.
I'm going to the bathroom.
If Master is going, I'll go too.
Okay, then we're going!
I wonder what I should get.
Jealous Chiwawa...
Ei-kun?
What's wrong?
You're looking kind of down.
Nothing's wrong!
Nothing's wrong! Nothing's wrong!
You know it doesn't matter which childhood friend came first, right?
There's no fooling you, Ei-kun.
How'd you know?
I've spent a lot of time with you. More than anyone else.
Ei-kun! Ei-kun! Ei-kun!
H-Hey, get off! This is embarrassing!
I've spent more time with you
than anyone else too!
Whatever! Just get off!
Oh yeah, are you doing anything tomorrow?
Why?
Come check out swimsuits with me!
Don't you have one?
You bought one over the summer
back in sixth grade.
I've grown since then.
So, can you?
Well...
There's a huge bookstore in the mall too!
I bet they've got tons of
test prep stuff you can look at!
I guess I could.
Yay! Ei-kun, my love!
I love you!
Sure, you can go.
R-Really?
But I'm going shopping with Chiwa.
You can go.
Wasn't she really upset when
I went to the fireworks show?
Okay, I'll go.
Have fun.
By the way, where are you going shopping?
The mall in front of the station.
Oh, that flashy place.
A cesspool where love-on-the-brains congregate.
Disgusting.
You sound like a bitter old lady.
You know, I'm surprised you went along with a trip to the beach.
Oh? Why?
Well, you can't swim.
I can swim.
I just couldn't say no after
what Akishino-san said.
So you can be nice sometimes.
Hey, Eita...
You've got childhood friends all around you.
Harusaki Chiwa...
Fuyuumi Ai...
And Akishino-san is your lover from your past life. That makes her a childhood friend too.
Past lives don't count.
No matter how well I pretend
to be your girlfriend,
I can't do anything about time.
Hanenoyama Station
Ei-kun, sorry.
Did I keep you waiting?
Oh, about five minutes, I guess?
Come on! You're supposed to say, "Nah, I just got here!"
Why?
That's just how it works.
Why'd we have to meet here, anyway?
We live right next to each other.
B-Because it feels more like a date this way.
N-Never mind!
Let's go!
Eita-kun!
Sorry I'm late.
Did I keep you waiting?
Why are you here?
Oh, please, Eita-kun.
You're supposed to say, "Nah, I just got here!"
Answer the question!
Because I'm your girlfriend.
Isn't that obvious?
But you told me yesterday that I could go!
Yes, but I didn't say I wouldn't go.
Hey, Natsukawa, what're
you trying to pull here?
Oh, you were here?
You're so small, I didn't notice.
Y-You... Summer River!
Is something the matter, Thousand Japan-san?
Hey, you guys... We're in public.
Hey, Master. I want to go over there too.
Takkun, you philanderer!
Hey, Ei-kun, what about this one?
Isn't it cute?
Don't you like this color, Eita-kun?
This design is pretty stylish, isn't it?
This color makes it look refined, doesn't it?
But this one's better!
No, this one is!
But this one's—
Oh, please! This one is!
Just shut up already!
You're bugging the other customers!
Natsukawa started it.
Look, just take turns. Decide who
goes first with rock-paper-scissors.
Fine.
If you insist.
Listen, now. Start from "First comes rock."
Fine.
Let's go.
First comes rock. Rock, paper...
Rock!
Paper!
Hey, Ei-kun.
Let's do that again.
Okay...
Rock, paper...
Men!
Natsukawa, you're good at rock-paper-scissors.
You're pretty good yourself, Harusaki-san.
Oh, just forget it.
I'll check out your choices at the same time.
Go get changed.
H-Hime?!
Eita, hold me.
Choose my swimsuit for me too.
W-Wait, wait, wait!
Something's wrong here!
What are these firm peaches?
You saying they're Hime's?!
Were they always this big?!
I need to calm down.
Just hold her and—
Wait, no! Calm down!
Eita...
I-If I hold you, I won't be able
to see your swimsuit.
Pick one.
Then hold me.
You didn't come here for that!
Show me your swimsuit instead.
Okay.
Wh-What do you think?
Does it look weird?
No, it looks great on you.
Really?
I wouldn't lie.
Okay, then I'll buy this.
Hey, wait! Wait!
Wait until I get out!
Ei-kun!
Are you still there?
Don't try to run away.
I won't.
Huh?
C-Could the person in there be...
That's right, it's me!
A-chan?!
How could you, Takkun?!
Spending time with
other women in secret!
D-Don't make it sound
like a scandal!
Just so you know,
you're guilty of cheating!
If we have to settle this matter, I'm going to epic win in court!
Okay, calm down! I'll
pick yours for you too!
Really?!
Then come with me!
Hey, we're looking at swimsuits, right?
Just you wait!
I'm going to blow Ei-kun's mind!
W-Well, maybe I won't blow it, but at least I can show him I've grown.
So how do I look, Ei-kun?
So how do I look, Eita-kun?
Huh?
Do I look beautiful?
Beautiful enough to marry you?
What the heck is wrong with you?
Would a white kimono be better?
That's not what I meant.
Why am I picking out a wedding dress?
Oh, you're right! I should
meet your parents first!
Ai-chan, always rushing things. Tee-hee.
I'm begging you, can we please have a conversation where you listen?
Please?
Ei-kun!
Eita-kun!
I can't believe you!
Why did you run off?
A man who doesn't wait while his girlfriend shops is a failure as a boyfriend.
Look, I bought the swimsuit.
S-School Rules, Article 3, Section 2!
You're supposed to wear your uniform when you go out!
Why are you all dressed
in casual clothes?!
The girl in the wedding dress should not be telling us that!
Spring, summer, fall.
In the same order as the seasons,
I'll spend twenty minutes with each of you.
Can we all agree to that?
Fine.
H-Hey, Kidou-kun?
What about winter?
Will there be a winter?
Nope.
You already have Michel, Ai!
How about putting on your swimsuit and sending him a pic?
All by yourself.
I would like you to watch over us as we love each other.
O-Okay. I'll do just that!
I screwed up big time! Ai-chan, epic fail!
All right, let's go.
BAM
Takkun?
What are you crying for?
The whole Michel thing is your own fault.
I-I know.
This summer's
ultimate
popucute
bikinis!
This summer's
ultimate
popucute
bikinis!
Here.
This summer's
ultimate
popucute
bikinis!
This summer's
ultimate
popucute
bikinis!
This summer's
ultimate
popucute
bikinis!
This summer's
ultimate
popucute
bikinis!
This summer's
ultimate
popucute
bikinis!
Red'll look
good on you!
You wanted me to pick
a swimsuit for you, right?
Red'll look
good on you!
My fashion sense probably sucks, though.
No.
Takkun...
What?
I wuv you!
Jeez...
Ai's cheating!
I'm telling! I'm telling!
I'm telling on you to Michel!
I-I'm not cheating!
S-Sometimes, it's important
to get a second opinion
when you're trying to be the popucutest!
That's my master!
She doesn't miss a research opportunity.
The fish were so cute!
Especially the yellow and the blue ones!
Maybe I should get one for home!
What's wrong? You tired?
You'd end up eating it.
I'm just feeling the effects of this building's love-on-the-brain poison.
No, I wouldn't!
Why'd you even come?
Chiwawa, you were drooling.
You were blasting this place all last night.
Really? You really are
a pitiful Chiwawa!
Look who's talking!
Oh, how scary!
Cut it out!
I'm the only one.
Huh?
Pitiful Chiwawa!
Stop that!
I'm the only one who doesn't have any memories with you.
Then we'll just have to make some.
Lots of them. Starting now.
Well, aren't you presumptuous?
You're just my "fake."
mirai he to futari no Wonder tale
Unfolding into the future, it's our fairy tale
senaka ni sasayakitai no
I want to whisper to you,
mune no naka sotto misete
Secretly show me what's in your heart
hontou wa ienai kikenai kara
But because I can't say it, I can't ask you,
ijiwaru shitakunaru
I just have to pick on you
konna hazu ja nai
It wasn't supposed to be this way,
watashi no kokoro ga
But my heart just can't help but sing,
shiranai tokimeki wo utaidasu
Skipping beats that it never ever knew could be,
girigiri no atsusa de
With a passion, about to explode
mirai he to futari no Wonder tale
Unfolding into the future, it's our fairy tale
hajimari ga kowai no ni tomaranai
The start scares me so much, but I have to keep going
kimi no hitomi ga watashi no tame ni
Why is it that I want your eyes
kagayaite hoshii no wa naze kashira
To start shining for me?
koi na no oshiete yo
Is this love? Can't you tell me?
I wanna put my swimsuit on right away!
Hey, which beach are we going to?
The one closest to here is Funase Beach.
Oh yeah, how are we
paying for the trip?
The club will get funds
from the school, right?
Of course not. Not until
the second term, anyway.
Oh my.
I don't think I can go
just on my allowance.
We can't go to the beach?
Hey, Eita!
Welcome back.
Oh, thanks. You too.
Hi there, Saeko-san!
Hey, Chiwawa-chan.
Energetic as ever, I see.
So you're the members of that Society Advocating Whatever?
I'm Kiryuu Saeko, Eita's aunt.
H-Hello.
P-Pleased to meet you.
So which one of these
girls is your girlfriend?
It's an honor to meet you.
I'm Natsukawa Masuzu.
I'm in a very fulfilling
relationship with your nephew.
Huh?
I'm not asking about
your fake, you know.
Fake?
Now, tell me which one of
these girls you really love.
Next Episode
The popucute item for next week is...
a psychological test.
Have him face this trial to find the light and darkness that hides within his heart.
The Excitement the Night Before the Trip Brings About a War Zone
By overcoming hope and despair,
you will be able to grow closer together.