Have you dug anything up on Fuyuumi Ai?
Fuyuumi definitely has a boyfriend.
She bragged about what she wears on dates with him
and how they started dating in great detail.
You call that proof?
What'll it take to get you to believe her?
We might just have to meet this Daigorou for ourselves.
If you doubt her that much, this'll never end.
How about trusting me
when I tell you something?
I'm sorry.
After living my whole life as a fake,
I've lost the ability to trust people.
That can't be true.
Sure, you might doubt
anything people say,
but you haven't lost your
ability to trust people.
If you couldn't trust anyone, you wouldn't be in our club with Chiwa and Hime.
And you make all those
get-super-popular plans
because you trust that they'll go along with them, right?
I... trust them?
Yeah. You need to put
more trust in yourself.
If you don't trust yourself, you—
Wh-What...
That's your reward for saying something so thoughtful.
isse-no
One, two, three
okaeri
Welcome back
saa dekakeyou
Now, let's go out
nukegake rendezvous
I'm stealing you for a rendezvous
kizuna ga daiji
Friends are important
koibito ga daiichi
But a girlfriend is the most
Girlish Lover
kono itami kimi no sei
This pain I feel is your fault
mune no tokimeki uso no tsumori
This feeling in my chest is supposed to be a lie
ima made no position wo
What would happen if tomorrow
koeta ashita wa dou naru no
I tried being more than what I am to you now?
nee motto issho shiyou
Hey, let's spend more time together
dame
Can't we?
dame watashi dake
You can't, he's mine
yudan mo suki mo nai
You can never be too careful with me
kimi to no border koetai
I want to jump the border between us
sou motto
Now, I'll be
daitan de chotto gouin
A bit bolder, maybe even aggressive
suki wo misetai
I want to show you my love
yasashii kimi mo
I want you when you're nice
ijiwaru na kimi mo
I want you when you're mean
hitorijime
You're all mine
kitsui tte
Too much for you?
yappa yamete
You really want to stop?
urahara fall in love
It's the wrong way to fall in love
tomodachi ijou
I'm more than just your friend,
honmono miman no
But less than a real
Girlish Lover
Pass in One Shot!
Hanenoyama Seminar
That concludes today's lecture.
A Double Date at the Movie Theater Turns Into a War Zone
We will continue as normal tomorrow,
but our facilities will be inspected the day after,
so there will be no lecture on that day.
Continue investigating Fuyuumi Ai.
Continue? What am I supposed to investigate?
Eita.
K-Kaoru?!
Wanna stop somewhere for drinks again?
S-Sure, why not?
Thanks. We should go somewhere different today.
Right, A-chan?
Y-Yeah.
Oh, A-chan, you'd go anywhere with Eita, wouldn't you?
Hey! What are you saying, you dummy?!
You dummy! Stop saying dumb things!
Dummy!
I'll be gracing you with my presence again today!
O-Okay...
Here's your order.
One jumbo banana parfait and a coffee.
Dang, that's huge!
Wow!
That was so good!
You can have these, Kaoru.
Okay, fine.
Do you not like bananas?
They're my favorite.
Huh?
Delicious!
So you're being a spy for Natsukawa?
I'm not a spy.
I guess if we do find dirty laundry on Fuyuumi,
we could stop the Society from getting shut down, but...
...it'd be like blackmail.
Huh?
"Tell us! Your 100% guaranteed Good-love Charms"?
It's a page for reader-submitted charms.
What? Reader-submitted?
Your 100%
guaranteed
It's summer!
Tell us!
Good-love
Charms
Ai-chan Epic Win
Regular PachiLe
Submitter!
Some of the regular submitters are really popular.
Your 100%
guaranteed
It's summer!
Tell us!
Good-love
Charms
Ai-chan Epic Win
Regular PachiLe
Submitter!
Your 100%
guaranteed
It's summer!
Tell us!
Good-love
Charms
Ai-chan Epic Win
Regular PachiLe
Submitter!
Your 100%
guaranteed
It's summer!
Tell us!
Good-love
Charms
Ai-chan Epic Win
Regular PachiLe
Submitter!
Like this girl.
Charms
Regular PachiLe
Submitter!
Charms
Regular PachiLe
Submitter!
Good-love
"Super-special love charm to make the guy you like ask you out."
"Step 1: Refrain from eating your favorite food for five days."
"If you give it to a friend, it might be more likely to work."
"Step 2: At exactly 7 PM on the fifth day,
repeat this incantation while gazing at the face of the person you like:
'Grant my desire. Meow, mreow, mew.'"
"You must chant the incantation for thirty seconds."
"But if the target finds out, it won't work."
No one in their right mind would do all of that!
That's not true!
This submitter is amazing! They got the highest score on Pachi Lemon's popucute test!
Everyone says that her charms work!
Then why don't you give it a try?
Why not?
I'll start today!
I won't eat my favorite food for five days straight!
Here you go. Meat udon with extra meat.
Yay! Meat! Meat! Meat!
Ei-kun, I love you!
Pass in One Shot!
Hanenoyama Seminar
Fuyuumi? What's she looking at?
Eita!
Finished looking up what you wanted to?
Yeah.
Come on, A-chan. Say hi.
Huh?
Wh-Wh-What a coincidence.
Didn't you just see me in the study hall?
Hane River Fireworks Show
The fireworks show is coming up pretty soon.
Yeah, it's packed with people every year.
I-I know. If only someone knew a secret spot to watch from.
A secret spot, huh?
K-Kidou-kun, are you going with Natsukawa Masuzu?
She invited me, but I turned her down.
What about Harusaki Chiwa?
Then are you going with Akishino Himeka?!
If she invites me, I'll turn her down.
Yes! The charm worked like an epic dream!
Now's my chance! My chance for love!
Ai-chan, epic win!
So excited about it that you fell out of your seat? You're quite the kid, Kidou-kun.
Right...
You need to start acting like an adult.
We're in high school, you know.
Right.
So who are you going to see the fireworks with?
What's wrong? Wh-Why don't you come right out with it?
I'm not going this year.
Huh?
Why? Are you busy that day?
I was thinking of using the time to study in the prep school's study hall.
Then you're not busy!
You should go!
I could, but...
Are you going with your boyfriend, Fuyuumi?
Huh? Boyfriend? What are you talking about?
I'm talking about Michel, obviously.
Oh, right! Michel!
We've got plans for dates, of course.
But he'll be in Tokyo on August 4th.
So I'm free for the fireworks show!
I see. You're free, huh?
Not just free! Completely free!
That's great.
Hey!
Hey, you guys!
Take a look at these.
Oh, tickets for Asura Fight?
Yeah, we don't have class tomorrow.
How about seeing it in the afternoon?
We could...
You'll come too, right, A-chan?
Yeah.
S-Sure, I can go.
All right, looks like it'll be the three of us.
Yeah, I'll go! I'll go with you guys!
A movie? This is your chance.
My chance?
Yes, your chance for Operation Acquire the Hall Monitor's Dirty Laundry with a Super Hot Date!
What? What do you mean?
We need that Hall Monitor from Hell to expose the love on her brain so we can collect her dirty laundry.
A date is perfect for that.
So basically, you want me to follow Fuyuumi on her date with Michel
to get some dirty laundry on her?
You're the one going on a date with her, Eita-kun.
What?
You're going on a date with Fuyuumi Ai
and making her fall for you.
Essentially, a male version of my get-super-popular plans.
You might call it the Society Advocating Masculine Elegance For All Gentlemen.
Once she falls for you, she's as good as ours.
Supposing this Michel really is her boyfriend,
the second she falls for you, she'll be cheating.
It's the best laundry we could ask for.
And if she doesn't have a boyfriend?
Then, once Fuyuumi Ai falls head over heels for you,
we'll make her our personal meat puppet and force her to do our bidding.
Meat!
A meat puppet...
Hold up a second! Don't ask for the impossible!
There's no way I can make
Fuyuumi Ai fall in love with me!
How pathetic.
The previous Burning Fighting Fighter would cry if he heard you now.
Huh?
What do you mean?
Please explain.
"July 10th. Sunny."
"Summer has started, and
Hurricane Me is approaching."
W-Wait!
"Our eyes met again. Four times today. Three times yesterday. So, why you?"
"My fair-skinned angel, trapped in this cage known as a classroom."
"Someone who should never have fallen in love with me."
"I'm bad to the bone."
"You've gone and fallen for me anyway."
"Not good."
"'It's not.'"
"It's hot."
"'So hot.'"
Eita's doing it again...
"But I, Burning Fighting Fighter, have offered my life to the cause of fighting the Wyverns."
I've gotten used to this.
He's so loud.
"I am destined to never date normal humans."
We're not in the clubroom, Ei-kun. Keep it down!
"I have to finish this while the fire of her love remains dim."
"Before her untainted, pure love flares up into pure black hatred..."
"Before our bodies are burned with the crimson flames of war."
"But if she gives me a letter,
I guess I'll take it."
Does that Student Council President have to rely on me for everything?
Fair-skinned Angel, Tanaka Yoshie
Kidou Eita
Kidou-kun?
Working late again, Miss Student Council Member?
Will you ever stop teasing me?
I-I bet everyone thinks I'm annoying.
They think I'm stupid for working so hard for the Student Council.
I know it!
No, you don't.
At the very least, there's one guy who doesn't think so standing right here.
E-Eita-kun...
I... I...
I've always... always...
I've always loved you, Shintani-kun!
What?!
S-Sorry.
I bet you think I'm really a pain for suddenly telling you that.
N-No, I don't.
I love you too, Tanaka.
Somebody pinch me!
Hey, who's out there?!
Let's do this, damn it!
Burn, my Dragonic Aura!
Fate Dark Black Flame!
Take this! And this! And this! And that!
Be at ease. I've eliminated the enemy.
Our eyes met again.
Four times today.
Three times yesterday.
My fair-skinned angel, trapped in this cage known as a classroom.
I'm bad to the bone.
I'll never forgive this rotten world.
So in order to make sure Fuyuumi-san and Eita-kun go on a date as a pair tomorrow,
I'll never forgive you, my angel.
Harusaki-san will join them and pair up with Asoi-kun to make it a double date.
I don't like it, but I'll do it.
Akishino-san and I will tail the four of you.
The moment we find Fuyuumi Ai in a compromising situation, I'll snap a picture.
I can't do that.
Why not?
Fuyuumi Ai is my love master.
I can't betray my master.
I understand.
You don't have to participate then, Akishino-san.
So tomorrow, we'll launch Operation Acquire the Hall Monitor's Dirty Laundry with a Super Hot Date!
Hanenoyama Station
Sorry to keep you!
Wh-What took you so long?
I waited for about five minutes.
Uh...
Men!
You're good at dodging, Ei-kun.
You were actually trying to hit me!
Huh? What are you doing here, Chiwawa-chan?
O-Oh, hi there, Kaoru-kun.
F-Fancy meeting you here!
You're going to see a movie?
I-I wanna come too!
Don't worry about the ticket.
I'll get my own.
You're so obvious.
Just act natural.
Natural.
I see.
Sure, let's go. The four of us.
Thank you.
You did it!
Why do Ei-kun and Fuyuumi have to be a pair?
Why are you complaining?
Everything's going just as planned.
I know, but...
What's wrong, Chiwawa-chan?
Nothing!
Really?
Now, make Fuyuumi Ai fall in love with you, Eita-kun.
I told you, it's impossible!
Hm?
Oh, nothing.
Um... D-Do you remember anything from kindergarten?
Uh... You mean Wakaba Kindergarten?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Nothing really worth talking about...
What's wrong?
N-Nothing's wrong! Nothing at all!
I see.
Um... What do you think about my clothes?
Do I look weird?
Do you think I'm a criminal now?
"Criminal"?
I mean, you asked me if I wore my uniform on dates.
Oh, that?
Yeah, you don't look like a criminal.
In fact, I think you look really cute.
Girlish, in a cute way.
I'm gonna...
I'm gonna go run outside!
Calm down, Fuyuumi!
We're already outside!
Where am I supposed to run then?!
You don't have to run!
Just walk like you were before!
Hey, don't you remember?
We ran while holding hands, just like this.
Don't you remember?
Huh?
Kote!
Ei-kun, you're good at dodging!
You always do that when something bothers you!
You know me well!
Well, we are childhood friends!
Stop interfering with the mission immediately, Harusaki-san.
What are you doing, Chiwawa-chan?
Um, er...
Childhood friends...
July 28 (Sun.)
Asura Fight!
Today:
Audience Shouting Day
I'm disappointed, Eita-kun.
Is that the best you can do to make her fall for you?
Hurry up and make Fuyuumi-san fall for you,
and talk to her in a way which I wouldn't classify as cheating on me.
Any idea how hard that is?!
Talk to you later.
I-I'm not scared. I'm not scared.
I classify this as cheating!
Eiji will marry me, his childhood friend!
Get away from him, Ami!
You come out of nowhere after all these years and try to break us up? You're horrible!
What are you talking about, China?!
Eiji and I promised to marry a long time ago!
And you tried to worm in and steal him while I was down after my accident, you thief!
It's too late!
Eiji is mine!
No, I'm taking him back!
Here I come!
Bring it!
Wait, China! Ami!
Get her, Ami!
China's a tiny girl!
She's no match for you!
Looks, brains, personality... You're better than her at everything!
She thinks she deserves him just because she's his childhood friend! Bring her down!
China-chan, you can do it!
That Ami girl is horrible!
She's trying to use her position to get her hands on your man!
Kick her ass! No quarter!
Come on, you two!
Come on, you two... Can't you get along?
You're pathetic, Eiji!
You call yourself a man?!
Can't you decide who'll be your girlfriend on your own?
You're trash! You suck, Kidou Eita!
That was my name you shouted, wasn't it?!
Who was it?! Come on, show yourself!
Get her, China-chan!
You're his childhood friend! She's got nothing on you!
Don't give up, Ami!
What's important isn't how long you've known someone, but how well you know them!
A childhood friend would obviously know someone the best and the longest!
You're just full of yourself!
Like you'd know anything about childhood friends!
Like you'd know anything either!
You'd never understand how someone who couldn't even become his childhood friend feels!
My feelings for you are stronger than anyone's!
Open your eyes, Eiji!
Can't you see who truly loves you?!
Is something wrong?
Do it, Ami!
End it all!
Now that I think about it, it's not really possible to get pictures of anything inside a movie theater.
Masuzu-san, epic fail! Tee-hee!
Don't you "Tee-hee!" me!
Then what was the point of the whole operation?!
It's been fun, Eita.
I'm going home with A-chan, so...
Oh, okay. Uh, Fuyuumi...
What is it?
Um, about earlier...
Y-You can forget about that.
It wasn't anything important.
mirai he to futari no Wonder tale
Unfolding into the future, a wonderful tale about us
senaka ni sasayakitai no
I want to whisper to you,
mune no naka sotto misete
Secretly show me what's in your heart
hontou wa ienai kikenai kara
But because I can't say it, I can't ask you,
ijiwaru shitakunaru
I just have to pick on you
konna hazu ja nai
It wasn't supposed to be this way,
watashi no kokoro ga
But my heart just can't help but sing,
shiranai tokimeki mo utaidasu
Skipping beats that it never knew could be,
girigiri no atsusa de
With a passion, about to explode
mirai he to futari no Wonder tale
Unfolding into the future, a wonderful tale about us
hajimari ga kowai no ni tomaranai
I'm afraid that it might start, but I can't stop it
kimi no hitomi ga watashi no tame ni
I wonder why I want your eyes
kagayaite hoshii no wa naze kashira
To start shining for me
koi na no oshiete yo
Is this love? Can't you tell me?
Next Episode
The popucute item for next week is...
a yukata!
Everyone loves navy blue and pink, and they definitely look good,
but you should try on different colors to find what's best for you!
A Promise Comes Back to Haunt as a War Zone
Make sure to keep your back straight and take short steps!