Hanenoyama Station
The gods are on the girlfriend's side.
We need to act like a couple. But I didn't need to tell you that, right?
I'm way ahead of you.
I'll make love-on-the-brains
look like amateurs.
Hey, Honey! Whatcha wanna
do when we get there?
Let's take a stroll together along the shore!
Sounds great!
We can talk about our future as we gaze at the sunset!
They're totally faking it.
They're so fake.
Fake...
Hey, Masuzu, don't you think it'd be romantic if we looked for shells together too?
Maybe we'll even find a pink clam!
Oh, how lovely!
We can each keep half of the shell as a souvenir of the trip!
Yeah, let's make lots of
memories of our love!
They're so awkward.
It's like I'm watching some C movie.
The early bird?
Damn it. I'm going to whip out the one thing a boyfriend and girlfriend can talk about!
Hey, Masuzu, last night, I was watching Magure Keiji...
isse-no
One, two, three
okaeri
Welcome back
saa dekakeyou
Now, let's go out
nukegake rendezvous
I'm stealing you for a rendezvous
kizuna ga daiji
Friends are important
koibito ga daiji
But a girlfriend is the most
Girlish Lover
kono itami kimi no sei
This pain I feel is your fault
mune no tokimeki uso no tsumori
This feeling in my chest is supposed to be a lie
ima made no position wo
What would happen if tomorrow
koeta ashita wa dou naru no
I tried being more than what I am to you now?
nee motto issho shiyo
Hey, let's spend more time together
dame
Can't we?
dame watashi dake
You can't, he's mine
yudan mo suki mo nai
You can never be too careful with me
kimi to no border koetai
I want to jump the border between us
sou motto
Now, I'll be
daitan de chotto gouin
A bit bolder, maybe even aggressive
suki wo misetai
I want to show you all my love
yasashii kimi mo
I want you when you're nice
ijiwaru na kimi mo
I want you when you're mean
hitorijime
You're all mine
kidzuite
Please realize
yappa yamete
Never mind, just stop
urahara fall in love
It's the wrong way to fall in love
tomodachi ijou
I'm more than just your friend,
honmono miman no
But less than a real
Girlish Lover
The Result of a Plan Is a War Zone
Here we go, Himecchi!
One, two...
What a view!
It's pretty good!
Hime, what do you think?
.ZIP please!
Club activities start now.
We'll be doing some popucute swimming, popucute shell gathering,
popucute playing in the sand, and popucute watermelon smashing.
I want you to do all of these as practice for the contest.
Okay!
It's not scary? It's really not scary?
It's not scary! I promise!
Let's go!
Jump!
This feels so good!
It's salty.
I have finally conquered the Grand Line!
They look like kids.
I couldn't agree more. They won't become popular like that.
I'm guessing you won't be going for a swim?
I might try to get back at you if you try to tease me.
Hey, look at this.
Doesn't it look like a heart?
Huh?
I bet another one just like it's lying around here somewhere.
Wanna look for it together?
What? It looks like a fried fish to me.
What's wrong with you?!
Takkun, you big dummy!
It seems even Fuyuumi-san's popucuteness is no match for your cluelessness.
And what about you, Little Miss Popucute?
As you can see.
You're like a koala at the zoo.
What? I'm like a Koala Yummy?
That's not what I said.
You don't have a gooey chocolate center.
Why are you acting like a love-on-the-brain?
We're supposed to act like we're dating, right?
Oh, yes, that's right.
But those three aren't even looking at us.
They sure are enjoying it.
What a strange taste.
The flavor leaves something to be desired.
The sauce is way too salty,
and not particularly good.
And the noodles are all soggy. It's horrible.
But strangely enough,
you're left wanting more.
Wow, she's not talking eighth-grade syndrome for once.
Everything tastes great at the beach!
Maybe they deliberately make the flavor so strong because everyone's tired after swimming.
Eita-kun,
would you mind preparing dessert for us?
Huh?
When'd you get that?
You can do it, Ei-kun!
Give it a popucute smash!
Eita's popucute sword
skills are second to none!
As a popucute hall monitor, I'll be grading you on how popucutely you smash it open!
Would you give the popucute thing a rest?!
Hey, where's the stick?
We don't have one.
Use your head, Eita-kun.
So you want me to think of an alternative?
No, I want you to smash
it open with your head.
You meant that literally?!
And begin!
Hey, hey, Ei-kun!
Over here!
Eita, no.
The underworld is that way.
Follow my voice!
Kidou-kun, over here!
The word of a hall monitor would never lead you astray!
Don't listen to them, Eita-kun!
They're all trying to trick you!
The truth would only come
from me, your girlfriend!
If there's anyone you shouldn't
trust, it's Natsukawa!
The club president is an
outer god of the darkness...
The lord of chaos... The queen of evil!
Be careful!
That woman will lead you to depravity!
I trust my girlfriend!
No! Ei-kun! Don't do it!
What are you saying?! Wait!
Don't go! Eita!
Masuzu, where's the watermelon?!
Straight towards me, three meters!
Jump right in and grab it!
All right!
Ei-kun!
No, wait!
Not that way!
This way! Ei-kun!
This melon's mine!
I-I got...
I got my hands on the world's
softest, whitest melons!
How are they, Eita-kun?
Are my melons good?
Ei-kun...
What do you think you're doing?
You refuse to hold me, and yet...
Lewd!
L
E
W
D
Branded with the mark of my sins...
We don't have any curry powder.
I'll go get some.
No, I'd like you to replace
the bulbs in the chandelier.
Huh?
It looks like they burned out.
Oh, okay.
Then...
We'll get it!
Hey, Natsukawa-san.
Did people stop asking you out when you started dating Kidou-kun?
Yes. They did.
I saw you getting asked out once.
It was behind the gym.
You heaved a long sigh after.
The guy yelled and screamed like crazy.
I hate it when guys get angry even though they're in the wrong.
If I were in your shoes, I'd get
tired of getting asked out too.
It wouldn't be strange to just stop caring and go out with whoever.
I see.
But...
If that's why you started dating Kidou-kun,
I don't think I could forgive you.
So is it, Natsukawa-san?
Fuyuumi-san.
How far are you supposed to peel an onion?
Why did you go all the way to the center?
You should've just stopped
after the brown part!
Oh, no wonder I couldn't see when to stop.
Why didn't you ask me sooner?!
I'll do the vegetables! You wash the rice!
And don't use any soap!
Why in the world would
I wash rice with soap?
I only warned you because you did something so cliché!
I can't believe you!
Talking to me like that...
Of course I'm not that stupid!
We need definitive evidence.
Huh? I can't really hear you.
We need to show them definitive evidence.
Something that proves we're dating.
Y-Yeah, but what do we do?
A-Any ideas?
Something like a present?
Material goods won't do.
We need something more intense.
It needs to be something that will force them to believe at once.
More intense, huh?
The Wind Slash.
The Wind Slash!
Huh?
"Wind Slash!"
You mean, a kiss?
Yes.
A nonchalant kiss in front of the others would work wonders.
You just have to kiss me as though it were a casual, everyday greeting between us.
Wait a second.
Are you serious about this?
What are you getting so flustered about?
We've already kissed countless times.
A simple kiss doesn't mean a thing to us anti-love types,
but it's a big deal to those
love-on-the-brains, right?
Do you know how that'll end up?
Yes. It will become quite the war zone.
You're throwing me to the wolves!
All three of them!
Yes, I would be.
That's why I'm giving you the option to back out on this one.
Huh?
I won't use your notebook
to force you to do it.
You decide if you kiss me or not, Kidou Eita.
Was this it?
Ei-kun, you suck!
The three of hearts is over here!
Are you bad at memorizing things?
No, uh...
Here's the plan.
After spending time with everyone,
you say you're going to bed because you're tired and stand up.
That's when I'll say, "Good night, Darling,"
and you whisper, "Okay, good night, Honey," into my ear and kiss me.
Where are we, Europe?!
Ei-kun?
Are you tired?
No, not at all! I'm still rarin' to go!
Really?
What about you guys? Still up for more?
Yeah, I'm fine.
If I kiss Masuzu, I'll be heading straight down the war zone route.
Yes. Condition green.
By the way, was that Michel
you were texting earlier?
But if I don't kiss her and
go down the harem route,
That's right! He'll die of loneliness if I don't text him every day!
it's just a matter of time before they figure out that it's all an act.
In that case...
I-I'm tired. I think I'll head to bed.
Say it.
Okay, then why don't we call it a night?
H-Hey, you don't have to stop just because I'm not playing anymore.
It's fine. I think we've played enough.
Anyway, there's something we wanted to give you today.
Here you go.
This one's for you, Ei-kun, and this one's for you, Natsukawa.
What's this?
Open it.
We all match!
Himecchi designed it.
By the way, this isn't a Z. It's the "maiden" in "maidenly elegance."
Master found a shop that
would make them for us.
Chiwa came up with the idea.
You know how sports teams have matching uniforms and stuff, right?
Our club didn't have anything like that.
We're an official club now, so I thought we needed something.
So I asked them what we could do.
We kept it a secret from you, Natsukawa-san.
You made the club for us, after all.
So you can think of it as a present from us members.
Why'd you keep it a secret from me too?
If we told you, Natsukawa'd find out for sure.
You're terrible at keeping secrets.
The contest's tomorrow, right?
It'd be hard to give you something like this after the contest,
so I wanted to do it now.
They weren't collaborating to break us up,
but to pull this off?
You got me.
Thank you for the very
thoughtful cell phone strap.
I'll treasure it.
Sorry!
I just couldn't kiss you in that situation.
It's fine.
If you had forced the kiss,
I would've hated you for it.
In spite of myself, I was touched.
And at the same time, I was reminded of just how wretched I really am.
No, it was just by chance that...
No, it wasn't just chance.
Harusaki-san and the others see me as a rival,
but they can still give me something like this as a present.
They can give a present to someone they're fighting with.
That's the kind of people they are.
Completely different from me.
I can't win the contest tomorrow.
You might be right.
Why don't you just withdraw?
I thought about it, but after considering their feelings,
I think I should participate
and face proper judgment.
When I think of how sad and painful it was for Harusaki-san when I snatched you away from her...
When I consider that, I can't simply forfeit.
September 10th. Sunny.
I'm going to be a doctor and fix Chiwa's hip!
Thank you for everything
you've done for me.
Once this trip ends, you'll be free.
The president still isn't up.
She looked perfectly fine yesterday.
I wonder if she'll make the contest.
What time does it start again?
The event opens at 4:00, and the contest starts at 4:30.
Participants are required to meet in front of the stage by 3:30.
She'll probably be ready by then.
Okay, we're heading out!
Make sure you come!
Of course.
Masuzu?
You awake?
You must be hungry.
Want some soumen?
No, thank you.
Could you leave me alone for now?
The sun shines bright in the sea.
My heart is also in the blu—
Move! Outta the way!
Ow...
Hands off, you molester!
Creepy-ass geek! Creepy-ass virgin!
Virgin?
Best compliment you could ever give me.
Huh?!
You're so gross! Gross, gross, gross!
Die, die, die!
Go to hell, freaking virgin!
That's what I'm talking about!
Keep it coming! Give me more!
My big resort trip is ruined now.
You've got enough money. Go overseas.
Been there, done that.
And someone like you
shouldn't even be here.
Oh, shut up.
I'm on a club trip.
Does that mean Suzu's here too?
So? How's Suzu doing?
Is she okay?
Is she eating right?
You concerned?
I'm not.
I'm only asking because I have to tell Daddy about her.
Now start talking!
Say what you want, but you really love your sister, don't you?
Shut up, virgin.
I see.
So that's what happened.
Suzu was called the jewel
of the Natsukawa family.
A jewel... In other words, an accessory.
A tool for Daddy to show off to his high society.
He took Suzu away from her mother to live with him for that reason.
Suzu acted just as our father wanted.
The intelligent, graceful, and obedient daughter who respected her father.
She played the part perfectly.
Me being the way I am,
Daddy didn't expect much out of me.
But he could expect a lot out of Suzu.
She kept acting to meet his expectations, until finally, it drove her crazy.
She kept lying to herself, and eventually, she forgot who she really was.
Suzu says some pretty crazy stuff sometimes, doesn't she?
She says something totally harsh, but suddenly she's nice,
and then she goes right back to being cold.
I bet she's taken you for a bunch of rides.
Yeah.
She took me for a ton of them.
But it wasn't so bad.
That kind of life wasn't so bad.
I see.
Thanks for coming to love my sister.
If there were someone who could stick with Masuzu, what do you think he'd be?
Someone who could stick with a liar?
That's totally obvious.
A partner in crime.
mirai he to futari no Wonder tale
Unfolding into the future, it's our fairy tale
Hey there, everyone! What you've all been waiting for, the Miss OreDere Contest, is about to begin!
senaka ni sasayakitai no
I want to whisper to you,
mune no naka sotto misete
Secretly show me what's in your heart
hontou wa ienai kikenai kara
But because I can't say it, I can't ask you,
ijiwaru shitakunaru
I just have to pick on you
konna hazu ja nai
It wasn't supposed to be this way,
watashi no kokoro ga
But my heart just can't help but sing,
shiranai tokimeki wo utaidasu
Skipping beats that it never ever knew could be,
girigiri no atsusa de
With a passion, about to explode
mirai he to futari no Wonder tale
Unfolding into the future, it's our fairy tale
hajimari ga kowai no ni tomaranai
The start scares me so much, but I have to keep going
kimi no hitomi ga watashi no tame ni
Why is it that I want your eyes
kagayaite hoshii no wa naze kashira
To start shining for me?
koi na no oshiete yo
Is this love? Can't you tell me?
Next Episode
The popucute item for next week is...
honest feelings.
No matter how many
words we string together,
if we don't really mean them, then no matter how honest we try to be,
A War Zone for a Whole New World
they don't mean a thing.