Yokodera Youto Theater
My Master and Me
July 2nd.
Sunny, then cloudy.
In order to recover my facade, I have changed
roles from Pervert Prince to Azuki Azusa's dog.
I'm waiting for her at the
school gates today too.
Everyone's saying, "Isn't he cute? He reminds me of Hachikou, from that story!"
8:20 am.
Azuki Azusa arrives at school.
She slips past me again.
Recess.
I roam the school, searching for Azuki Azusa.
Here she is, on the roof,
sleeping in the shadow of the water tank.
As punishment for being so careless, I doodle on her belly.
A commemorative photo with a big belly raccoon!
Need to send her a copy!
Lunch.
Azuki Azusa invites me on a walk.
She's smiling!
I'm smiling!
Everyone's smiling!
You perverted dog!
She wrings my neck,
and deletes the photo.
After school.
I apologize to Azuki Azusa.
"I won't mess with your belly again!"
Her belly?!
They've gone that far already?!
The crowd goes wild!
What do you think you're doing,
you disgusting dog?!
I played with my master a lot today too!
Let's keep it up!
To Be Continued
By Storywriters' Messageboard
So you're enjoying your life as a dog?
I see.
You're an absolutely hopeless pervert.
I can't tell. Are you trying to speak daggers to me?
It may seem that way because my facial expression doesn't change.
So what are you going to
do about Azuki-san now?
We're going to the next town
over to talk about that.
Got any ideas?
What about giving up on Azuki-san?
I can't retreat under enemy fire!
I can't just sit back knowing
that she's got my facade!
I hope that's all it is.
mou ikkai kocchi muite..
One more time, look this way
iitai koto ga motto aru kara..
There's still more that I want to tell you
mou ikkai kocchi muite..
One more time, look this way
honki ga yureru ai no future..
Who you love's going to change in the future
dakara kocchi muite..
That's why you should look this way
maware chikyuu koi wo nosete..
The world turns, filled with love
dakara kocchi muite..
That's why you should look this way
guuzen ja nai fantafuture..
It wasn't just chance, it's our fantastic future
watashi
kara
sasou
yuuki
wo
watashi kara sasou yuuki wo
To have the courage to ask you out myself
kudasai
to
tsuki ni
negau
no
kudasai to tsuki ni negau no
I wished on the moon that I could
setsunai
kokoro
ni
mahou
kaketemimashou
setsunai kokoro ni mahou kaketemimashou
Let's cast a little spell on that breaking heart
mirai
he
no
chikamichi
ne
mirai he no chikamichi ne
It's the fastest way to the future
amaku naare egao de
With a smile I'm making even sweeter
kimi yo tokechae
I'll make your whole self melt
kyou no yozora wo mitsume
Tonight I'll look at the sky
chotto senobite
And try to reach a little closer
mou ikkai kocchi muite..
One more time, look this way
iitai koto ga motto aru kara..
There's still more that I want to tell you
mou ikkai kocchi muite..
One more time, look this way
honki ga yureru ai no future..
Who you love's going to change in the future
dakara kocchi muite..
That's why you should look this way
maware chikyuu koi wo nosete..
The world turns, filled with love
dakara kocchi muite..
That's why you should look this way
guuzen ja nai fantafuture..
It wasn't just chance, it's our fantastic future
The Fairy Doesn't Get Mad
This is the place!
I saw it and thought it would be perfect to come here with you!
A Japanese-style animal café?
Animal Cafe
Wuff Muff
It's a bit far from home,
but it'll be perfect for planning our next step!
We'll come up with a plan as we relax with the puppies and kittens!
You wanted to come here with me?
Just the two of us?
I see.
I really can't tell how you feel about this.
Wait up!
Welcome home, Master!
You wanted to come for
the maids, didn't you?
Of course!
I get to treat you to a great time snuggling with the animals,
and at the same time, have
a great time with the maids!
You're an incurably hopeless pervert,
but I suppose the uniforms are cute.
I'd like to try wearing them at least once.
I'd like to see you cosplaying at least once, too!
If you only look, I guess I could try it.
I definitely wouldn't only look!
I definitely won't do it, then.
A-Azuki Azusa?!
Did you know about this?
No way! It's a total coincidence!
Why would you go to the next town over by coincidence?!
Because you're a pervert?!
It's because you're a pervert, isn't it?!
Azuki-chan! They're customers! Customers!
Good day, Master.
Do you have an order for your pet?
Woof.
Could I get a Japanese cutlet, with the animal-maid "Ahn!" service?
What?!
Is there a problem?
In this store, the customers are masters.
Coming right up, woof.
I'll do whatever it takes to please my master, woof!
Man, animals really do make you feel all warm and fuzzy!
Ow!
We didn't even get our order!
But I never thought Azuki Azusa would be working there!
"An Heiress's Holiday Revealed!"
It's the perfect headline for the
billboards at school! Just need a picture!
That won't help you get back your facade.
That's just you being a pervert.
Wait, Tsutsukakushi, where are we going?
This should be perfect.
A Lovely Time
A Rest . . . Starting at 4000 yen
A Night . . . Starting at 7000 yen
But isn't this...
A love hotel?!
Wilde
Wait, Tsutsukakushi—
Please keep your voice down.
But we can't do this!
We're still in high school!
We need to be in love!
On the other hand, the innocent, facadeless me
wouldn't mind ascending the steps to adulthood in one bound!
What do you think we're doing, you pervert?
We're getting out of the rain.
I think we should wait here until Azuki-san is done with her shift and talk to her directly.
We can watch the entrance,
and we're out of the rain here.
Oh, that's what you meant?
I thought you wanted to spend time with me in the hotel.
I got all excited.
You were excited?
I see.
Is she mad at me?
I can't tell what she's thinking.
Senpai.
Senpai, look.
All right, let's go.
Stop right there!
What the hell're you doing?!
It says no freaking kids allowed, don't it?!
Tryin' to show off to a loner
working on a Sunday like me?!
Uh...
I'm gonna cry, asshole!
You hear me, you little shit?!
She's shaking.
Let's go.
You runnin', you little dick?!
Well, I hope yours falls off!
I hope everyone's falls off!
Damn it!
Geez, that employee was kinda scary.
Do we look like a couple?
I dunno. What do you think?
I don't know.
My parents died when I was young.
I don't have any brothers.
I had a hard time talking to boys.
I always ran away.
But you're okay with me?
Fortunately, even if I'm embarrassed, I can't show it now.
It's like hiding in the dark of night.
This is one thing I can thank for Stony Cat for, I suppose.
What is it?
You just kinda reminded me of a cat.
A cat in a bag.
She's in distress,
but pretends to be calm.
That isn't what it means.
And I can't see why you'd say that.
I see.
We ended up losing track of Azuki-san.
Well, what's done is done.
We can just talk to her at school tomorrow.
Okay.
Senpai.
What is it?
That.
Azuki Azusa?
An heiress taking on two jobs?
Azuki Azusa News
AANN
A Day in the Life of a (Self-proclaimed) Heiress
Azuki Azusa's mornings start early.
She gets to enjoy the little things in life when she plays with dogs at houses she delivers papers to.
She lives on the fourth floor of your normal neighborhood apartment. No pets allowed.
She works in the next town over.
She works as a waitress,
then at a construction site.
She's so tired, she sleeps at school.
The nocturnal lifestyle doesn't
really bother her, though.
"My chest may be flat as a board,
but my dreams are puffed
bigger than a hot air balloon!
One day, I'll become a rich girl for real!"
You stalked me?
Of course not!
I stayed close by you physically
without your consent
to bridge the gap between us spiritually!
That's called stalking, you fantasizing sicko!
But the I got the plot right,
didn't I, Your Flatness?
Don't call me that, you pervert!
And you're completely wrong!
AV Lab
I'm not working just because I want to become rich.
But you are taking on multiple jobs and do live in a normal apartment, right?
You're pretending to be an heiress using the money you worked so hard to earn.
You turn down anyone who asks you out.
Is looking down on people really that fun?
What, are you trying to teach me a lesson?
Why don't you just tell everyone, then?
What a water flea like you
does is no concern of mine.
If it bugs you, why not just say something?
I-It doesn't bug me at all!
I'm not going to tell anyone.
I just want to know more about you.
Everything I said in front of everyone...
I really meant it.
You've stolen something precious from me.
Seeing you smile innocently drives me crazy. I can't stand it.
How can you say something like that with a straight face?
Because I can only say how I really feel.
Enough.
So what do you want me to do?
Can we go on a date this Saturday?
A-A date?!
You're taking on too many jobs, Azuki Azusa.
I can't stand not being by my master's side!
Y-You come right out with
everything, don't you, pervert?
Can we?
W-Well, it is a master's responsibility to care for her pets.
Yay!
This Saturday!
What is the meaning of this?
Well, you know, Azuki Azusa's heiress
act is driving her into a corner.
She might see the joys of being a commoner and give up her facade if she goes on a date with me.
You just wanted to go on a date with Azuki-san, didn't you?
I see.
Huh? Did you hear anything I said?
I'll go on the date too.
Huh?
But...
I'm going.
Sorry!
Did I keep you waiting, Azuki Azusa?
O-Of course I wasn't waiting!
I'm not a baby sparrow waiting
for a meal, you know!
Then how about we
start with a little walk?
That's fine, I guess.
Here. "Ahn!"
Ahn!
So where are we going?
I was thinking of showing you the joys of being a commoner today!
I'm sure you'll like it!
Come on, let's go inside!
They've got A/C in there!
Azuki Azusa, I want you to know...
the happiness commoners feel,
being able to marry whoever they want!
Wh-What was that about?!
I wanted us to have a serious discussion about commoner marriage—
That's too soon!
Way too soon!
We aren't even close to that step!
I don't want to go through
the steps to reach it either!
Oh, good point! We should
go through all the steps.
After marriage comes...
Maternity
Clinic
Come on, let's go in!
I'm a man, you know!
I know how to take responsibility!
Until you understand the joy of making babies, we can have a nice, long—
What was that for?!
Pervert! Pervert! Pervert!
Stupid pervert!
Freak! Maniac! Rapist!
When?! When'd you do it?!
When I was sleeping?!
It was my first time!
My first time!
What's going to happen?!
What do I do?! What will you do?!
Honestly.
He's a horrible, womanizing,
lewd, hopeless pervert.
However...
Senpai would never do that.
Especially not to you.
T-Tsutsukakushi?
Huh?
Who are you?
Tsutsukakushi. First-year.
I begged Senpai to let me tail you.
You can't leave a hopeless
pervert unsupervised.
Just so you know, I know how much of a pervert he is. There's no problem here.
I don't think you realize
just how perverted he is.
Oh, really?
So you know how this pervert sniffs the napes of girls' necks as they sleep in the nurse's office?
I'd believe it, considering he showed me designs for his ideal school swimsuits.
And that he took those to the company that makes our school's swimsuits?
He's an unbelievably hopeless pervert.
How he can put in all that effort is beyond me!
G-Girls, please don't fight over me!
We're not fighting.
We are not fighting!
Yeah, you guys get along great.
Why do I have to come here with this pervert?
Come on, now.
It's hot outside.
And I thought you might enjoy entertainment for commoners.
Entertainment for commoners, huh?
Oh?
Why cyan't I gyet it?!
20 straight losses...
It's myay first time playing this!
I can't help it!
Here, take it.
Can I really?
Thank you!
No! Don't!
Don't be mean to them!
No! Stop! You'll rip them off!
I'm serious! Stop!
How was your first time at an arcade?
W-Well, I can't say it wasn't fun.
I even got a stuffed animal too.
Yeah!
Commoner entertainment is wonderful!
Commoner life is exciting!
Everything about being a commoner is fun!
Why are you so obsessed with that?
Do you want some?
"Ahn!"
Want more? You can have the rest.
Thank you very much.
Here, have another.
It's great how girls can become friends and start acting like sisters so fast.
Here.
Who are you calling friends?
Sure, I'm playing with her now,
but that's only because
I let you trick me into it.
Being friends is just a pain.
It gets in the way of living my life.
But we had so much fun together.
Wouldn't you say we're already friends?
I...
I'm going to the restroom.
She really is losing something
important thanks to her facade.
You can't blame her.
What kind of relationship someone has with others is a hard question for everyone.
Sometimes, I wish that my own sister could be someone like Azuki-san.
Tsutsukakushi?
What are you two doing?
Captain?! What are you doing here?!
The weekend was made for self-training.
I was giving some members of our team
some gentle guidance with regards to this.
Gentle?
More importantly, Yokodera, you were supposed to be recovering from a case of pervertitis.
Why are you with Tsukiko?
We're on a date.
What?! I didn't hear about this!
You never asked.
Um...
How do you two know each other?
Track Team Captain Tsutsukakushi Tsukushi.
She's my older sister.
Why did you choose my
sister for your rendezvous?
I-It's not like that, Captain!
Sure, it's a date, but there's another girl too...
Oh? You were two-timing?
Perhaps you care to elaborate?
It's none of your business, Nee-san.
None of my business, you say?
I hope you're ready.
Run!
You degenerate!
Tsutsukakushi!
Senpai...
Wait!
Sorry I took so... long...
Huh? Isn't that Li'l Bean?
Oh yeah, it's Li'l Bean!
Long time no see!
Like, how you been?
Hold on a second, Senpai.
No, I can't hold on!
Let's keep running together forever!
Ow!
That hurt, Tsutsukakushi!
You wouldn't have stopped
if I didn't hurt you.
There was no need to run from my sister.
But she was gonna kill me!
What about Azuki-san?
Azuki Azu—
We wanted to know if you, like, made new friends at your new school!
But, like, you're alone at an arcade, so it's, like, totally obvious!
I hope you didn't transfer because of us.
Why don't you, like, come back?
Yeah, yeah!
Like, we're waiting for you.
See you, Li'l Bean.
Let's, like, hang out again!
Um...
See? Just like I said.
We aren't friends.
So I was expecting anything out of you.
It's not like that!
I'm sorry we kind of ditched you, but some stuff happened.
Yeah. "Stuff" happens to everyone.
You had a different motive
behind this date, didn't you?
We didn't!
Well, we did, but...
We didn't.
There was another reason, but...
Well... stuff happened.
I understand.
You called it a date to get me to come.
You asked Tsutsukakushi-san to follow.
You made me put down my guard and run into people from my old school.
You planned it all like the sly snake you are.
That's what happened.
I knew you were just making fun of me.
You said we were friends and made me feel like we were.
Like an idiot.
No. I can tell you we weren't—
It's okay. I don't mind.
Everyone's a liar.
Why does everyone have to lie?
Never talk to me again.
The three of us are incomplete creatures.
Unable to express emotions.
Relying on a facade.
Lacking a facade.
None of us can be happy.
kimi ni baby sweet berry love
I'm in baby sweet berry love with you
honto no kimochi dake
It would be so nice if I could
wakeaetara ii no ni na
Share with you how I really feel
negai wo kanaete yo
Make my wish come true
c.u.t.e. funny cat
C-U-T-E funny cat
give me give me shiny time
Give me give me shiny time
p.r.e.t.ty
P-R-E-T-T-Y
tiny tiny berry love
A tiny, tiny berry love
daisuki no heart mo
My heart full of love for you
gomen ne no namida mo
And these tears because I'm sorry
honto wa sunao ni misetakute
I really wish I could just show them to you
tsutaetai omoi to
I want to tell you that I feel this way
uragaeshi no taido
But the opposite is what I always say
jouzu ni narenai
I just can't do it right
kokoro moyou
Expressing myself
doushite karamawari
Why can't I get on the ball?
mune ga gyutto naru
My chest feels so tight
chigau kyorikan ga
Feeling so close to you
modokashii yo nee
Frustrates me so much
todoketai no
I want you to know
kimi to baby sweet berry love
I want a baby sweet berry love with you
kitto gikochinakute
I know it'll be awkward
demo ne massugu ni mitsumete
But I want to look you straight in the eye
sorairo utsushitai
So you can see a clear blue sky
motto baby sweet berry love
I want a more baby sweet berry love
semete kimi no mae de wa
I wish that at least in front of you
waratte okotte afureta
I can smille and pout all I want
ari no mama de itai
I want to be myself
dakara baby sweet berry love
That's why baby sweet berry love
issho ni hajimeyou
Let's start together
Say It Before You Regret It
Next time: Say It Before You Regret It.