I don't want you to get the wrong idea.
I don't hate my sister.
We used to get along.
We took baths and slept together until my sister started middle school.
Then... why?
It's my fault.
After our parents died when we were young,
I stuck to my sister like glue.
Whenever I opened my mouth, it was
give me food, give me snacks,
play with me, stay with me.
I think it was when I graduated middle school.
My sister started to steer clear of me.
Pick up the pace! You're slowing down!
I thought that if I hid my expressions and stopped acting so childish,
we could go back to the way we were, but...
That's why Tsutsukakushi...
Hello, Azuki Azusa calling.
What is it?
Um...
I wanted to thank you, so...
Thank you.
You came to visit when I was sick, right?
And I really loved the stuffed turtle!
That's all! Okay, bye!
mou ikkai kocchi muite..
One more time, look this way
iitai koto ga motto aru kara..
There's still more that I want to tell you
mou ikkai kocchi muite..
One more time, look this way
honki ga yureru ai no future..
Who you love's going to change in the future
dakara kocchi muite..
That's why you should look this way
maware chikyuu koi wo nosete..
The world turns, filled with love
dakara kocchi muite..
That's why you should look this way
guuzen ja nai fantafuture..
It wasn't just chance, it's our fantastic future
watashi
kara
sasou
yuuki
wo
watashi kara sasou yuuki wo
To have the courage to ask you out myself
kudasai
to
tsuki ni
negau
no
kudasai to tsuki ni negau no
I wished on the moon that I could
setsunai
kokoro
ni
mahou
kaketemimashou
setsunai kokoro ni mahou kaketemimashou
Let's cast a little spell on that breaking heart
mirai
he
no
chikamichi
ne
mirai he no chikamichi ne
It's the fastest way to the future
amaku naare egao de
With a smile I'm making even sweeter
kimi yo tokechae
I'll make your whole self melt
kyou no yozora wo mitsume
Tonight I'll look at the sky
chotto senobite
And try to reach a little closer
mou ikkai kocchi muite..
One more time, look this way
iitai koto ga motto aru kara..
There's still more that I want to tell you
mou ikkai kocchi muite..
One more time, look this way
honki ga yureru ai no future..
Who you love's going to change in the future
dakara kocchi muite..
That's why you should look this way
maware chikyuu koi wo nosete..
The world turns, filled with love
dakara kocchi muite..
That's why you should look this way
guuzen ja nai fantafuture..
It wasn't just chance, it's our fantastic future
How to Bring Down  a Breezy King
Okay, here's your English, Geography,
Home Economics, World History, HPE, and Chinese Literature for today.
School Counselor
Be sure to do it all!
It's more work than a reindeer has on Christmas.
Too bad, isn't it?
You did so poorly on your finals that even Santa could faint.
Put the key back in the faculty room when you're done.
Remedials?
Looks pretty brutal.
Y-Yokodera...
Don't worry!
You're a chicken who can fly if she tries!
So that you can finish it
even a second sooner, I'll...
You'll...
...be praying for you!
Pr...
Oh, come on!
50 more laps!
Show me your spine!
How are you doing, Captain?
Oh, Yokodera?
Have you recovered from your pervertitis?
Yes. Thanks to you, I've fully recovered.
Wonderful. Then...
Your two-timing date with my sister at the arcade...
You're here to atone, I'm sure.
Um...
I let you go out of my heart's compassion,
but now that you've recovered, I needn't hesitate.
Um... Er...
I-I think the person you met was my...
younger twin brother!
Brother?
I never knew you had one.
It's a big secret from everyone!
There's a 1 in 256 chance that you'll encounter him!
You've got great luck, Captain!
It's like meeting a metal babble!
Metal? Babble?
Metal? Huh?
Metal doesn't go down very easily, does it?
My brother's really stubborn and babbles a lot!
We've got bad blood between us!
To two-time like that?
He's the scum of the Earth!
So it wasn't you?
Yes, exactly!
His younger brother did it.
His younger brother did it!
Repeat after me!
His younger brother did it?
I'm glad you understand!
It sucks having siblings, doesn't it?
I heard you didn't get along
with your sister either...
Who told you that?
Only a fool would believe something so absurd and baseless.
So you're saying you get along well with your sister?
I'm not saying we get along either way. I'm saying, "Don't pry."
But it seems your sister feels like—
Enough!
This is between her and me!
Could you tell me just one thing?
What do you think of your sister since she lost her expressions?
Expressions?
You know what they say about the stony cat, right?
Your sister prayed to the cat statue and lost her expressions.
What are you talking about?
That thing can't answer prayers.
But...
It's impossible.
Because I made that cat statue when I was young.
I see.
Nee-san remembered about the stony cat.
Once, when we were young, we got into a fight.
Nee-san made the statue to apologize.
We put the statue on a hill in our backyard,
and we promised to stay together forever.
It's a very precious memory to me.
Though I wish I could do it all over again.
I'll help you out.
We're partners in crime, after all.
And it's my turn to help you get your expressions back.
I'll do anything you need—
Senpai.
Hm?
Are you helping me just
to get my expressions back?
Of course!
You helped me get my facade back first, after all.
I see.
Yes, I see.
Senpai.
Are you free tomorrow?
There's something I'd like to buy.
Santa girls are cute.
Vampires and little witches are also good.
Oh, so you wanted to buy...
We thought the kids might like it if we dressed up for the next Youth Service Club Storytime.
I see.
Which do you prefer, Senpai?
The nurse outfit's pretty nice,
but I think swimsuits are the best.
You should wear clothes made of minimal material
to teach children the importance of environmental protection!
Stop climate change!
Just kidding!
You're right.
A swimsuit may be a good idea.
Was Tsutsukakushi the type to do this?
Oh, God, I'm so stupid!
She can't show her emotions!
I need to think about how she feels!
She didn't want to wear a swimsuit, but because I said she should...
I need to stop her!
Don't force yourself, Tsutsukakushi!
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'm not mad.
It's my own fault for letting my guard down.
You only did what was in your nature as a hopeless pervert.
Don't forgive me just like that!
I was seriously worried that I forced you into it!
Don't worry.
I'll be sure to use a fitting room with a lock next.
You still want to wear one?
Since I can't express emotions,
I'd like to make it up to the kids by wearing a nice costume.
I don't know much about cosplay,
but since you do, I'd like your advice.
Something about Tsutsukakushi today...
This strange feeling...
What is it?
When you said those hills were in your backyard,
I thought you might be rich, but...
See you again, Senpai.
Oh, yeah. Good night.
The day has eyes, the night has ears, and I have both!
I have undeniably witnessed your affair with my own eyes and ears!
Captain?!
No, I was just helping her shop for something today! It wasn't a date—
Silence!
Though my successor,
Yokodera, may have the right,
you have no right to call me "Captain"!
To even consider fooling me by claiming to be your elder twin is beyond reprehensible!
Surrender at once,
Yokodera's younger brother!
She believed me?!
I heard everything from your brother.
I see. You may look the same down to the inch, but I shan't be fooled again!
Regret that you ever laid your cheap hands upon my sister!
Sh-She liked it, so what's the problem?!
What?!
I—I mean, our relationship is none of your business!
You've got no right to butt into your sister's life!
It's none of your business!
I have reason to meddle in Tsukiko's affairs.
I intend...
to end our relationship as sisters.
End your relationship as sisters?
It makes perfect sense when you consider the future.
Apart from exams for college,
I need to start thinking about marriage and similar matters.
Marriage?
But before that, I must end my current relationship with my sister.
How she laughs, cries, and panics so easily...
The very idea of being related to her by blood irks me to no end.
And so, I—
What'd you just say?!
Laughing and crying?!
You don't know what Tsutsukakushi's going through right now!
Just shut up, stupid!
S-Stupid?!
Whoever calls someone stupid is stupid, stupid!
You're stupid, so I called you stupid, stupid!
Tsutsukakushi prayed to the cat statue to lose her expressions for your sake!
Take a hint, damn it!
Naturally, I noticed that Tsukiko has changed!
But it is not because of the cat statue.
Tsukiko is hiding her emotions of her own will in order to grow up.
Once she grows up, I can
graduate and marry in peace.
What are you...
If that sort of idle gossip
should continue to spread,
perhaps I should just destroy the statue with my own hands.
Honestly. Believing stupid rumors—
You!
So you've come to?
Nee-san stomped off somewhere in a rage.
Did you hear all of that?
Nee-san thought just what I thought she would.
You don't need to be concerned about me.
Of course I'd be!
She said she wanted to end
your relationship as sisters!
She said she'd destroy the statue!
She doesn't care about you at all!
The cat statue belongs to my sister.
If she wants to destroy it,
I have no right to stop her.
And...
I never needed my expressions in the first place.
If I regain my expressions, my sister will hate me more than she already does.
If I stay this way, I'm sure...
But that's...
That's just totally wrong!
You needed your facade, Senpai.
How is that any different from me?
It's completely different!
You'll live without expressions for the sake of a sister like that?!
It's hard to live when you can't show emotions! You said so yourself!
It's okay. As long as you understand.
It's not just my problem!
It is just your problem.
What are you to me, Senpai?
What?
What is your relation to me, Senpai?
We're partners in crime
to regain your expressions.
Then what will happen when I regain them?
I won't have any reason to see you at school or on the weekends.
My sister will hate me.
I'll be all alone.
That's not...
I'll do anything it takes to stay with you.
But it's no good if I'm the only one who feels that way.
Because you have Azuki-san.
What?
Azuki Azusa and I are friends. Nothing more and nothing less.
Maybe now.
But in the future...
You and Azuki-san make a good couple.
If I were to regain my expressions,
I'll have no connection to you anymore.
Senpai, tell me.
Once we're no longer partners,
what will you be to me?
You're terrible!
Why didn't you say anything?!
Why are you mad at me?
Because Tsutsukakushi-san and I are fr—rivals!
Rivals? In what?
That doesn't matter.
Right now, Tsutsukakush-san's way more—
Can you do me a favor?
What are you going to do with her sister's career consultation?
I'm going to show Tsutsukakushi that not getting her expressions back is stupid.
To do that, I need to bring down the Steel King no matter what.
So...
Don't you have anything else to say?
Oh, right.
You're so nice, Azuki Azusa.
Almost like a fluffy sheep's wool—
That's not what I mean.
I don't care for cheap words anyone can say.
I want to hear how you really feel.
How I feel?
I...
Tsutsukakushi is more important to me than anything.
I want to help Tsutsukakushi Tsukiko in any way I can.
Please, help me.
See? You can say it.
Yokodera's younger brother.
Do you really think you can defeat me in a duel?
Duel
Hmph!
I'm not—
Don't think I'll go down like I did yesterday!
What?
Stony Cat! Take away my tendency to get embarrassed and run away!
Behold!
I offered my underwear and lost my sense of shame!
Steel King!
I challenge you to a duel over Tsutsukakushi Tsukiko!
Over Tsukiko?!
What is Tsukiko to you?!
I can say it now!
Tsukiko-chan is my precious...
precious...
Little Sister
little sister!
Huh?
I will win this duel and officially be Tsukiko-chan's older brother!
I love Tsukiko-chan!
As an older brother!
You make no sense!
I've navigated through all the events!
I got on top of Tsukiko-chan,
and she got on top of me!
I've even seen her in her birthday suit!
Oh?
And that makes you her brother?!
How indecent!
Resorting to violence because
you can't win with words!
Fool!
You dare say you love her with only that?
When we were young, we counted each others moles in the bath!
She had a mole in a very strange place.
Oh, and I've washed bedsheets she's wet too.
Bed wetting?!
We even fought over how
to split a meat bun once.
That was why I gave her the cat statue.
Tsukiko and I have gotten
along wonderfully ever since.
Liar!
You said it as though you still love Tsukiko!
Naturally!
I obviously love my adorable little Tsukiko more than you!
Oh. I see.
For now, the two of you
should either apologize to me
or pull your tongues out.
I ran here to stop a duel.
To think I'd feel such shame.
I'm sorry.
Regardless,
do you really still love me, Nee-san?
Y-Yeah. Yeah?
Don't let her fool you, Tsukiko-chan!
Look at this!
It's her career consultation survey!
The Steel King is going to Massachusetts after she graduates!
Colleges
(School name, major, minor)
Priority
School Name
First Choice
Second Choice
Massachusetts University
Abandoning your sister and going overseas is inexcusable!
Why do you want to go to America?
You can't even write the alphabet.
The school in Massachusetts has an excellent track program,
and I'm learning English using a learn-while-you-sleep pillow.
She lies!
She wanted to end your relationship as sisters!
She's got something more evil planned! I know it!
Now! Tell us what the real reason is!
Nee-san.
I-It's to fulfill my promise with you.
Promise?
We vowed on the cat statue that
through joy and sorrow, sickness and health,
we'd be together forever.
That's why I...
I wanna marry Tsukiko!
Gay marriage is legal in the state of Massachusetts!
We're ending our relationship as sisters, marrying, and living in happiness till death do us part!
I've heard that brides must go through something called "marriage blues" before the marriage!
That's why I pretended to fight with her,
though it pained my heart to do so!
Your losing your expressions is a part of the marriage blues, right?
I don't know where to start.
Blood sisters can't get married even if they aren't legally family.
Though that's not the biggest problem.
What'd you say?!
But what about my perfect lovey-dovey plan?!
It was flawed from the start.
Then why did you get the marriage blues?!
Because of someone other than me?!
You can't do that! You can't do that! You can't do that!
I didn't get the marriage blues.
I lost my expressions to the stony cat.
What?
Now that you mention it, I think I heard something like that...
Like a whisper in my wise mind...
Yeah, I told you.
Oh, I see.
That's great.
That's not great!
Cat statue!
Return Tsukiko's expressions at once!
If you don't, I shall drop the hammer and mercilessly dispend indiscriminate justice!
Nee-san.
We can't get married,
but maybe we can eat meat buns like we used to.
You're not mad?
I'm not.
But it's easy to misunderstand you.
You should show your feelings and emotions on your face more.
So could you eat this?
Like you used to.
Sure.
I don't really understand, but you're giving me the whole bun?
You've sure grown, Tsukiko.
Wait, that meat bun!
Tsutsukakushi's expressions are in that meat bun.
It's okay.
She's the only sister I have.
B-But you don't need to sacrifice yourself for someone like her.
I love my sister, despite her flaws.
And so, Tsutsukakushi's expressions had yet to return
as our summer drew to a close.
The stony cat lost its power.
I tried praying several times,
but my underwear never came back.
Looks like summer vacation ends tomorrow.
Huh?
Tsukiko-chan, don't you feel kinda sad?
About the passing of another short summer,
and the season for swimsuits.
Please stop calling me that.
Pervert.
Huh? Why not?
"Tsukiko-chan" is standard on a prim and proper little sister route!
I'd rather initiate Armageddon than have you as a brother.
You really don't like it?!
This is far enough.
Huh? Why don't I take you all the way home?
Well then, Senpai.
Good-bye.
Her actions since that day gave me the feeling
that she was keeping her distance from me.
We'll have even fewer chances
to talk once school starts again...
But before I had a chance to think about it,
something so unbelievable happened that it vanished from my mind.
No way...
How is this even possible?
My house...
My house is gone!
kimi ni baby sweet berry love
I'm in baby sweet berry love with you
hontou no kimochi dake
It would be so nice if I could
Share with you how I really feel
wakeaetara ii no ni na
negai wo kanaete yo
Make my wish come true
silky vanilla
Silky vanilla
kimi kimi sunny time
You, you, sunny time
p-r-e-t-t-y
Pretty
tiny tiny berry love
A tiny, tiny berry love
daisuki na heart mo
My heart full of love for you
gomen ne no namida mo
And these tears because I'm sorry
hontou wa sunao ni misetakute
I really wish I could just show them to you
tsutaetai yo motto
I want to tell you more openly
uragaeshi wa dantou
But doing the opposite is who I am
jouzu ni narenai
I just can't do it right
kokoro moyou
Expressing myself
doushite karamawari
Why can't I get on the ball?
mune ga gyutto naru
My chest feels so tight
chigau kyorikan
Feeling so far from you
modokashii yo ne
Just frustrates me so much
todoketai no
I want you to see them
kimi to baby sweet berry love
I want a baby sweet berry love with you
kitto gikochinakute
I know it'll be awkward
demo ne massugu ni mitsumete
But I want to look you straight in the eye
sorairo utsushitai
So you can see a clear blue sky
motto baby sweet berry love
I want a more baby sweet berry love
semete kimi no mae de wa
I wish that at least in front of you
waratte okotte afureta
I can smille and pout all I want
ari no mama de itai
I want to be myself
dakara baby sweet berry love
That's why baby sweet berry love
issho ni hajimeyou
Let's start together
Good-bye My Home
Next time: Good-bye My Home.