I knew it from the start.
I'm not surprised at all.
It's not the pervert's fault.
If...
If anyone's at fault,
it's me.
mou ikkai kocchi muite..
One more time, look this way
iitai koto ga motto aru kara..
There's still more that I want to tell you
mou ikkai kocchi muite..
One more time, look this way
honki ga yureru ai no future..
Who you love's going to change in the future
dakara kocchi muite..
That's why you should look this way
maware chikyuu koi wo nosete..
The world turns, filled with love
dakara kocchi muite..
That's why you should look this way
guuzen ja nai fantafuture..
It wasn't just chance, it's our fantastic future
watashi
kara
sasou
yuuki
wo
watashi kara sasou yuuki wo
To have the courage to ask you out myself
kudasai
to
tsuki ni
negau
no
kudasai to tsuki ni negau no
I wished on the moon that I could
setsunai
kokoro
ni
mahou
kaketemimashou
setsunai kokoro ni mahou kaketemimashou
Let's cast a little spell on that breaking heart
mirai
he
no
chikamichi
ne
mirai he no chikamichi ne
It's the fastest way to the future
amaku naare egao de
With a smile I'm making even sweeter
kimi yo tokechae
I'll make your whole self melt
kyou no yozora wo mitsume
Tonight I'll look at the sky
chotto senobite
And try to reach a little closer
mou ikkai kocchi muite..
One more time, look this way
iitai koto ga motto aru kara..
There's still more that I want to tell you
mou ikkai kocchi muite..
One more time, look this way
honki ga yureru ai no future..
Who you love's going to change in the future
dakara kocchi muite..
That's why you should look this way
maware chikyuu koi wo nosete..
The world turns, filled with love
dakara kocchi muite..
That's why you should look this way
guuzen ja nai fantafuture..
It wasn't just chance, it's our fantastic future
A 100% Girl
Senpai, are you fighting with Azuki-san?
Huh?
No, not really...
It's that time of year again, when the sweet aroma of olives fills the air.
Unfortunately, the Azuki Azusa Problem is also in the air.
Ever since then, she hasn't answered my calls or texts.
She's just watches me from the distant shadows.
But if I try to approach her, she runs away at full speed.
Zoom
Ahem.
We're setting up for the athletics festival today, huh?
And where there's athletics,
there's a swimsuit paradise!
I can't wait for those passionate battles in the pool!
Are you trying to change the subject?
Tsutsukakushi, what events are you in?
Ts-Tsukiko, what individual events are you participating in?
The eating race.
What events are you in, Senpai?
The relay with the track team.
The girls won't practice with me, though. It's a bit of a problem.
Oh, that's right.
All girls born after you on this blue planet hate you more than anything.
Y-Yeah.
It's that bad?
The only one who gets along with you is me.
Soon, I'll hit a growth spurt.
Once I grow up, I win.
I see.
Um... Tsutsukakushi-san?
I suddenly have free time today.
I was thinking of helping someone practice.
I wonder if there's anyone here who needs help.
Uh...
Then could you help me practice?
If you insist, I might be able to help you.
I insist.
Ts-Tsukiko, please?
I guess I can, Yo-Yoko-Yoko...
Youto-kun...
Huh?
...senpai. What a nice breeze.
And such nice weather.
Today is going to be a beautiful day.
Fire!
Onii-chan?
Onii-chan.
Onii-chan!
What'd you call me?
Oh Lord, a beautiful, 100-percent smile!
You seem to know each other very well,
Yokodera-san.
No, this is all a misunderstanding.
Guess who!
Uh...
Who?
You don't know?
Sorry. No idea.
Um...
I really don't know her!
I've never seen her before, so I'm definitely not her—
Make it work out for now.
Huh?
Unini?!
Hey, Emi.
I keep telling you to stop causing people problems.
Let go of me, Onii-chan!
Huh?
Is she your sister?
Yeah.
She's my sister, Emanuela Pollarola.
We call her Emi at home.
She went to live in Italy for a while.
She just got back yesterday.
Um, um...
I'm Emi!
I'm his sister!
My dream is to make breakfast for Youto Onii-chan every day!
I see.
Nice to meet you.
My name is Tsutsukakushi Tsukiko.
Tsutsukakiku? Tsutsukinoko?
Tsu... Tsutsutsu...
Okay!
Tsu-chan!
Tsutsukakushi.
I'm one year younger than your brother.
Emanuela Pollarola-san.
Nice to meet you, Tsu-chan!
Grr.
Tsu-chan, Tsu-chan, Tsu-chan!
Actually, Yoko Nono, she keeps saying she wants to check out our high school.
But I don't have a minute to spare today.
Sorry, but Tsutsukakushi and I—
Just this once?
I love you, Youto Onii-chan!
Her smile is just 100-percent perfect!
Hello, is this the police?
I'd like to submit information regarding a loli-pedo hybrid pervert.
Who are you talking about and why does he sound kind of cool?!
Just kidding.
You should have told me she was your friend's sister.
Why don't you show her around our school?
Uh... But...
Practice for the athletics festival...
I'll be waiting for you at school.
Take your time.
Sure it's okay?
You can take her back after a little tour, right?
So, what do you want to see first, Emi?
But it has to be somewhere I can make a quick getaway.
Um, um!
The music room!
Do you like music?
A little.
I'm still pretty pumpkin at it.
But, but!
What I wanna see most is the pool!
Really?
Me too.
We're setting up for the athletics festival today,
so non-team students should have access too.
According to my research, the girls should be there...
Unini?
Youto Onii-chan, you know so much!
You can call me the Swimsuit Professor!
Yay! Yay!
Swimsuit! Swimsuit! Swimsuit!
Hey, Pervert.
Uwargh!
"Uwargh," what?
How rude.
Hurry up and die.
Sorry—
Wait, wasn't that ruder than me?
Shut up. Silence.
First, the Captain. Now, a girl too young to resist you?
Your desire to rape is so incredibly large that it crosses national borders, Pervert.
Hurry up and die!
Die, now!
Die, and on the third day rise again, only to die once more!
Your demands are getting harder to fulfill by the second.
What's "rape"?
It's when the pervert takes a diamond drill and forcefully updates your body.
It hurts very much.
So I've heard.
Hey!
It hurts?
So you've heard?
So you don't know?
I can imagine.
The pervert is violent and clumsy.
He spreads open your legs and, suddenly, plunges his dynamite drill into your diamond...
Darn.
Phew. That was close.
Youto Onii-chan, does everyone at school call you a pervert?
Are you a pervert from the roots up?
Well, you could say the Vice-Captain has a bit of a beef with me.
You're not a super popular guy that everyone loves?
Um...
High school's a lot boringer than I thought.
This is totally different from what I used to imagine!
Used to?
It's so boring!
Boring! Boring!
I don't like boring!
Emi...
So it'd be better if it was funner!
Is that...
Make Youto Onii-chan a lot cooler!
And make everyone want to go to the pool too!
And make the school and everyone in it fun and exciting!
Emi!
Huh?
Vice-Captain
It's the Vice-Captain's bra!
Onii-chan, pass!
Catch!
Nice brassiere! Return!
Hey, Prince.
Prince?
Me?
Yeah.
To forever be young at heart is cool.
There are times when I want to play catch too.
I understand.
You used underwear that happened to be there for a ball.
Give me your hand.
This is easier to throw. Use it next time.
Give it back when you're done.
Something weird's going—
Swimsuits are the best!
Thank God for wedgies!
Hey there, Prince!
Looking good today!
Totally!
Every part of my body starts feeling good when I see you!
Lewd guy, our Princey-pie!
Youto Onii-chan, is high school fun?
It's the funnest thing ever!
I knew it, Youto Onii-chan!
I can't wait for the athletics festival!
Let's go to the pool you love!
I wanna learn how to be a swimsuit professor just like you!
It's better if you don't.
To be a swimsuit professor,
you must first spend 400 days in a single year doing squats by the pool!
No! I wanna! I wanna! I wanna!
If you insist, we can swing by the track.
There's a girl there called Miss Steel. If you tell her,
"I want to try out this club. I'd like the same training routine as Yokodera."
What happens then?
Miss Steel will be very happy.
You can become a swimsuit professor too.
Maybe.
Yay! I'll try it!
Damn. Stupid useless pumpkin.
Huh? Did you say something?
Mind if I sit here?
Go ahead.
Want some?
Shouldn't you be showing Emanuela-san around?
I left her with Miss Steel.
A-And...
I kind of wanted to eat lunch with you, Tsukiko.
I see.
Would you like to try some of my pasta?
Thanks.
Sorry if I'm wrong, but...
Do you not like Emi very much?
I have a hypothetical situation for you.
Imagine for a moment that you played tennis.
Okay.
One day, your partner for doubles says,
"I don't want to be a team with you.
I don't want to be stuck on you like glue.
I'd rather feel excited because we don't see each other all the time."
And so, you practiced your heart out in the hopes of standing on the same court one day.
But then, soon after, your partner formed a doubles team with someone else
and went completely ga-ga from getting called "Onii-chan." What would you think?
Um... Is that...
Just a hypothetical situation.
What would you think?
"I've been had," I guess.
That's how I feel right now.
Um...
I guess...
Sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
She smells like an unfair, rule-breaking evil woman to me.
And for some reason, I don't like it.
If you don't want to believe me, then don't.
Whoever you decide to be in a relationship with, it's none of my business.
A relationship?
Emi's just a little girl. I'd never even imagine of having one with her.
I see.
I'd want a big girl who's big here and there!
Ow!
You really are a hopeless per—
Per—
Prince.
You're a prince.
Huh? Why does that feel new?
I should pick up Emi soon.
Why don't you come with me?
Maybe I will.
They say modern warfare begins with reconnaissance.
Right.
Now let's go.
Everest is taller than I imagined.
Oh, Yokodera.
Today's practice is about to end.
Whoa!
Emi, you okay?
Being a swimsuit professor is so hard.
Huh?
Why is she here?
I'm going home now!
See you later, Youto Onii-chan!
Azuki Azusa?
Red light! Green light!
No! Stop!
Let go of me!
Hey, wait! Calm down!
If you do anything rough, I won't like you any—
No! You pervert! You beast!
Calm down! I just want to talk!
Mama! Mama!
Prince.
Pervert! Stupid! Stupid! Stupid Pervert!
Doing things so suddenly is bad.
Mama!
I think it's very bad.
Have you calmed down?
Why aren't you wearing a swimsuit, Azuki-san?
I'm not wearing a swimsuit!
He'll do weird things to me!
This pervert will!
Pervert?
Isn't he a prince?
Everyone's so weird today!
The pervert is a pervert.
A pervert who'll stare at anyone wearing a swimsuit.
But a pervert who didn't go to Okinawa!
So much of a pervert that a panda could see it's black and white!
A dirty pervert who'd foul up a bird's nest when it leaves!
Pervert...
A lying pervert, betraying
all the bunnies he bluffs!
Prince...
A transforming pervert like a fox!
Pervert...
Prince...
A traitorous pervert who'll
change his shape like a bat!
Pervert...
Pervert.
Pervert! He's a pervert! A total pervert!
He was a pervert.
He is a pervert.
Because he's a pervert.
Why are you wearing a swimsuit?
Why? Because it's our uniform.
That's a swimsuit.
This is a uniform.
Understand?
Eek.
Found it!
I knew it.
It's behind all this.
Another wish was granted.
Or so it appears, prince.
No. A pervert in prince's clothing.
Yeah. Someone must have—
You've been caught red-handed.
Huh?
The cat god did three things this time.
One, you were treated like a prince.
Two, our uniforms became swimsuits.
And three, school became fun and exciting.
Do you understand?
Prince, swimsuits, school.
Only one person benefits from this.
The prince.
I didn't wish for this!
No excuses.
Cancel the wish before I get revenge for having my swimsuit-show-off plan ruined.
It really hurts to have Tsutsukakushi doubting me.
But it really does look like a world made just for me.
Stop, Yokodera!
Suicide's not the answer!
I'm here for you!
Don't even think of jumping!
I wasn't going to!
Tsukiko told me everything.
She said that all the evidence points to you.
But even so, I'll believe you!
C-Captain!
So... That's what I said.
Could you indirectly tell your younger brother that I said that?
Huh?
No, uh, indirectly, okay? Indirectly.
Like, "Captain Tsutsukakushi's so nice,"
or, "She's so reliable,"
or, "She's worthy of being your future mate,"
or, "Make it a traditional Shinto wedding."
Um... Could we get on the same page here?
What?
You won't tell him?
That's not nice, you know!
That sounded cute, but you're still threatening me!
Don't tell me that you said you'd believe me to get to my brother—
Wh-What are you saying?! Wh-Where's the evidence for that?!
I'll never believe anyone again.
That's not it.
I have other reasons not to doubt you.
The old gym over there.
It looks just like the Colosseum in Rome.
The ruins throughout campus and the Palatine Hill.
The swimming pool has to be the Blue Grotto on Capri.
You know a lot about Italy.
I planned to move to Italy once.
It was over ten years ago.
Our father was from Italy, it seems.
Tsukiko doesn't remember,
but on nights when she couldn't sleep,
I would pull out the photographs and we would imagine the faraway land.
This scenery reminds me of those warm nights from back then.
So...
So I think this might be my wish.
Is this situation my fault?
Or is it someone else's?
She smells like an unfair, rule-breaking evil woman to me.
I want to discover the truth.
And to discover it...
Captain...
And to discover it, I'm going to your house tomorrow morning!
Huh?
And you, your brother, and I will have a happy family meeting, just the three of us!
Oh, how adorable!
Is this kindergartener your younger brother?
Y-Yeah.
This elementary schooler looks like you, but it's actually your brother!
What makes her think that that isn't me?
It's too bad your brother couldn't be here,
but it's become quite the unexpected harvest!
Hey, why are you taking them out?
Oh, um, my hand moved on its own.
Um... Because of love, I guess.
That's not an excuse.
This looks like Emi.
And the boy holding the rabbit beside her...
Oh, that's Ponta.
Emi's brother.
He loves his bunny Yaji-san so much,
almost like a little sister...
What's wrong?
His sister Emi...
But Yaji-san...
Emi his bunny?
Yaji-san his sister?
That's right! Ponta's "sister" was Yaji-san, his bunny!
Then Emi...
Um, um!
Onii-chan, let's promise!
When I come back...
kimi ni baby sweet berry love
I'm in baby sweet berry love with you
honto no kimochi dake
It would be so nice if I could
wakeaetara ii no ni na
Share with you how I really feel
negai wo kanaete yo
Make my wish come true
c.u.t.e. funny cat
C-U-T-E funny cat
give me give me shiny time
Give me give me shiny time
p.r.e.t.ty
P-R-E-T-T-Y
tiny tiny berry love
A tiny, tiny berry love
daisuki no heart mo
My heart full of love for you
gomen ne no namida mo
And these tears because I'm sorry
honto wa sunao ni misetakute
I really wish I could just show them to you
tsutaetai omoi to
I want to tell you that I feel this way
uragaeshi no taido
But the opposite is what I always say
jouzu ni narenai
I just can't do it right
kokoro moyou
Expressing myself
doushite karamawari
Why can't I get on the ball?
mune ga gyutto naru
My chest feels so tight
chigau kyorikan ga
Feeling so close to you
modokashii yo nee
Frustrates me so much
todoketai no
I want you to know
kimi to baby sweet berry love
I want a baby sweet berry love with you
kitto gikochinakute
I know it'll be awkward
demo ne massugu ni mitsumete
But I want to look you straight in the eye
sorairo utsushitai
So you can see a clear blue sky
motto baby sweet berry love
I want a more baby sweet berry love
semete kimi no mae de wa
I wish that at least in front of you
waratte okotte afureta
I can smille and pout all I want
ari no mama de itai
I want to be myself
dakara baby sweet berry love
That's why baby sweet berry love
issho ni hajimeyou
Let's start together
The Happy Prince
Next time: The Happy Prince.