Even while imprisoned, the Irish author
Oscar Wilde, a pervert who I respect, said,
"I don't regret for a single moment having lived for pleasure."
Suppose we took a poll of what women's swimsuit is most attractive.
What style would come out on top?
I ponder eternal questions such as this every day.
Among the myriad varieties of swimsuits,
the racerback is particularly enticing.
I arrived at this conclusion in July of my second year of high—
Hey, Yokodera.
The unquestioned sovereign who rules over us, the captain of the track team,
the Steel King!
It's not what you think!
I wasn't peeping on purpose!
It was all just coincidence!
No, an accident!
No, a conspiracy!
I've been framed!
What sort of nonsense are you spouting?
I have something important to announce.
I've decided that you're worthy of being my successor.
I'm telling you, I'm innocent—
Wait, successor?
I hereby declare...
that Yokodera Youto will
succeed me as team captain!
Wh-Why him?
Yokodera Youto.
Since you joined the team,
you haven't missed practice even once,
and in your passion, you've done
squats every day to improve yourself.
No, that was...
...all to see those girls in swimsuits for even a second longer.
The rest of you must find an unconditional love and respect for track as he has—
Captain! I'm afraid you're making a big mistake!
Oh?
Um, well, you see...
There's something more
important to me than track,
And that something is swimsuits.
and it's kind of like what I live for, so...
More important than track?
Please, elaborate in detail.
I didn't join the track team because I liked or hated track or anything.
I just...
Oh God! At this rate, all my time's
going to be wasted on being captain!
If I don't tell the truth now, I'll regret it for the rest of my life!
I was born to be your successor, Captain!
Words could never express
what an honor this is!
I humbly accept!
mou ikkai kocchi muite..
One more time, look this way
iitai koto ga motto aru kara..
There's still more that I want to tell you
mou ikkai kocchi muite..
One more time, look this way
honki ga yureru ai no future..
Who you love's going to change in the future
dakara kocchi muite..
That's why you should look this way
maware chikyuu koi wo nosete..
The world turns, filled with love
dakara kocchi muite..
That's why you should look this way
guuzen ja nai fantafuture..
It wasn't just chance, it's our fantastic future
watashi
kara
sasou
yuuki
wo
watashi kara sasou yuuki wo
To have the courage to ask you out myself
kudasai
to
tsuki ni
negau
no
kudasai to tsuki ni negau no
I wished on the moon that I could
setsunai
kokoro
ni
mahou
kaketemimashou
setsunai kokoro ni mahou kaketemimashou
Let's cast a little spell on that breaking heart
mirai
he
no
chikamichi
ne
mirai he no chikamichi ne
It's the fastest way to the future
amaku naare egao de
With a smile I'm making even sweeter
kimi yo tokechae
I'll make your whole self melt
kyou no yozora wo mitsume
Tonight I'll look at the sky
chotto senobite
And try to reach a little closer
mou ikkai kocchi muite..
One more time, look this way
iitai koto ga motto aru kara..
There's still more that I want to tell you
mou ikkai kocchi muite..
One more time, look this way
honki ga yureru ai no future..
Who you love's going to change in the future
dakara kocchi muite..
That's why you should look this way
maware chikyuu koi wo nosete..
The world turns, filled with love
dakara kocchi muite..
That's why you should look this way
guuzen ja nai fantafuture..
It wasn't just chance, it's our fantastic future
The Pervert and the Stony Cat
It just means that hottie thinks
you've got a future ahead of you.
It's a good thing!
That's not the problem here.
I've always made excuses for stuff off the top of my head.
Oh?
Like you're always putting up a facade?
I want to be able to fantasize about girls all day, every day!
I don't want to be on the team,
let alone be captain!
I want to spend the rest of
my life surrounded by girls!
Yeah, sounds like you're going to waste your life on earthly desires.
Yokodera, I have something
I want to pass on to you.
Oh my God!
Dong in the
New Year:
The Complete
Collection
The legendary Dong in the New Year: The Complete Collection!
The elusive Street corner swimsuits collection!
Street corner
swimsuits
And all these enticing yellow 18+ stickers!
You should know better than to take gems like these out in public!
Well, you see...
I've outgrown the way of the adult.
What are you talking about, Ponta?!
We swore that we would dedicate our
lives to our hopes and dreams! To girls!
Have you forgotten our vow?!
Look, lady-killer.
There are millions of children out there
dealing with circumstances worse than ours.
As a fellow human being,
I can't allow such injustice.
I ask this favor as your oldest friend!
Take these off my hands for 100 yen!
100 yen?!
100 yen can give a child 40
liters of clean drinking water.
It'll bring us a step closer to world peace!
Ponta, what's got into you?
You know the Stony Cat Statue on Lone Cedar Hill?
The Stony Cat.
If you present it an offering,
it will give something you don't need to someone who does need it.
I always thought I'd end up dead in a ditch somewhere if I didn't change.
The Legendary Body Pillow
Margaret-san of the Icy Eyes
If there's anything I didn't need, it'd be my earthly desires.
So, I offered it a useless body pillow, and what do you know!
Good-bye, earthly desires!
My mind's clear as a sage's!
Full speed ahead! Next stop, world peace!
Wishing itself is free.
Something I don't need? My instinctive facade.
The Legendary Body Pillow
Barbara-san of the Flaming Cape
Thanks to my facade, I can't live freely.
I want to think about girls even more.
I want to see even more girls in different situations!
Under their skirts and above! I want to see it all!
I want to get friendlier with girls!
It doesn't look too friendly.
I can't unbuckle it.
A pervert!
Wait! Stop!
It's a misunderstanding!
There's no misunderstanding or corpse!
I didn't see anything!
That's my story and I'm sticking to it!
Is it really?!
I get the feeling you'll be telling
someone else a different story later!
Of course!
All the policemen in Japan are on my side!
You've got it all wrong!
If we slowly, carefully, and tenderly talk things over, I'm sure you'll understand!
No! Not a chance!
You need to be in love to do that!
I don't think we're on the same page here!
I don't want it gentle or rough!
I don't want it gently or rough!
I'm screwed enough as it is!
Just listen to me! You're making a mistake!
Ow...
I'm not tasty at all.
I'm weak and flat.
There's nothing underneath.
I was at the bottom of my class for the yearly physical check-up.
I'm sure I'll be tastier in
two years, so until then...
I want to stay pure until then!
Let me explain.
Barbara-san is just a body pillow.
I'm innocent.
I've never even hit on a girl before.
I'm completely pure.
If you're safe and pure,
could you please get off of me?
Uh... Sure.
Um, I didn't mean to scare you.
It just...
sort of happened.
I'm sorry.
We're sorry.
What was that supposed to be?
Even the way you apologize is perverted.
Oh, I see. So it's your facade?
Yeah.
I was going to ask the statue about it.
It sounds like that rumor's really getting around.
Thanks.
By the way, in my family, when a girl is shamed by a man, the man has to take responsibility.
I hope you're prepared.
What?!
It was a joke.
You didn't need to sound so disappointed.
No, that was my facade kicking in.
I actually couldn't be happier!
So you'll take responsibility, then?
Um...
It was a joke.
You really can't control that facade of yours, huh?
Sorry.
Why did you come here?
I want to be more mature.
I'm quick to lose my temper and cry.
I want to be able to be able to control emotions.
I think girls are cute when you can tell whether they're happy or sad.
You're wrong!
That's just being childish!
Really?
Why don't we try praying together?
Please help me to stop putting up a front, dodging questions, and telling lies.
Please help me not show my emotions on my face.
What was that?
Huh?
Did you eat another meat bun?
No, only the one you gave me.
I see.
One of the meat buns I was
saving for later is missing.
You're going to eat more?
Barbara-san's belt is gone!
I'll have to hug it home now.
Oh, but it'll be good practice for bringing girls home in my arms!
You really are a pervert.
W-Well, looks like nothing happened.
Wanna leave?
Yes.
We were too reckless.
While we did pray to the statue,
we also made light of the Stony Cat's power.
Summer's all about those bra lines showing through blouses sticking to girls' backs!
The stimulating scent of sweat is in the air!
You've got your pedal to the metal this morning!
Azuki-san! I love you! I love you so much!
Oh, looks like another episode of Azuki Azusa's Service Time.
I love you with all my soul!
Please, go out with me!
Who is she?
You seriously don't know?
She transferred here this spring.
She's a knockout. There's always someone trying to woo her.
I didn't know.
I'm usually at morning practice.
Oh, right, what happened—
Go out with you, huh?
Well?
Even flamingos do a courtship dance.
I hope you have something else to show me.
Are words all you have to offer? Even a parrot can speak.
Show me how you feel
through your actions.
I'm not asking you to chauffeur me in a Rolls-Royce and roll out a red carpet at the school gates.
But if I were to call for you, morning or night,
would you drop everything and come running?
Are you willing to throw away everything and obey me like a blind sheep?
See? You won't.
Th...
Thank you very much.
That's an heiress for you!
Azuki Azusa is a natural-born heiress or something.
She's in top form today!
She can give me a piece of her mind any day!
She takes class distinctions to the extreme.
She turns guys down hard.
Guys with certain tastes call it "Azuki Azusa's Service Time."
She can act snobbish all she wants!
She's still as flat as a board!
Huh?
What's going on?
What I thought came right out!
Oh my...
You have an amusing way with words.
Almost as amusing as being
bitten by an untrained dog.
But now that I've seen them
up close, they really are...
Perhaps you'd like to go on a little walk with me?
D-Don't worry!
I love 'em big,
but some people consider
flatness to be a status symbol!
And if you're flat, you don't need to buy new bras!
And they'll never sag!
In fact, there's nothing there that can sag!
You're one lucky girl! Viva, flat chests!
E-Excuse me!
You seem to be enjoying yourself.
Who are you? Don't meddle in my business!
Silence!
You are the one meddling my business.
This man will now choose
between life and death.
Dead or die.
Dead... or... die?
Talk about lucky. I've got two girls fighting over me. It's like a dream come true.
Yokodera.
Why didn't you come to
practice this morning?
Well, a few things happened last night, I overslept, and...
Don't look at her while she's dressed like that!
Don't look!
What are you mumbling to yourself about?
Why are you wearing track shorts, Captain?!
What happened to your short tights?!
You're killing every adolescent's BDSM fetishism!
Take them off now!
And put on your short tights now!
You brainless fool!
Per... vert...
And that's how I came to be known as the Pervert Prince.
Catch ya later, Pervert Prince!
I hope I never end up like him!
Oh, the misery.
Why does everything I think
come out my mouth?
Damn it!
I'll need to get out those old idol
swimsuit contest videos for consolation!
Memories popping out!
Boobs popping out!
You're as big a pervert as they say.
Who is she?
Why are you staring at me?
You're an even bigger pervert than they say.
I'm not!
Who are you?
Maybe this will jog your memory.
If anyone sees me like this again, I'll...
You'll what?
I see.
So that wasn't your first time?
You're absolutely, positively, absotively a pervert.
Wait, are you the girl I met on Lone Cedar Hill?
My name is Tsutsukakushi Tsukiko.
This is embarrassing, so could you get off of me?
Embarrassing?
Yes. I'm so embarrassed, I could die.
I haven't been able to make facial expressions ever since I prayed to the cat statue.
That must mean my facade
disappeared along with my belt.
And my facial expressions were taken by the statue, along with my meat bun.
I didn't believe it actually
had the power to do that.
It granted my wish a little too perfectly. So much so that it's a problem now.
Being unable to make facial expressions has consequences in my daily life.
Please give my facial expressions back.
I think we're too late.
Huh?
According to the rumors, the Stony Cat gives what you don't need to someone who needs it, right?
Yes.
Someone already has my facade.
We don't know how to get your facial expressions back from the statue.
So...
So what? What should I do?
Am I supposed to stay like this forever?
What will happen to me?
No, wait!
I know a way to make you laugh, guaranteed!
What is it?
We just have to do...
this!
Laugh, laugh, laugh!
Laugh for me!
You know, I must look like
a real pervert doing this!
You don't...
just look like one!
I'm sorry.
I hope so.
Anyway, I have an idea.
The Stony Cat takes things people don't need.
That means we need to find someone who doesn't
need their facade and get them to pray to the statue.
Then the cat will give you their facade because you need it.
That's it! That's exactly right!
I tickled you precisely because
I wanted to say that!
Senpai, are you really sorry?
Not the slightest bit!
Huh?
You're very open with your feelings.
If we don't do something about that soon, you're bound to get yourself in trouble.
I've decided to help you find someone who doesn't need their facade.
Is that okay with you?
Yeah.
We can look for someone who wants to hide their facial expressions while we're at it.
And so, I formed an alliance with Tsutsukakushi.
So what happened to you today?
I tried to see if the Steel King had a facade or emotions to share, and...
Good morning!
Oh, Yokodera.
Are you cured of your pervert disorder—
Captain!
What year of elementary school did your boobs start getting so huge—
Creep. Die. Die thrice.
...let's just say, the Steel King was very open with her emotions and smashed my face in.
I know you need to find someone who isn't open with their emotions,
but I think there's a better way to go about it.
Can you keep it down?
You're that pervert!
Well, if it isn't Azuki Azusa!
Have a nice nap?
Don't talk to me, pervert!
And why did you just ask me that, pervert?!
Because you've got drool from when you slept on your face.
When you're part of high society, even drool is a fashion statement!
Th-That's right!
I don't need you to point it out!
It's like giving a down comforter to a fluffy penguin!
Then I guess the way your blouse button is undone...
and the way your skirt is flipped are fashion statements too!
You must be leading me on!
An heiress would never forget to check her appearance!
It's obviously intentional!
O-Obviously!
Excuse me, but what kind of relationship do you have?
R-Relationship?
With this pervert?
What a silly girl! An heiress wouldn't be so loose as to lead on a total stranger!
You pervert!
O-Oh. It's like how apes scratch each other's backs.
G-Good day!
Man, it must suck to be so proud!
I see. So you scratch each other's backs.
Please, stop kicking!
It was too much fun. I couldn't help but tease her!
I'm sorry!
So you really aren't in a relationship with her?
Of course not!
She hates my guts!
If we were ever in a dark alley together, there'd be a murder investigation!
What's wrong?
No, it's just that as soon as she noticed me, she stopped expressing herself openly.
It was almost unnatural.
So you're saying she can only put up a facade for strangers?
Oh, that's right! I called Azuki Azusa flat as a board in front of everyone.
You did? You're a hopeless pervert.
But she didn't get angry.
She has to keep up her reputation as an heiress when she's in public.
But being able to keep cool like that isn't natural.
And the choker she was wearing...
It looks like the leather belt that I lost at the Stony Cat.
So you're saying...
Yeah.
Azuki Azusa can't express herself openly because she received my facade.
Now all we need to do is to get Azuki Azusa to give it back!
It won't be easy.
Huh?
Azuki-san received your facade because she needed it.
If so, it won't be easy to—
No!
It's only natural to return what
isn't yours to its rightful owner!
But—
Give me a second!
Senpai—
Azuki Azusa may be a tough opponent.
But I'm getting socked and berated to death.
I'm suffering way too much!
I need to give her a piece of my mind!
Azuki Azusa!
Give me back my precious!
I've been watching you,
and I've realized something!
You stole everything from me!
Take responsibility!
Wh-What are you saying, you pervert?!
Y-You should show how strongly you feel through your actions.
What can you do for me, I wonder?
Showing off that you've got my facade?
Well then!
I want to take all of you, Azuki Azusa!
All of me?!
So let me stay by you forever!
Schthay by me?!
24 hours a day!
Whenever, wherever, however!
H-Hyoweaver?!
So that you can open your body and heart to me at any time!
And share that precious thing!
Oh damn, he's a total pervert! This is crazy!
What?
He's going full pervert!
Azuki Azusa!
You said to show my feelings through actions?
W-Wait...
What are you doing?
Woof!
To stay by you forever, I'll be your dog!
Now what, Azuki-san?
The Pervert Prince's confessions are on a whole 'nother level!
No! Absolutely not!
It's totally perverted.
What if it backfires?
I don't want to be with a pervert forever!
I definitely don't want that!
Yay. I'm so happy.
As happy as a cheetah wrapped like a spool.
The prince took down the heiress!
And so, to regain my facade,
I changed roles from prince to dog.
You really are a pervert.
kimi ni baby sweet berry love
I'm in baby sweet berry love with you
honto no kimochi dake
It would be so nice if I could
wakeaetara ii no ni na
Share with you how I really feel
negai wo kanaete yo
Make my wish come true
c.u.t.e. funny cat
C-U-T-E funny cat
give me give me shiny time
Give me give me shiny time
p.r.e.t.ty
P-R-E-T-T-Y
tiny tiny berry love
A tiny, tiny berry love
daisuki no heart mo
My heart full of love for you
gomen ne no namida mo
And these tears because I'm sorry
honto wa sunao ni misetakute
I really wish I could just show them to you
tsutaetai omoi to
I want to tell you that I feel this way
uragaeshi no taido
But the opposite is what I always say
jouzu ni narenai
I just can't do it right
kokoro moyou
Expressing myself
doushite karamawari
Why can't I get on the ball?
mune ga gyutto naru
My chest feels so tight
chigau kyorikan ga
Feeling so close to you
modokashii yo nee
Frustrates me so much
todoketai no
I want you to know
kimi to baby sweet berry love
I want a baby sweet berry love with you
kitto gikochinakute
I know it'll be awkward
demo ne massugu ni mitsumete
But I want to look you straight in the eye
sorairo utsushitai
So you can see a clear blue sky
motto baby sweet berry love
I want a more baby sweet berry love
semete kimi no mae de wa
I wish that at least in front of you
waratte okotte afureta
I can smille and pout all I want
ari no mama de itai
I want to be myself
dakara baby sweet berry love
That's why baby sweet berry love
issho ni hajimeyou
Let's start together
The Fairy Doesn't Get Mad
Next time: The Fairy Doesn't Get Mad.