Hey...
Could you be a little more gentle?
Yokodera's younger brother...
Is this how you feel about me?
That's all you have to say in this situation?!
mou ikkai kocchi muite..
One more time, look this way
iitai koto ga motto aru kara..
There's still more that I want to tell you
mou ikkai kocchi muite..
One more time, look this way
honki ga yureru ai no future..
Who you love's going to change in the future
dakara kocchi muite..
That's why you should look this way
maware chikyuu koi wo nosete..
The world turns, filled with love
dakara kocchi muite..
That's why you should look this way
guuzen ja nai fantafuture..
It wasn't just chance, it's our fantastic future
watashi kara sasou yuuki wo
watashi
kara
sasou
yuuki
wo
To have the courage to ask you out myself
kudasai to tsuki ni negau no
kudasai
to
tsuki ni
negau
no
I wished on the moon that I could
setsunai kokoro ni mahou kaketemimashou
setsunai
kokoro
ni
mahou
kaketemimashou
Let's cast a little spell on that breaking heart
mirai he no chikamichi ne
mirai
he
no
chikamichi
ne
It's the fastest way to the future
amaku naare egao de
With a smile I'm making even sweeter
kimi yo tokechae
I'll make your whole self melt
kyou no yozora wo mitsume
Tonight I'll look at the sky
chotto senobite
And try to reach a little closer
mou ikkai kocchi muite..
One more time, look this way
iitai koto ga motto aru kara..
There's still more that I want to tell you
mou ikkai kocchi muite..
One more time, look this way
honki ga yureru ai no future..
Who you love's going to change in the future
dakara kocchi muite..
That's why you should look this way
maware chikyuu koi wo nosete..
The world turns, filled with love
dakara kocchi muite..
That's why you should look this way
guuzen ja nai fantafuture..
It wasn't just chance, it's our fantastic future
Someday, My Family
It just fell apart?
I guess old buildings are more fragile than swallows' nests.
Well, all that matters is that you two are okay.
But...
Wh-What were you doing with my pet?!
It was an accident!
It doesn't count!
W-Wait! What kind of accident?!
Like a fender bender?!
A rear-end collision?!
What are they talking about?
Who knows?
Anyway, I'm glad you aren't hurt.
We should sleep now.
School starts up again tomorrow.
Yeah.
Her late father's tracksuit.
...then the world should just fall into ruin!
That's what Miss Steel wished for.
I don't think it'll end with just the storehouse collapsing.
I couldn't sleep thinking about it.
It's delicious!
My family always has toast and jam.
This feels so new!
So kids these days call this new?
And you love rice with mayonaise, Nee-san.
What's wrong with that?
Mayorice is justice!
Oh, could I borrow your phone?
I need to tell my mom that I can't make the first day.
Of course. Please do.
Thanks.
I doubt anyone could.
The school is probably closed due to the typhoon.
Right. Thanks.
But I should call anyway.
How is everyone so relaxed?
I got all worried for nothing!
But...
Is that really it for Miss Steel's wish?
Um, sorry, but...
I'm not getting a dial tone.
You're right. No dial tone.
Maybe the line snapped?
My cell phone doesn't have signal.
Mine doesn't either.
That's why I was going to use your phone.
I was going to check the weather forecast,
but it seems the television is broken.
I'm bored.
I'm bored too.
Why don't we play a game?
Just sitting around isn't very exciting.
What? Cards?
Yes.
What should we play?
Well, let's see.
We have four people.
How about President?
Oh, President?
I've played that with my friends before!
With my friends!
But, just to be sure, could you explain the rules?
Oh...
She's never played before.
I'll explain them now.
Nee-san forgets them whenever we play, anyway.
Nee-san?
Huh?
Oh, sorry.
I was just about to make sure the house is okay.
I closed all the rain shutters.
Right.
But our house is big.
You could have missed one.
It isn't like you to say that.
Our house might be big—
I knew it!
Knew it?
It's this bad?
It looks like the house might flood.
It's just like 12 years ago.
12 years ago?
When the levees collapsed under heavy rain.
Don't you remember?
Um...
We need to move everything upstairs now.
Yokodera's younger brother, will you help us?
Yeah, of course!
We can't use any of these rooms.
The roof above them are leaking badly.
What?
Then where should we put these?
The entire mansion collapsing from a typhoon?
This has to be part of the wish.
It's worse than I thought. Does this mean my secret room is in danger?
No, that's the middle of the
second floor. It won't leak.
Right! It's safe! Perfectly safe!
Nee-san, you have a secret room?
Yeah!
There's a hidden door in the closet—
Let's check if it's safe first.
If it is, we can move everything there.
Wait, hold on!
We can't do that!
We just can't do that!
Anywhere but there!
I've kept detailed records of Tsukiko in every situation possible since she was young!
You could call it the Tsukiko Museum—
The museum will be closing its doors today.
This is now censored.
This is against the law.
This is unacceptable
How could you be so cruel?
This too.
This too. This too. This too.
I'll bring the stuff here.
Could you two just lift them into the room?
Huh?
No, I'll help you.
Don't worry!
I'm a man!
Leave it to me!
Sometimes, but very rarely,
he can be a little dependable.
W-Well, sometimes, but extremely rarely,
maybe he can be.
Acting like a worthless guy who gets dependable in an emergency takes a lot out of you.
Your daughters have done a lot for me.
An admirable act.
Bowing your head to another family's altar of your own will.
How inspiring.
You're back on your feet already?
I can't just sit and sulk.
It looks like you've taken most of the furniture up.
Thanks.
Don't mention it.
You get pretty dependable in an emergency.
O-Oh, right! We'd better take the altar up too!
No.
These are all we need.
But...
A Buddhist altar is just a box.
What's truly important is etched within our hearts.
Like the image of Tsuiko sleeping so adorably!
You just made that entire moving speech void!
Precious memories remain, unchanging in your mind.
Close your eyes, and you see them as if they were only yesterday.
The expressions on my parents' faces, praising my genius, as I recited my multiplication tables!
They exclaimed that I should be a doctor, or part of the Diet,
or perhaps the savior of the world!
You're glorifying them way too much!
Your memories are all changed!
The living have the right to glorify their memories!
And with our memories of the dead, we live for the living.
Is that everything?
Yes.
But I'll go around once more to check.
It's started!
We need to tell Tsukiko.
Wh—
What are you stopping me for?
I want you to pray to the cat god.
Take back the wish you made yesterday.
What?
That cat god really has the power to grant wishes.
You might not believe me, but—
Of course I'd believe you.
It granted one of my wishes when I was young.
Tsukiko and I had gotten into a fight over something trivial.
My wish was to make up with her.
Really?
The cat god brought to me a block of wood and a chisel,
and I made the cat statue on Lone Cedar Hill.
Tsukiko was very happy—
Then this situation...
Right.
This all might be due to my wish.
It did cross my mind.
Then cancel it now!
Everything'll go back to normal!
Really?
Yeah. Trust me.
O-Okay!
Cat god! The wish I made last night doesn't count!
Forget I ever made it!
It seems the cat god won't let me take it back.
No. You should be able to cancel it.
Hey! Where are you going?
It's back.
The Steel King's wish only destroyed the storehouse.
What caused the flood, then?
Incoming Call
Ponta
I can still receive calls?
Hello?
Hey, what's up, Pervert Prince?
Caught a cold?
Uh... No, I'm fine.
Oh, so that's how it is!
Skipping like a schoolgirl gone naughty?
You sure got balls, kid!
Skipping?
Isn't the school closed for the typhoon?
Huh?
You getting delirious in this summer heat?
The typhoon passed first thing this morning!
Yaji-san, where you going?
Sorry, call you back later.
That means someone else wished to the cat god for this.
The flood hasn't reached the kitchen or banquet hall, even though they're on the first floor.
Whoever wished for the storm wished for this too.
Like to eat dinner together
Whoever runs out of cards first is the president.
and play cards like a happy family.
Whoever runs out next is kind of amazing.
Whoever runs out after that is not that amazing.
Whoever runs out last is the scum.
Each card has different strength.
3 has the least, followed by 4, 5, 6, and as the number increases, they have more muscle.
Hey, Azuki Azusa.
Could you do me a fa—
I wonder what'll happen if no one comes to rescue us.
Maybe we'll need to be a new Adam and Eve and start a new family.
Huh?
I'll try to hang in there, so...
Can you hang in there enough to make a soccer team?
Whose future are we planning here?
And why are you assuming we'll live here?
Isn't that why you wanted to talk to me?
No!
Definitely not!
Then why?
I have a favor to ask.
Huh?
Could you talk to the Captain for a bit?
Maybe in her secret room—no, maybe just the kitchen.
The flood hasn't reached there.
Why?
Just because.
Please.
Ten minutes is good enough.
No.
I don't like her.
And if you think someone will do something for you without an explanation,
you're wrong.
At least explain a little of why.
If you can't, then try to.
I'll try to understand.
I need to talk to Tsutsukakushi,
but I don't want the Captain to hear.
She gets lonely easily.
It'd be sad for her to learn everything.
Senpai, c-could you come here a second?
Hm? What for?
Azuki Azusa always helps me.
Someday, I'll need to return the favor.
You're back?
We're ready to play President.
We'll start playing when they get back.
I have the 3 of diamonds, so I'll start.
Is it that much fun?
Yes.
I like playing President.
No, not that.
You're enjoying this situation, aren't you?
No.
No one on Earth could enjoy
having their house flooded.
Tsutsukakushi, you can't accept this kind of situation.
What do you mean?
It isn't natural.
If your house falls apart, you won't be able to clean.
It's okay.
I was starting to get tired of cleaning anyway.
The bath is too big.
The bathrooms are too dark.
The halls are too long.
There are a lot of rooms we don't even use.
It's too much house for just my sister and me.
Tsutsukakushi...
You said that you wanted to be my brother.
Do you still want to?
If I said I wouldn't ask for much—
just that you'd be my brother—would you?
Nothing would really happen if you did.
It's just like something for good luck, so—
Sorry.
I can't grant your wish.
I can't be part of your family.
This isn't my home.
I can't stay with you forever.
I can't keep you satisfied forev—
Why?
How can you say that?
I don't understand.
You said you'd be my brother.
You treated me like your little sister.
I finally convinced myself that I could live with that if it was all I could be to you.
But now I can't even be that?
You lied, Senpai.
You said you'd stay with me.
I don't like liars.
Hear me out, Tsukiko-chan!
I don't like you calling me that.
Let go.
Let go of me.
You never treat me right.
You never hear me out.
You never hear me out when I really want you to.
It doesn't matter! Just hear me out!
Tsukiko!
Tsukiko, I don't want to be your family.
I want to stay with you in a different way.
It's exciting because we don't see each other all the time.
That's what I want.
That's just you—
We live right by each other in the same world.
We can't live in the same place
and see the same things.
But living right by each other and sometimes coming together...
I think we can do that.
You can come to my home sometimes.
We can eat dinner with my family.
And we can play cards after that.
We can all play President together.
So...
Distant, but close.
Distant, so fun.
Let's stay together like that.
Cards.
Was that a promise?
After the storm passes, we'll play.
You promised.
Yeah. After it passes, we'll play.
Tsutsukakushi's wish was cancelled.
The Tsutsukakushi and Yokodera family homes went back to normal.
And so did our lives.
Two weeks have passed since.
Tsutsukakushi is coming to my home for the first time today.
City Hall
Along with Miss Steel and Azuki Azusa.
But I asked Miss Steel to see me before we were supposed to meet.
This is the Yokodera family record.
Look at who's on the record and who isn't.
As dense as the Steel King is,
I'm sure she'll finally understand that Yokodera Youto doesn't have a younger brother.
I see.
So that's how it was.
Do as you will!
Don't worry. It'll all be okay.
You may have been erased from the public records
and be treated as a nonexistent person,
but I'm on your side.
I understand.
You're alone. You need a family.
And the two of us need one too.
Actually, I asked Tsukiko about you the other day.
Tsukiko said she didn't care about any person called "Yokodera's younger brother."
That means we have no reason to hesitate.
Hold on, hold on, hold on!
Hold on one second!
Naturally, I love Tsukiko too,
but I'm not cheating on her.
I'm serious about both of you.
You, Tsukiko, and I are all family!
We'll all be happy!
Um... What do you mean?
How dense can you be?
What do I mean?
Well, basically...
I don't know, either.
You tell me.
I knew it from the start.
I'm not surprised at all.
It's not the pervert's fault.
If...
If anyone's at fault,
it's me.
Please...
Make me a different me.
kimi ni baby sweet berry love
I'm in baby sweet berry love with you
honto no kimochi dake
It would be so nice if I could
wakeaetara ii no ni na
Share with you how I really feel
negai wo kanaete yo
Make my wish come true
c.u.t.e. funny cat
C-U-T-E funny cat
give me give me shiny time
Give me give me shiny time
p.r.e.t.ty
P-R-E-T-T-Y
tiny tiny berry love
A tiny, tiny berry love
daisuki no heart mo
My heart full of love for you
gomen ne no namida mo
And these tears because I'm sorry
honto wa sunao ni misetakute
I really wish I could just show them to you
tsutaetai omoi to
I want to tell you that I feel this way
uragaeshi no taido
But the opposite is what I always say
jouzu ni narenai
I just can't do it right
kokoro moyou
Expressing myself
doushite karamawari
Why can't I get on the ball?
mune ga gyutto naru
My chest feels so tight
chigau kyorikan ga
Feeling so close to you
modokashii yo nee
Frustrates me so much
todoketai no
I want you to know
kimi to baby sweet berry love
I want a baby sweet berry love with you
kitto gikochinakute
I know it'll be awkward
demo ne massugu ni mitsumete
But I want to look you straight in the eye
sorairo utsushitai
So you can see a clear blue sky
motto baby sweet berry love
I want a more baby sweet berry love
semete kimi no mae de wa
I wish that at least in front of you
waratte okotte afureta
I can smille and pout all I want
ari no mama de itai
I want to be myself
dakara baby sweet berry love
That's why baby sweet berry love
issho ni hajimeyou
Let's start together
A 100% Girl
Next time: A 100% Girl.