Night soon became morning.
Today is August 31st, the last day of summer vacation.
And yet, I...
Senpai.
Oh, Tsutsukakushi?
Good morning.
So this is where you were?
I've been looking for you.
Sorry.
But after what happened last night, I couldn't really stay in the house.
I see. That.
Th-That was... Uh...
The next time you peek, I'll really get mad.
Y-Yes, ma'am!
As long as you understand.
Senpai, why is this storehouse...
Yeah. Don't be surprised.
This is my room.
No, my home.
mou ikkai kocchi muite..
One more time, look this way
iitai koto ga motto aru kara..
There's still more that I want to tell you
mou ikkai kocchi muite..
One more time, look this way
honki ga yureru ai no future..
Who you love's going to change in the future
dakara kocchi muite..
That's why you should look this way
maware chikyuu koi wo nosete..
The world turns, filled with love
dakara kocchi muite..
That's why you should look this way
guuzen ja nai fantafuture..
It wasn't just chance, it's our fantastic future
watashi
kara
sasou
yuuki
wo
watashi kara sasou yuuki wo
To have the courage to ask you out myself
kudasai
to
tsuki ni
negau
no
kudasai to tsuki ni negau no
I wished on the moon that I could
setsunai
kokoro
ni
mahou
kaketemimashou
setsunai kokoro ni mahou kaketemimashou
Let's cast a little spell on that breaking heart
mirai
he
no
chikamichi
ne
mirai he no chikamichi ne
It's the fastest way to the future
amaku naare egao de
With a smile I'm making even sweeter
kimi yo tokechae
I'll make your whole self melt
kyou no yozora wo mitsume
Tonight I'll look at the sky
chotto senobite
And try to reach a little closer
mou ikkai kocchi muite..
One more time, look this way
iitai koto ga motto aru kara..
There's still more that I want to tell you
mou ikkai kocchi muite..
One more time, look this way
honki ga yureru ai no future..
Who you love's going to change in the future
dakara kocchi muite..
That's why you should look this way
maware chikyuu koi wo nosete..
The world turns, filled with love
dakara kocchi muite..
That's why you should look this way
guuzen ja nai fantafuture..
It wasn't just chance, it's our fantastic future
Welcome, My Friend
So you're saying that your room was transported to this storehouse?
Everything here is from my house.
It's the only explanation I have.
And look.
There's another cat statue here.
Maybe it has something to do with all this.
Then this belongs to you too?
Three Hours of Boobs, Boobs, Boobs: Ah, What a Beautiful Mountain Range. I see.
Um...
Steet Corner Marshmallow Visits.
A Method to Raise the Delicious Melons.
The Pervert King and My Royal Chest.
Please, Tsutsukakushi! Forgive me!
You're carving my heart up with them!
Marshmallow Visits 3.
So you like people with large chests, Senpai?
You're a hopeless pervert. Even trash has more worth.
No, I got those a while back.
My tastes have changed since then!
Out of curiosity, how have your tastes changed?
I used to only care about the top,
but the difference between that and the lower measurement matters a lot.
Stop!
The stony cat in the storehouse must have transported my house there.
I forgot to tell Tsutsukakushi, but that was my theory.
So first, we need to learn more about the statue.
There's only one person I can ask about it.
Incoming Call
Azuki Azusa
Sorry. I don't have time to talk right now.
Leave a message after the tone.
I even called him myself!
Stupid pervert!
Stupid spotted hippopotamus!
What?
The cat statue in the storehouse?
Y-Yes.
I was wondering what it was.
It's the cat god that our family worships.
We've been worshipping it for a long time now.
D-Does she have to make such lewd noises with each rep?
Your family worships that cat god?
Cat gods stay in houses they inhabit...
and invite prosperity by drawing wishes to themselves.
But they also bring the curse of a short life.
I-I can't seem to focus on what she's saying,
but she mentioned that it draws wishes to itself?
Hey. Pervert.
I'm gonna kill you.
What's the issue?
He was looking at you with lewd eyes!
He slowly licked you all over with his criminal eyes!
N-No I didn't!
He practically laid his loins bare!
He tried to impregnate you with his child!
He tried to bathe you with viscous, cloudy white genetic fluids in accordance with his animal instincts!
Hey, what are you making a girl say, you freaking pervert?
You said it on your own!
You're even creeping me out!
You're the top of the pervert hierarchy!
Hold on, I'm talking to Yokodera right now.
We can talk about visc... whatever later.
Yes, Captain.
Remember this, cloudy white fluid.
So, Yokodera, how did you know about my family's cat god?
Seriously, my younger brother is nothing but trouble for everyone!
He babbles on and on about stuff you don't care to know!
I see.
So when he said the Yokodera family home disappeared...
Just a lie off the top of his head.
Just as I thought.
He wanted to kidnap Tsukiko.
Yup. Trying to sink his fangs into such a cute girl?
A real lowlife, isn't he?
Just "cute"?
I hope you're not complimenting Tsukiko with only half a heart.
If you are, you're actually insulting Tsukiko.
O-Of course I'm not!
The first time I laid eyes on your sister,
she was so cute that I lost my breath!
I was that surprised!
Then answer this:
Propose a statistical explanation of Tsukiko's cuteness.
Use a simple random sample of 6 billion people.
Give them phone, personal, and exit interviews.
No matter what, she'll come out on top in cuteness!
And a philosophical explanation?
First, postulate that "Your little sister is cute."
Then "All cute girls are your little sister" must also be true.
Because this is a tautology, it must hold that "Your little sister is cutest"!
And a track explanation?
Bubka with angel's wings!
Abebe wearing the red shoes!
Bolt drawing a bow to the sky!
We could be good friends.
I agree with you on all counts.
So will you assist me in strangling your brother to death?
Of course!
Wait, death?
Yes. As soon as possible.
First, you call him to a remote location.
When he arrives, you strike him with a blunt object and restrain him.
Then we lay him on a bed of nails.
Next, we'll skin him alive and...
Oh God, she's serious!
At this rate, I'll be an accomplice in murdering myself!
Hold on!
Hold on one second!
What?
What about your sister?
I don't think she hates him that much.
Tsukiko is being fooled.
But if my brother disappears while she's fooled,
your sister will remember him that way forever.
We'll need to change her opinion of him first.
H-How can we do that?
Seduce the man and tear the two apart!
Seduce?
Once they stop seeing each other, your sister will forget all about him,
and we can eliminate him as we please!
I see! You're smart, Yokodera!
We'll put a rain check on strangling him!
Yeah, let's do that. Let's do that.
This cat statue draws wishes to itself.
That's what Miss Steel said.
A simple test will show if it's true.
But what should I wish for?
Incoming Call
Azuki Azusa
Hello?
Finally! You answered!
Are you sorry for what you did?!
Huh?
I'm asking if your stomach's full of guilt like a troop of monkeys.
About what?
Didn't you feel anything after hearing that voicemail message?!
You felt lonely because your calls wouldn't get through, right?
Your heart was wracked with pain because we were apart, right?
You couldn't sleep at night thinking of me, right?
You nearly came to tears a bunch of times, right?
No, not at all.
So why are you so angry at me, anyway?
You don't know?!
I shouldn't have to tell you!
You big bald bear! Betraying all the bunnies you bluff!
Come again?
I even bought a new swimsuit! And it's really nice!
Oh, right. You said it was a bikini?
Yeah.
You're a pervert! Why didn't you want to see it?!
Oh, I see. Azuki Azusa in a bikini.
I am kind of worried the top doesn't have anything to catch onto.
So I do want to see it with my own eyes.
Huh?
Afugi Afufa!
No!
Wh-Where am I?!
What's going on and why?!
So it granted my wish to see Azuki Azusa?
You pervert!
What did you do, you pervert?!
So let me get this straight.
This is the storehouse at Tsutsukakushi-san's home.
Yeah.
This cat god has the power to grant wishes.
Sniff sniff.
Wh-What is it?
You have Tsutsukakushi-san's scent on you.
Oh... Huh?
You've been using the same shampoo!
Why are you staying at Tsutsukakushi-san's home and using her bath?!
Uh... um...
So your relationship's developed while I was cast away to Okinawa?
Why are you laughing creepily and crying?
Shut up!
I'm not crying!
The cat on Lone Cedar Hill gave things people didn't need to others, right?
This one sounds a lot more useful.
The way it grants wishes is kind of twisted, though.
Maybe we're not wishing on it right.
If we wish properly, maybe...
I want this pervert to tickle my belly.
Huh? Sorry, what'd you say?
What's this?
No!
What is this?!
What's going on?!
Wh-What are you doing?!
What's wrong with you?!
I don't know.
I just feel like I have to do this.
You're so pretty, Azuki Azusa.
Pretty?
Very, very attractive.
I like that.
No...
This is all fake!
It doesn't make me happy at all!
I'd rather do it slow and steady like a swallow building a nest than cheat like this!
I take it back!
Huh?
Sorry!
What the heck just happened?!
It's not your fault, pervert.
I'm to blame for wishing for something stupid.
What did you wish for?
Th-That's a secret!
I'm glad I took it back.
So you can take back wishes?
Anyway, we know what the cat god can do.
I just noticed—your hair's different today.
Y-Yeah.
I only do this when I go swimming.
It's pretty cute too.
Oh, really?
Well, of course it is!
I need to tell Tsutsukakushi about Azuki Azusa.
She can't go home in this weather.
One day, while walking through the woods,
a bear said to me,
"Little girl, please wait."
"You were so cute that I lost my breath! I was that surprised!"
Huh? Did Tsutsukakushi hear me when I said that?
Oh, my, Mr. Bear, thank you very much.
"No matter what, she'll come out on top in cuteness!"
As thanks...
I guess compliments make you happy, Tsutsukakushi?
Of course.
But what made me happiest was that the person who complimented me was S—
S-S...
A sumo champion.
Oh, you like sumo?
I like it too!
Come on, bring it!
Bring it.
No. Senpai, when did you get back?
A while ago.
I was at the cat statue.
So, um, how many people are you cooking for?
If you thought anything weird while you were watching me, you're mistaken.
Completely, utterly, absolutely, and conclusively mistaken.
Huh?
Okay.
So, about dinner...
Can you make enough for four?
What's this about dinner?
You shouldn't change the subject.
Bring it.
Huh?
Isn't that shirt the one I wore yesterday?
An apron.
My apron.
I carelessly misplaced it,
and I just happened to put on what just happened to be nearby.
Oh, I see.
Actually, in a girl game I played once,
there was a girl who said, "When I'm wearing your clothes, I can smell your scent! It makes me so happy!"
I'm glad you're not a pervert like her!
Huh? Tsutsukakushi?
I'm very sorry.
Please forgive me.
Huh? What's wrong?
Forgive you for what?
I see. So you came today too, Yokodera's younger brother?
My skin! Anything but my skin!
No need to be so scared.
Actually, I've always wanted to get to know you better.
Oh, I know. Won't you stay for dinner?
Huh?
Nee-san, this is Azuki Azusa-san.
Thank you for having me.
I see. Enjoy your stay.
Oh, my! Your cup is empty!
I-It's just tea. You don't need to pour for me.
No need to be shy!
What's pouring tea between us?
Not only am I kind, but considerate!
And I have never once had a boyfriend!
You could call me a newly built, high-security, exclusive, high-quality home!
I'm just waiting for someone to move in!
Oh God, please tell me Miss Steel doesn't intend to seduce me on her own!
Come now, open wide.
"Ah."
Ah...
Will you cut that out?
Who do you think you are?
You're as unfair as a black kite stealing fried tofu!
I must say, you have excellent table manners.
But who gave you the right to act high and mighty when you are a guest in our home?
What kind of relationship do you have with this man?
We're f-fri—
I'm sure you can't simply be friends.
...ends—
No, I mean...
He's my pet!
He's my personal pet!
Pet?
I'm still your pet?
That's right!
Come on, little doggy!
In my lap, just like you always do!
A-Always do?
But it's easy to take that the wrong way. What about my repu—
Woof!
S-See?
He can shake, sit, sleep, rub, and lick!
Lick?
I can make him do that too.
Come here and lick it off my hand.
Hurry, or it might fa—
It's cold, but it's okay.
Come lick it off!
No! No licking!
Come now, lick!
Don't lick!
I don't like people who waste food.
Wow, this beef stew is so soft!
These sautéed beans are great too!
The miso is even more delicious than usual!
Dinner was really good.
Thanks again.
I see.
I enjoyed it too.
It was a fun little dinner party.
Eating together is a good thing.
Is Azuki-san really here because of the cat statue in the storehouse?
Yeah.
I'm pretty sure it is.
If it is, then it might be all my fault.
What's your fault?
Your house being transported here.
What?!
You wished that the Yokodera family home would disappear?!
Do you hate me that much?!
There are times when I wish you were dead too.
What?!
Just kidding.
I thought, "Senpai's home is far away, so we can't eat dinner together."
It may have taken that in a strange way.
But Tsutsukakushi, when I offered to take you home, you turned me down.
As many times as you take me home, that doesn't mean we'll be together forever.
Well, sure, but...
Getting close to someone halfheartedly can cause you suffering.
Tsutsukakushi...
But dinner tonight was fun.
Very, very fun.
My wish was granted.
Now everything is perfectly, cleanly, and completely resolved.
I'm very sorry.
There has to be some deeper meaning behind Tsutsukakushi's wish.
I just don't know what it is.
Wh-What are you doing?!
I'm sure you can tell.
I'm seducing you.
Now let's get down to business.
Hell no!
No need to be scared.
It'll be over soon enough.
You can just count the stains on the ceiling.
No!
Mommy!
So... What am I supposed to do next?
You don't know?!
Then get off me!
Why?!
Don't you want to bend my body to your bidding?
Girls shouldn't say stuff like that!
You'll get totally messed up!
I don't care.
Huh?
M-Mess me up all you want!
If that's what it takes to take Tsukiko back...
You don't have to worry about me.
Tsukiko-chan's defenses are
harder than you think, King.
No, you're wrong.
You're stronger than you think you are.
I know I'll lose.
And Tsukiko will leave me.
You're overreacting.
You wouldn't understand.
You've never lost someone before.
You could never understand.
It takes a long time to adjust to it.
I don't want to be left behind again!
I don't want to feel like that again!
If separation is all the future holds for us...
No! It's not!
...then the world should just fall into ruin!
Get down!
kimi ni baby sweet berry love
I'm in baby sweet berry love with you
honto no kimochi dake
It would be so nice if I could
wakeaetara ii no ni na
Share with you how I really feel
negai wo kanaete yo
Make my wish come true
c.u.t.e. funny cat
C-U-T-E funny cat
give me give me shiny time
Give me give me shiny time
p.r.e.t.ty
P-R-E-T-T-Y
tiny tiny berry love
A tiny, tiny berry love
daisuki no heart mo
My heart full of love for you
gomen ne no namida mo
And these tears because I'm sorry
honto wa sunao ni misetakute
I really wish I could just show them to you
tsutaetai omoi to
I want to tell you that I feel this way
uragaeshi no taido
But the opposite is what I always say
jouzu ni narenai
I just can't do it right
kokoro moyou
Expressing myself
doushite karamawari
Why can't I get on the ball?
mune ga gyutto naru
My chest feels so tight
chigau kyorikan ga
Feeling so close to you
modokashii yo nee
Frustrates me so much
todoketai no
I want you to know
kimi to baby sweet berry love
I want a baby sweet berry love with you
kitto gikochinakute
I know it'll be awkward
demo ne massugu ni mitsumete
But I want to look you straight in the eye
sorairo utsushitai
So you can see a clear blue sky
motto baby sweet berry love
I want a more baby sweet berry love
semete kimi no mae de wa
I wish that at least in front of you
waratte okotte afureta
I can smille and pout all I want
ari no mama de itai
I want to be myself
dakara baby sweet berry love
That's why baby sweet berry love
issho ni hajimeyou
Let's start together
Someday, My Family
Next time: Someday, My Family.