Take care.
Thank you very much.
I told my mom that she was a failure as a mother.
Even though she truly loves Nee-san and me.
I forced my own ideals onto her.
Just like that mini-Nee-san did.
Mom... is...
You don't need to be so hard...
on yourself... and your sister...
and Tsukasa-san.
mou ikkai kocchi muite..
One more time, look this way
iitai koto ga motto aru kara..
There's still more that I want to tell you
mou ikkai kocchi muite..
One more time, look this way
honki ga yureru ai no future..
Who you love's going to change in the future
dakara kocchi muite..
That's why you should look this way
maware chikyuu koi wo nosete..
The world turns, filled with love
dakara kocchi muite..
That's why you should look this way
guuzen ja nai fantafuture..
It wasn't just chance, it's our fantastic future
watashi kara sasou yuuki wo
watashi
kara
sasou
yuuki
wo
To have the courage to ask you out myself
kudasai to tsuki ni negau no
kudasai
to
tsuki ni
negau
no
I wished on the moon that I could
setsunai kokoro ni mahou kaketemimashou
setsunai
kokoro
ni
mahou
kaketemimashou
Let's cast a little spell on that breaking heart
mirai he no chikamichi ne
mirai
he
no
chikamichi
ne
It's the fastest way to the future
amaku naare egao de
With a smile I'm making even sweeter
kimi yo tokechae
I'll make your whole self melt
kyou no yozora wo mitsume
Tonight I'll look at the sky
chotto senobite
And try to reach a little closer
mou ikkai kocchi muite..
One more time, look this way
iitai koto ga motto aru kara..
There's still more that I want to tell you
mou ikkai kocchi muite..
One more time, look this way
honki ga yureru ai no future..
Who you love's going to change in the future
dakara kocchi muite..
That's why you should look this way
maware chikyuu koi wo nosete..
The world turns, filled with love
dakara kocchi muite..
That's why you should look this way
guuzen ja nai fantafuture..
It wasn't just chance, it's our fantastic future
The Pervert Prince and Outside the Memories
Tsukasa-san's always had health problems.
That's why she couldn't go to Italy and see her daughters.
And the flood two years ago only made it worse.
She might not have much longer.
She should've just left, but she couldn't abandon the home she lived in with her daughters.
Tsukushi...
Tsukiko...
When I first met her, her daughters had left just days before.
She looked so lonely.
I wanted her to smile, even just a little.
But...
I can't make her smile from the bottom of her heart.
Why?
Why can't I do anything?
Is it because I'm a kid?
If I were grown up, would I have been able to make her smile?
Onii-chan...
It's difficult to make a girl smile, even as a grown-up.
But you should never, ever, make a girl cry.
And if you ever see a girl crying, help her.
You might not be able to make her smile, but they'll know how you feel.
Okay!
I know perfectly well that I have no right to talk.
But if it's to set an example for my younger self, maybe it's okay.
I want to make girls smile too.
Enough dawdling! Let's go!
What now, Tsukiko?
Mommy?
I don't care.
We're going back to Italy.
Wait!
Y-You!
How did you know we were staying here?
Grown-ups know everything!
But that doesn't matter.
Please, just hear me out.
Tsukasa-san wants to see you.
I said I would never see her again.
You don't want to part like that, do you?
There's no way Tsukasa-san doesn't love you!
Yesterday, she could barely even stand,
but she stayed up all night,
making clothes for you.
U-Unfortunately, our flight will be leaving soon.
Our grandparents will be here for us soon.
I have no time for your foolishness.
Let's go, Tsukiko.
Tsukiko?
Mommy.
Tsukiko...
Let's go.
Hey!
Hey, Tsukasa-san...
Stay still.
Don't you have marks for your daughters?
Of course not.
I couldn't do a single thing for them.
I wish I could've at least left something for them.
Tsukasa-san.
Is there anything I can do for you?
Tell me! I'll do anything!
Freaking kid.
Don't think you can do anything for a grown-up.
Tsukiko...
Tsukushi...
Food!
I see.
It really is Tsukiko-chan.
Your sister went in.
What's wrong?
Need me to go to the bathroom with you?
F-Fool! Imbecile! Have you no shame?!
I do not know if I may set foot inside this house.
My mother did not personally request that I come.
I have not seen my mother for four years.
Of course you can.
Tsukasa-san's always been waiting for you.
Your words mean nothing.
If she wanted to see me, she could have come at any time.
Yet...
Senpai. Senpai.
A strange girl just came into the kitchen.
I'm making porridge, and she keeps eating it like there's no tomorrow.
Who is she?
You don't recognize yourself?
Nee-san—
So you came, Tsukushi-san?
Your mom will be very happy.
Oh, I know!
Why don't we play strippy-strip before we see your mom?
Senpai, depending on what you say next,
the police may need to see you ten years from now.
Not like that!
I just want Tsukushi-chan to wear the clothes that Tsukasa-san made for her!
That should do it.
Th-These clothes are not to my liking.
But you look good in them.
Tsukasa-san will be really happy when she sees you wearing them.
B-But...
You know...
You can't make this many clothes in just one or two days.
She's been dreaming of seeing you.
She's always been thinking about you.
Onee-shan!
Mother!
Mom!
Mama!
Mom?
Is this... my fault?
I threw that stone, and it struck her...
No, no! That's not it!
Then she will be better soon?
Why do you remain silent?
If she is not injured, is she ill?
In that case, I shall look after her!
I shan't go back to Italy!
She will recover if I do, right?
Right?!
Then my returning to Japan was for naught.
I have not played with my mother since I was three.
I want her to praise me more!
I want her to lecture me more!
I want her to teach me more!
I want... I want to live with Mother more!
If there's anything she doesn't like about me, I'll change!
I won't be picky!
I'll exercise!
I'll be nice to my sister!
Please!
I want more memories of my mother!
Onee-shan...
Tsukiko...
Crybaby.
You act all tough, but you're just a crybaby.
You had so much to say about Tsukasa-san, but you're just a crybaby.
Who are you?
I hate crybabies.
I hate people that only act tough.
I hate Tsukasa-san's kids even more.
Don't say hate!
Anyone who says hate is hate!
I hate you,
but I love Tsukasa-san more
than anything in the world.
I'll grant your wish.
After all, if I ever see a girl crying, I need to help her.
Right?
Did you know?
There's a cat god in this house.
Tsukasa-san told me about it once.
A cat that brings, and a cat that gives.
The cat that brings will
bring you anything you want,
but it only grants your wishes
in ways you never wanted.
But the cat that gives will give something you don't need to someone who needs it.
I think that if something you have is useful for someone else, it's a good thing.
What... do you...
You want memories of Tsukasa-san, right?
So I'll give you mine.
I've made enough of them.
But then, you...
It might be kind of sad,
but I don't care much about the past.
Cat god, please.
Give my memories to someone who needs them.
I see.
That's why I...
I gave her my memories,
so I can't remember anything.
No...
Senpai, this is wrong.
All wrong.
Giving away your memories for us...
Losing something so important...
We can still stop them.
We can change the future.
Senpai?
It's okay, Tsutsukakushi.
I want Miss Steel to have those memories.
But then you'll—
Let's go home, Tsutsukakushi.
No.
We're going home, Tsukiko-chan.
Cancel your wish.
No. I won't.
Tsukiko, let's go home.
Cancel it.
Why?
I never said I wanted to cancel...
I would have had the past for myself.
I thought I could stay your dearest girl in that sense.
I wanted to remember.
For Tsutsukakushi's sake.
Tsukiko, I'm sorry.
This wish...
was mine.
Huh?
Wasn't there someone...
Tsukasa-san, are you okay?
Of course.
I won't die just like that.
Mommy!
There, there.
You've sure grown.
M-Mother...
Mama!
Sorry I couldn't see you until now.
We'll be together forever from now on.
Come on, you too.
Can I?
What, you need to ask?
You're family too.
Hey, let's all go to Italy when Tsukasa-san gets better.
Who knows when that'll be?
Th-That doesn't matter.
I'll wait, even until I'm grown up.
Let's wish to the cat god.
That we can all go to Italy when we grow up.
I know.
Meeting Miss Steel when I was younger...
Meeting Emi when I was younger...
I still can't remember them very well.
If it's only meeting and talking to someone...
I can remember that much.
But the moment they become "memories," I forget.
That was my deal with the cat god.
Then what about me?
What about that night I wore a cat mask and met you?
No...
This is...
This is just wrong.
Why?
I'm sorry.
So you're back?
Tsukasa-san?!
What took you so long?
Oh, it's only you, Nee-san.
"Only"?! Has Tsukiko become a troubled teen?!
Why are you wearing that costume?
Oh, this?
I was sorting through my memories of mother, and I found it.
Memories are the most important thing.
The column, this costume, and everything else.
Such clear and distinct memories could never be false!
The four of us are family.
Four?
Of course, Yokodera's younger brother.
You've been family for a very long time.
Right.
I'll talk to our grandparents and make them understand.
Yes. That's best.
Yes, yes!
I wonder how many times I've worn this tracksuit.
These marks will stay here forever.
Even if I were to forget again.
I'm feeling somewhat conflicted right now.
Huh?
You gave your memories
away for my mom's—our sake.
But you lost your memories of me as well.
I should be thankful to you,
but a part of me can't accept it.
I'm horrible.
I'm sorry.
You don't need to apologize.
I understand,
but I can't come to terms with my feelings.
Regardless, I've decided.
I'm not going to Italy or anywhere else.
If I go away...
If I become just a memory to you,
you'll forget me.
I don't want that.
I...
I don't want that either.
I don't want you to be just a memory either.
I want to keep making memories with you.
Even if I'll just lose them,
I want to stay right by you because I love you.
Words...
Anyone can simply string words together.
If I'm dearest to you,
then you have to prove it somehow.
Huh?
Not with words.
I'm sure you've heard the saying, "Actions speak louder than words."
Um...
Uh...
kimi ni baby sweet berry love
I'm in baby sweet berry love with you
A few days later...
honto no kimochi dake
It would be so nice if I could
Yokodera!
wakeaetara ii no ni na
Share with you how I really feel
Good morning, Azuki Azusa.
negai wo kanaete yo
Make my wish come true
You're here early!
Like an early bird at dawn!
c.u.t.e. funny cat
C-U-T-E funny cat
You don't go to an amusement park every day!
give me give me shiny time
Give me give me shiny time
p.r.e.t.t.y
P-R-E-T-T-Y
It's a date!
tiny tiny berry love
A tiny, tiny berry love
We're all here! It's going to be fun!
I haven't been to an amusement park in quite a while.
Captain...
daisuki no heart mo
My heart full of love for you
Alone with Captain at an amusement park...
Why do I have to go
with this pumpkin pervert?
gomen ne no namida mo
And these tears because I'm sorry
honto wa sunao ni misetakute
I really wish I could just show them to you
Oh? A canteen?
Looks like someone's ready
for a happy fun picnic!
tsutaetai omoi to
I want to tell you that I feel this way
No I'm not!
Hands off!
All right! Yokodera (Younger)!
uragaeshi no taido
But the opposite is what I always say
jouzu ni narenai
I just can't do it right
Let's get on those
"scream machines" or whatever!
kokoro moyou
Expressing myself
H-Hey!
Get off her, Pervert! I'll call the cops!
Come on, Tsutsukakushi-san. Let's go.
doushite karamawari
Why can't I get on the ball?
Something wrong.
Hm? Is there?
mune ga gyutto naru
My chest feels so tight
No, it's just that you look so happy even though it's not just you and Senpai.
chigau kyorikan ga
Feeling so close to you
modokashii yo nee
Frustrates me so much
Yeah, I'm really, really happy.
todoketai no
I want you to know
Did something happen?
kimi to baby sweet berry love
I want a baby sweet berry love with you
Well, you could say I had a dream.
kitto gikochinakute
I know it'll be awkward
A dream?
What kind?
demo ne massugu ni mitsumete
But I want to look you straight in the eye
It wasn't anything major.
sorairo utsushitai
So you can see a clear blue sky
And it was a while ago, so...
motto baby sweet berry love
I want a more baby sweet berry love
So it was such a good dream that just thinking about it makes you smile?
semete kimi no mae de wa
I wish that at least in front of you
Yeah.
waratte okotte afureta
I can smille and pout all I want
Of course, it's just a dream.
It's probably just a dream.
ari no mama de itai
I want to be myself
I had my first kiss.
dakara baby sweet berry love
That's why baby sweet berry love
I feel like I can do anything when I remember that dream!
issho ni hajimeyou
Let's start together
c.u.t.e. funny cat
C-U-T-E funny cat
give me give me shiny time
Give me give me shiny time
Even if it's in your dreams,
p.r.e.t.t.y
P-R-E-T-T-Y
I hope you're not stealing my Yo—
tiny tiny berry love
Tiny, tiny berry love
Nothing.
I see.
I see...
Come on, let's go!
kajirareta heart wo
Something gnawed at my heart
Everyone's already gone!
sagashite miru keredo
So I tried to look for it
I'm glad for you, Li'l Bean. You made friends.
honto wa jibun no oku ni aru
But it was really something inside me
But it, like, looks like it's gonna get kinda ugly, you know?
Hey, Yaji-san!
maru de sabishii no ni
Almost like a stray cat
Yaji-san!
Oh, have you seen a rabbit about yea big?
sumashita mayoi neko
Acting cool even though I feel lonely
koboreta yuuhi ni shitto shichau
I wish I could show my colors like the sunset
No, like, don't think so.
Oh, okay. Thanks.
Yaji-san!
But, like, a rabbit?
fui na yasashisa ni
Suddenly you're nice to me
hashagu mune no oto
And my heart starts to race
A girl who has lost her facial expressions...
dotabata toka colorful de kyun to
I panic, and all sorts of feelings
And me, who has lost his memories...
What awaits us in the future?
michiteiku no
Start to fill my heart
No one knows yet.
kimi to baby sweet berry love
I want a baby sweet berry love with you
It might be an ugly,
hellish war zone.
nanka mujun darake
But nothing ever comes out right
daiji de areba aru hodo
The more that I love you
Making one person happy may be different from making everyone happy.
gomakashite shimau no
The more I act like I don't
dakedo baby sweet berry love
But I'm in baby sweet berry love with you
But I still don't want to make any girls cry.
jibun no kokoro made
There are times when I don't know
wakaranai toki wa kimi to
How I really feel, and I want to
No matter what.
tashikameaitai no
See you and find out again
This is my first time alone with someone on a ferris wheel.
dakara baby sweet berry love
That's why baby sweet berry love
It's a fun experience.
onaji basho ni itai
I want to stay with you always
First time?
The Irish author Oscar Wilde, a man whose refreshing ideas I respect, once wrote,
"Men always want to be a woman's first love—
women like to be a man's last romance."
kimi to baby sweet berry love
I want a baby sweet berry love with you
It isn't refreshing at all when you say it.
jibun wo mamoru yori
I've found something more important
And why say that now?
Basically, since I'm the first you've gone on a ferris wheel with,
taisetsu na koto ga aru no
Than just protecting myself
Senpai.
konna ni mo chikaku ni
And it's right next to me
I'm your first—
Senpai.
Look.
kimi to baby sweet berry love
I want a baby sweet berry love with you
kitto gikochinakute
I know it'll be awkward
demo ne massugu ni mitsumete
But I want to look you straight in the eye
Eek.
sorairo utsushitai
So you can see a clear blue sky
motto baby sweet berry love
I want a more baby sweet berry love
Senpai,
my opinion of you had recently changed,
semete kimi no mae de wa
I wish that at least in front of you
but to think you'd plan to use a rabbit to do this...
waratte okotte afureta
I can smille and pout all I want
According to an anonymous source, you also did something shameless to Azuki-san in her dreams.
ari no mama de itai
I want to be myself
dakara baby sweet berry love
That's why baby sweet berry love
konna ni mo suki da yo
Can't you see how much I love you?
No, uh, this was coincidence,
and that was destiny...
c.u.t.e. funny cat
C-U-T-E funny cat
Or, I mean, this was... that was...
give me give me shiny time
Give me give me shiny time
p.r.e.t.t.y
P-R-E-T-T-Y
Do you have anything
to say for yourself?
tiny tiny berry love
Tiny, tiny berry love
Then I will give you my verdict.
You're absolutely, positively, absotively, right down to the last second of the last cut of the last episode...
zutto baby sweet berry love
Forever baby sweet berry love
a hopeless pervert.