I wish...
I wish there was a way we could confirm the past ourselves.
Your wish has reached me.
Cat god?!
Tsukiko!
Sen... pai...
Senpai?
What just...
We had a run in with the cat god.
What did he do?
This place feels different.
The cat god must have done something.
So what if we don't got a ball?
You know what they say! "Do with less so they'll have enough!"
Have I met you bef—
What're you doing, slow shit!
What's your deal?
Get turned on by little kids, pervert?
I'll call the cops on you if I see you again!
A hundred times!
Hey, wait up!
Wait up, I said!
Wasn't that...
Senpai.
Take a look at this.
Um...
Mayoral Election
Vote on November 16, 2003
Mayoral election... Vote on November 16...
Mayoral Election
Vote on November 16, 2003
2003?!
It seems the cat god granted my wish in an absolutely unbelieveable way.
I wished we could confirm the past ourselves.
We've gone back in time ten years.
mou ikkai kocchi muite..
One more time, look this way
iitai koto ga motto aru kara..
There's still more that I want to tell you
mou ikkai kocchi muite..
One more time, look this way
honki ga yureru ai no future..
Who you love's going to change in the future
dakara kocchi muite..
That's why you should look this way
maware chikyuu koi wo nosete..
The world turns, filled with love
dakara kocchi muite..
That's why you should look this way
guuzen ja nai fantafuture..
It wasn't just chance, it's our fantastic future
watashi kara sasou yuuki wo
watashi
kara
sasou
yuuki
wo
To have the courage to ask you out myself
kudasai to tsuki ni negau no
kudasai
to
tsuki ni
negau
no
I wished on the moon that I could
setsunai kokoro ni mahou kaketemimashou
setsunai
kokoro
ni
mahou
kaketemimashou
Let's cast a little spell on that breaking heart
mirai he no chikamichi ne
mirai
he
no
chikamichi
ne
It's the fastest way to the future
amaku naare egao de
With a smile I'm making even sweeter
kimi yo tokechae
I'll make your whole self melt
kyou no yozora wo mitsume
Tonight I'll look at the sky
chotto senobite
And try to reach a little closer
mou ikkai kocchi muite..
One more time, look this way
iitai koto ga motto aru kara..
There's still more that I want to tell you
mou ikkai kocchi muite..
One more time, look this way
honki ga yureru ai no future..
Who you love's going to change in the future
dakara kocchi muite..
That's why you should look this way
maware chikyuu koi wo nosete..
The world turns, filled with love
dakara kocchi muite..
That's why you should look this way
guuzen ja nai fantafuture..
It wasn't just chance, it's our fantastic future
W-We've gone back in time?!
What do we do now?!
Inside Tsutsukakushi-san's Home
We might never get back to the future!
By the time we get back to our original time,
we'll have four, five... eleven kids!
It's a wish from the cat god.
If I cancel it, we'll go right back,
you hopeless pervert from the future.
We can go back at any time.
There's no reason to panic and cancel now.
First, let's see if my mom is at work.
Your mom?
We'll be able to see if my sister and I lived with her if we do.
Oh, I see.
And if I can prove that I met you in the past,
I'll be the one—
Oh, my.
My, my. Thank you.
I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
A-chan, come on. Say "Thank you."
A-chan?
Onii-chan... Thank... you.
Why were you staring at that girl?
Is your batting average that low?
No! Yoshida Kenkou once wrote
that sometimes you should
look at things yet to ripen!
Adoring young girls is perfectly natural!
Honestly. You're a hopeless pervert in idleness.
Oh. I think that's...
Amazing.
Amazing, amazing, amazing.
Tsutsukakushi!
Amazing.
Amazing, amazing.
Amazing, amazing, amazing.
Too amazing.
Far too amazing.
What's up, Tsutsukakushi?
Far too amazed.
Senpai, allow me to introduce you.
This is Yokodera Youto-kun,
six years old.
Nice to meet you, Onii-chan.
Huh?
No way.
I'm sorry.
Onii-san here is just surprised at how polite you are.
Don't worry! I'm more surprised that a pretty little lady like yourself would talk to me!
Honestly.
You have such a way with words, Youto-kun.
That tickles, Onee-chan!
Adoring things yet to ripen is perfectly natural.
If I raise him in a sanitized environment,
in ten years, he'll be the next Hikaru Genji.
Listen well.
Grow up the way you are now.
Do not screw up your life by turning into a pervert.
Okay!
I'll try to be a cool grown-up like Onii-chan!
Are you waiting for your mom to pick you up?
No.
I'm waiting for Miss Tsutsukakushi Tsukasa to finish work!
Miss Tsutsukakushi Tsukasa?
You're here again, freaking kid?
Old Lady Tsukasa!
I told you not to call me an old lady, freaking kid.
Sorry, Old Lady Tsukasa. Whoops.
Old Lady Tsukasa.
Oh, sorry.
Old Lady Tsukasa!
All right!
Not right. Nowhere near right, freaking kid.
Tsukiko-chan, is that...
Yes.
What're you here for today?
My mom.
You'd better not ask for that again.
Or at least, I think so.
My mom and dad can't come home today,
so I thought maybe you could feed me tonight.
And, if things work out, maybe I could sleep over too!
No way any of that'll work out.
You graduated. I got no reason to deal with you, freaking kid.
You don't need a reason! You just need love!
Don't got love, neither.
I hate kids.
And I hate you most of all.
She feels kind of different from the photos.
Rather.
Quite.
Very different.
So I can't?
You're bothering me. Now go home.
Okay.
I'll go home.
Just one night.
Yay!
Huh?
We need to see if Nee-san was right.
Um... Mo—Tsukasa-san.
What do you want?
And who are you?
I'm Kikko Y. Azukiela.
This is my brother, Toyo T. Azukiela.
And we're step-siblings, so there are no legal problems.
So?
There's something we'd like to ask you.
I know!
Why don't you have dinner with us?
Huh?
Hey, don't get ahead of yourself, freaking kid.
Please, Tsukasa-san?
I said, no.
Okay... Never mind—
Just this once.
Never happening again.
Okay!
The Tsutsukakushi residence is the same ten years in the past.
Or so I thought. It isn't.
Seriously, how much trouble can one kid cause?
Eat up. I made it myself.
Tsukasa-san isn't much for housework.
It must be a huge shock for Tsukiko-chan.
Or so I thought. It isn't.
Thank you for the meal.
Sorry I wasn't able to assist you in preparing this lovely meal.
Seriously. Way too much trouble.
I'm full.
Got room for more, don't you?
Thank you very much.
Me too!
I want seconds too!
Mind your manners, freaking kid!
I'm sorry.
Pick one.
Yay!
Thanks, Tsukasa-san!
Don't get a brain freeze, freaking kid.
Do you have a place to stay tonight?
If you don't, why not stay here?
But...
It's okay!
Tsukasa-san's always lonely!
Huh?
You got the wrong idea, freaking kid.
Okay, never mind.
I'm going to be busy tomorrow, anyway.
I need to do something really, really important.
Okay. Never mind.
I'll be—
Okay! Never mind!
Stay in the first floor guest room.
Thanks!
I love you, Tsukasa-san!
Get off me! I'll get all sticky!
Have a nice, relaxing time, Onii-chan, Onee-chan!
I've had enough for today.
I'm going to sleep.
Here. Breakfast.
Okay! Thanks!
Is this what she always has for breakfast?
Not always.
Sometimes she has potato chips.
I thought she'd be a better mother.
Tsukiko-chan?
Tsukasa-san's a nice person.
She just doesn't mind what she eats because she lives alone.
Huh?
Hold on... She lives alone?
Yeah.
She's always alone and looks so lonely,
so I try to see her as much as I can.
I... see...
Tsukasa-san... doesn't live with Miss Steel or Tsukiko-chan?
Maybe Miss Steel's memories are wrong?
And my memories too.
I don't remember meeting Tsukasa-san when I was young.
Something just doesn't click.
I've worn this tracksuit a lot now.
Huh?
Huh? Onii-chan?
Hey.
What are you doing here?
I've been charged with being Onee-chan's guard!
Oh, really?
Have fun with that.
You can't go in now.
Onee-chan's in there,
trying on underwear she
borrowed from Tsukasa-san.
Are you okay?
Look out!
Man, that was a close one!
No need to worry now!
Senpai.
For future reference, what were you worried about?
He's too young to see Tsukiko-chan's fair skin!
Tsukiko-chan's chastity and the boy's innocence!
Both preserved for another—
Huh?
I can't see anything.
And this bra is too big for—
For some reason, I can't remember what happened these last few hours.
I have a feeling I saw something flat.
Whoa! A giant hedgehog?!
What are you doing here?
Tsukasa-san?
Didn't you go to bed?
I couldn't fall asleep after changing into my pajamas.
There's something I want to finish by tomorrow, anyway.
Those are pajamas?
Um...
Mind if I ask a question?
Where's your family?
Why're you asking?
No, um, I don't mean to pry, but...
Well, guess you'd want to ask after seeing this huge house.
There used to be a lot more people living here,
including my daughters.
Two of them.
They loved me, until the family fell apart.
Fell apart?
My husband suddenly died, and some other stuff.
But in the end,
I ruined it all.
Then what about your daughters?
They're with my husband's family in Italy.
But tomorrow...
They might...
Huh?
Doesn't matter.
Hit the sack.
Is Tsukasa-san still asleep?
Her alarm went off a while ago.
But yeah, she hasn't come down.
She said she had something important today, didn't she?
Oh, she was going to measure my height today too!
Height?
Yeah.
Tsukasa-san measures me once a month.
...like these marks my mother made to keep track of my height.
Maybe Miss Steel's memories are wrong?
A car?
Is she expecting guests?
I'll answer the door. Could you wake Tsukasa-san up?
Okay.
Onii-chan, hurry up!
They're coming now!
C-Could this be...
Tsutsukakushi ten years ago?!
Please.
O-Okay.
Um...
Who's this?
Tsukiko!
M-Miss Steel?!
Go back to the car, Tsukiko.
Okay.
You must be Tsukasa-san's daughter.
Who are you?
Bring my mother out at once.
I have a right to ask why she broke her promise.
What kind of promise?
We crossed the ocean with our grandparents to discuss our future.
Yet she did not show herself at the hotel at which we are staying.
Is this insult to mean that she does not need her daughters?
N-No! You're overthinking things!
You should not know, knave!
If she truly treasured us, she would have come running to us at all costs!
Would she not?!
It could be said that this was a litmus test of her devotion
to determine if she had the revovosolve to raise—
Uh, sorry?
What do you mean?
Repeat after me.
Treaty of Tordesillas.
Tweety of Tordenianias?
Sri Lanka
Sri Jayawardenapura Kotte
India
Sri Lanka
Sri Jayawardenapura Kotte
India
Sri Lanka
Sri Jayawardenapura Kotte
India
Sri Lanka
Sri Jayawardenapura Kotte.
Sriwawayapa—
Sri Lanka
There, there.
That must have hurt.
Acting all tough but soft on yourself.
Unhand me, knave!
Rubbing your filthy hands on me!
Insolent rogue!
Shameless villain!
Villainous cad!
But you liked it just now...
Right?
She looked super happy.
Silence! Silence!
You dare claim that I felt any such emotion!
You shall die for this sin!
Ow!
Quit it!
Didn't your mother ever teach you that it's wrong to throw stones?
I have no mother!
You do!
And she's inside this house!
That woman...
That woman who cast us aside...
has no right to call herself our mother!
Quit being cranky!
You don't know! Tsukasa-san's always—
Shut up! Shut up!
If she doesn't need her daughters, then her daughters don't need her!
You've grown so much since I saw you last, Tsukushi.
I don't know you!
I don't... know you!
You're no mother of mine!
Tsukushi!
I never want to see you again!
Mom.
Let's go!
Only natural, right?
Tsukasa-san...
You're a failure as a mother.
A mother...
A mom should love her daughters.
I do love them.
Then you should chase after them no matter what they say.
Why not tell them that you love them?
H-Hey, don't fight...
I'm sorry.
I went too far.
No.
It's okay.
Hey, freaking kid.
Put 'em on.
Um...
Old Lady Tsukasa?
Seriously, those dicks?
Callin' me a punk just 'cuz we met in high school?
I'm a boy...
This is just wrong!
You shoulda seen their faces when we said we'd elope!
Oh, that was rich!
All right. This one next, freaking kid.
Do I have to?
It's about time we stopped her, huh?
Huh?
Tsukiko-chan?
My body feels kind of hot.
Huh?
Hold on, she got drunk from the fumes?
Oh, my, if it isn't Youto-kun.
You've grown so much since I saw you last.
Um... Hold on...
Did you grow up innocent like I told you to?
Wh-What are you doing?
I'm taking off your clothes. What else would I do after that?
Ts-Tsukiko-chan?
H-Hey...
You smell nice, Youto-kun.
Um... Are you okay?
Sure you've got the right guy?
I know I've got the right guy.
Hold on!
You're my Youto-kun.
Tsutsukakushi?
Youto-kun, mine and all mine.
Lick.
Tsukiko-chan?!
As long as you don't become a pervert...
A-Am I dead or alive? I can't tell.
Free yourself from earthly desires.
Old Lady Tsukasa? I'm a boy, you know?
No earthly desires!
I'm a boy...
Those clothes...
You made them yourself?
Were you going to give them as gifts?
To your daughters?
Were you making them all last night too?
Just a way to pass the time.
Why did you let your daughters go?
I-If...
If you love them that much...
They were only supposed to take care of them for a short while.
But...
Things ended up dragging out way longer than expected.
The authorities won't let me on a plane.
I couldn't go to get them.
Things happened, one after another, until they said they wanted to take custody of the kids...
and I thought maybe that'd be the best for them.
But I just couldn't give up.
Now I'm a mess.
Bet they wouldn't want to see their mother like this.
Mo—I think they still love you, Tsukasa-san.
Even if they did, they won't after today.
You're drinking too much.
For some reason, everything you say feels like something from my daughter.
Then listen to me.
You can change things, even now.
So...
It's okay.
It's too late now.
Either way, I'm out of time—
Tsukasa-san!
She's burning up!
Hang in there!
Tsukasa-san!
kimi ni baby sweet berry love
I'm in baby sweet berry love with you
honto no kimochi dake
It would be so nice if I could
wakeaetara ii no ni na
Share with you how I really feel
negai wo kanaete yo
Make my wish come true
c.u.t.e. funny cat
C-U-T-E funny cat
give me give me shiny time
Give me give me shiny time
p.r.e.t.t.y
P-R-E-T-T-Y
tiny tiny berry love
A tiny, tiny berry love
daisuki no heart mo
My heart full of love for you
gomen ne no namida mo
And these tears because I'm sorry
honto wa sunao ni misetakute
I really wish I could just show them to you
tsutaetai omoi to
I want to tell you that I feel this way
uragaeshi no taido
But the opposite is what I always say
jouzu ni narenai
I just can't do it right
kokoro moyou
Expressing myself
doushite karamawari
Why can't I get on the ball?
mune ga gyutto naru
My chest feels so tight
chigau kyorikan ga
Feeling so close to you
modokashii yo nee
Frustrates me so much
todoketai no
I want you to know
kimi to baby sweet berry love
I want a baby sweet berry love with you
kitto gikochinakute
I know it'll be awkward
demo ne massugu ni mitsumete
But I want to look you straight in the eye
sorairo utsushitai
So you can see a clear blue sky
motto baby sweet berry love
I want a more baby sweet berry love
semete kimi no mae de wa
I wish that at least in front of you
waratte okotte afureta
I can smille and pout all I want
ari no mama de itai
I want to be myself
dakara baby sweet berry love
That's why baby sweet berry love
issho ni hajimeyou
Let's start together
The Pervert Prince and Outside the Memories
Next time: The Pervert Prince and Outside the Memories.