Miss Emanuela!
That's enough!
Why can't you stay in
tune with everyone else?
You are hindering everyone's practice!
Wait right th—
Huh?
What's wrong?
Are you stuck up there?
It's okay now.
No need to be scared.
So that's where you were!
So you saved her? Thanks.
mou ikkai kocchi muite..
One more time, look this way
iitai koto ga motto aru kara..
There's still more that I want to tell you
mou ikkai kocchi muite..
One more time, look this way
honki ga yureru ai no future..
Who you love's going to change in the future
dakara kocchi muite..
That's why you should look this way
maware chikyuu koi wo nosete..
The world turns, filled with love
dakara kocchi muite..
That's why you should look this way
guuzen ja nai fantafuture..
It wasn't just chance, it's our fantastic future
watashi
kara
sasou
yuuki
wo
watashi kara sasou yuuki wo
To have the courage to ask you out myself
kudasai
to
tsuki ni
negau
no
kudasai to tsuki ni negau no
I wished on the moon that I could
setsunai
kokoro
ni
mahou
kaketemimashou
setsunai kokoro ni mahou kaketemimashou
Let's cast a little spell on that breaking heart
mirai
he
no
chikamichi
ne
mirai he no chikamichi ne
It's the fastest way to the future
amaku naare egao de
With a smile I'm making even sweeter
kimi yo tokechae
I'll make your whole self melt
kyou no yozora wo mitsume
Tonight I'll look at the sky
chotto senobite
And try to reach a little closer
mou ikkai kocchi muite..
One more time, look this way
iitai koto ga motto aru kara..
There's still more that I want to tell you
mou ikkai kocchi muite..
One more time, look this way
honki ga yureru ai no future..
Who you love's going to change in the future
dakara kocchi muite..
That's why you should look this way
maware chikyuu koi wo nosete..
The world turns, filled with love
dakara kocchi muite..
That's why you should look this way
guuzen ja nai fantafuture..
It wasn't just chance, it's our fantastic future
Emi was, without a doubt, in the album.
The Happy Prince
She wasn't part of Ponta's family, but she was there.
The school became Italy, and the uniform became swimsuits.
Why did Emi wish on the cat god for this?
Tsutsukakushi wasn't waiting for me.
I guess she's still mad.
Huh? You sister's gone missing?
Yeah, you know, Yaji-san.
It's been two nights since she ran away.
I can't sleep without her, so I've been searching all over.
Uh...
Isn't Emi your sister?
Emi? Sorry, but who's that?
Yaji-san's my one and only sister.
If you don't mind,
could you search for her too?
S-Sure.
Thanks.
It seems her wish to be Ponta's
sister has been canceled.
Emi might have something to do with Yaji-san's disappearance.
I might have to ask her directly.
But will she give me a straight answer?
I'm worried for Yaji-san too.
We're talking about animals.
She might be able to help.
Wait! I need to ask you for a favor!
No... Why...
No! Stay away from me!
I-If you do anything bad,
I'll make you regret it!
You can't move. Just stay still.
You'll really regret it!
I'll get you out of there.
Why?
Why do keep doing weird things to me?
I'm not doing anything this time.
You keep running away
whenever I try to talk to you.
I'm not running away.
Can we put an end to this?
Let's just get along like we normally do.
I-I am being normal...
But I... just don't want to be near you.
I want to make up with you.
My life feels empty without you.
Let's not think in terms of near or far.
Could we go back to normal?
The captain has the wrong idea.
She doesn't really want to be friendly with me.
It's someone else.
Someone else?
Well, she's mistaken me with someone who's like a younger brother to me.
But anyway, the captain doesn't love me.
I see.
But... Tsutsukakushi-senpai might be wrong now, but she might not be soon.
No, it's not just her. Someone else...
What about someone else?
I get what you're trying to say.
If you prove you'll stay loyal after
making up, we can go back to normal.
How can I prove it?
Like...
The prince gently...
takes the princess, and they...
kiss.
Huh?
Th-The prince gently takes a young village girl's hand, and they shake hands.
If we can make up with a
handshake, then I gladly will.
So... What did you want to ask me?
Okay, I can look for Yaji-san.
I'll ask the stray dogs around here.
S-Stray dogs?
Yes.
Woof!
Grr...
Woof, woof, woof!
Like that!
Strangely enough, I can talk to them!
Beyond human, huh?
What should I do?
You don't need to do anything.
Just do what you normally do.
See you,
Yokodera-kun.
The swallow can't say no to the prince.
And so, the swallow—
Tsu-chan!
You're specially, psychedelically tone deaf!
It's too bad! You have a really nice voice!
Your song is like a rafflesia!
Emanuela-san,
supposing, against the fact,
that I am tone deaf,
I'm good at drawing, good at cooking, and I give massages every day.
I'm a utility player.
So it's fine.
I'm better than you in more ways than one.
You think so?
I think I'm better than you at sports!
No, I'm better.
No, I'm better! Eat my dust!
Um...
I think a race can settle this.
Then let's race!
Ready...
Go!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Innertube, yahoo!
The sea, as wide as the eye can see!
Wow, it's cold!
Yahoo!
What a race.
I can't tell who's in elementary school anymore.
Inner-inner-innertube, inner, inner!
Who... won... the race?
Inner-inner-innertube!
You both finished at the same time.
Tsu-chan was faster than me!
I'll be fair and admit my defeat!
I see.
I'll practice so there's no doubt next time, Emanu—Emi-san.
Hey, Youto Onii-chan, did you have fun?
Yeah, I guess so.
I'm satisfied too!
So I think I'll cancel this wish now!
Everyone wants to go to the pool, cancel!
And then the teacher...
Ts-Tsutsukakushi!
Y-You've grown a lot since
the last time I saw you!
I'm satisfied with the pool!
So you'll cancel the other wishes when you're satisfied?
Huh?
You found out that I wished for all of this?
Yeah.
You weren't supposed to find out this soon.
They lied to me.
Lied to you? Who?
So, what'll you do with
the culprit, Youto Onii-chan?
Punish them?
I won't do anything.
But if you made Yaji-san—Ponta's rabbit—
go missing, could you cancel that right away?
Ponta's really worried for her.
Yaji-san's gone missing? That's terrible!
You didn't wish for it?
No.
You were part of a church choir, right?
And Ponta and Yaji-san—
Youto Onii-chan, you finally remember?!
Not everything, but...
I don't think we were that close.
Why?
How can you say that?
This is so boring!
I don't like boring!
A long time ago, I got
along great with Onii-chan.
When Papa said we had to go back to Italy,
Onii-chan pinky swore with me.
When I came back to Japan,
he'd play with me.
But I think I'll quit now.
I'm tired.
Emi?
Please, Youto Onii-chan. This is my last wish.
Can you play with me
at the athletics festival?
If you do, I'll give up.
Give up?
On what?
You're such a pumpkin.
I can't wait for the athletics festival!
Thanks a bunch!
Yaji-san's back!
Oh, really?
You asked Azuki-san to look for her, right?
Azuki-san found her, and a girl named Emi brought her back home.
Huh?
Why Emi?
And after seeing her, I remembered!
She's the girl you were talking about, right?
That whiny, potty-mouthed girl?
So she's back from Italy?
She's really looking forward
to the athletics festival.
What, you don't remember her?
You got along with her way better than me.
He remembers Emi?
Yaji-san used to run into
that old church all the time.
I went there to look for her,
and you two were talking up a storm!
Anyway, thanks for everything! See you!
See you.
Why don't I remember?
Fire!
P-Perfect timing.
There's something I wanted to ask you.
Huh?
What kind of person was the "Onii-chan" you mentioned yesterday?
If you want to be friends
with him again, I can help.
Are you seriously saying that?
Of course.
I knew you were stupid, but I didn't think you had complete shit for brains!
A pumpkin will always be a pumpkin!
I'm sick of this!
I'm canceling everything!
Cat god! Reset everything!
Cancel all the wishes I made!
Ha!
You can't do shit for me,
you god damn pumpkin.
Wh-Why are you suddenly so mad?
And why'd you wish to the
cat god in the first place?
I'm sure you had a reason.
I didn't like it, so I wished
for whatever I wanted.
Like how uncool you were, and swimsuits, and a 100 percent smile.
Whatever you wanted?
It's a helpful little god, after all.
The cat god isn't just some fix-all tool!
There's a girl out there who was so worried that she unconsciously wished on it!
You didn't know that, did you?!
Unlike you, just wishing on whims!
What are you—
Listen, Emi.
What's truly important to you won't change whether you wish or not.
Why?
How can you say what's
important won't change?
How?! When you completely
forgot about me and our promise!
Crazy pumpkin! Rotten squash!
Stinking gourd! Get your
golden acorns mashed!
Emi...
Pumpkin-headed pumpkin pants!
Your momma's a jack o' lantern!
Church choir, promise...
Why can't I remember?
Senpai.
Are you okay?
Yeah, just thinking about some stuff.
The evil woman has you by the nose?
That girl is bad.
Definitely not.
Understand?
I'm sorry.
But Emi canceled all her wishes. I don't think anything bad—
No. It's not over yet.
What's not over?
This is still Italy.
What? Why?!
She canceled her wishes.
I saw it with my own eyes.
Could this be Miss Steel's wish?
There you are, Yokodera.
Captain?
I'm going to Italy next month.
Huh?
But that's so sudden! Why?
A school over there saw our school become Italian and was unusually interested
in a sister school exchange program.
I was chosen as the first
exchange student under it.
Does that mean... this was your—
No. I've tried canceling any
Italy wishes over and over.
This is not my wish.
Then... whose...
Emi...
No, we can't find the entrance!
That's impossible! Look harder!
O-Okay.
The girl from the other day?
I wonder what she's up to.
I want to talk to her.
No. I need to.
I'll find a way for you.
Here?
I saw her go in there a minute ago.
Thanks.
Sorry I have to rely on you for everything
I'll do whatever it takes to
make your wishes come true,
Yokodera-kun.
Emi!
Stay away, pumpkin!
Don't do anything hasty!
Let's talk!
I kept thinking about what I wanted to say to you first when I got back to Japan.
I couldn't wait to see you for so long.
But you...
You didn't care about me at all!
Acting like an older brother, but just
screwing around with a stupid little girl!
And then you forgot our
promise as soon as I left!
Please, don't cry—
That's right.
I went to the church looking for something,
and I tried to cheer up a girl the nuns had gotten mad at.
Ugh, I can't remember anything else.
Am I the only thing you've forgotten?
Are you forgetting anything else important from the past?
Like a girl with a 100 percent perfect smile?
100 percent?
You didn't pray to the cat god for that?
No.
They said I was borrowing the
smile of the girl you once loved.
The girl I once loved...
What was that?
Problem solved, Yokodera-kun?
All thanks to me again.
Do you know the story of The Happy Prince?
It's a charming story.
A prince and a swallow help everyone,
and he dies, satisfied.
But what about the swallow?
She does everything, devoted to the foolish prince, but her own wish was never granted.
Was the swallow truly happy?
That's how it always goes.
The prince and the people are all happy.
But what about the swallow?
She helped the prince more than anyone,
but why didn't he ever consider her wishes?
Tell me, why?
Who are you?
It's me.
Your dear friend, Azuki-chan.
The Azuki Azusa I know
doesn't talk like that.
Very well.
Perhaps I should apologize
for the other day.
You had quite the experience in the Tsutsukakushi family storehouse.
You had me on pins and needles.
The cat god?!
Why are you inside Azuki Azusa?!
She wished for it.
To be a different person.
Azuki Azusa wished for that?
I sit back and watch for the most part,
but I'll take over when it's necessary.
Like for the rabbit incident.
You... Why are you doing this?
How dare you take
advantage of Azuki Azusa?!
Hey, now.
I'm simply helping her.
When you want to cancel a wish, I'll cancel it.
I'm completely fair. You should be praising me.
But you criticize me instead? How silly!
Liar!
I canceled my wishes! Why is the school still Italy?!
This place is your wish,
but at the same time, it isn't.
This is Yokodera-kun's wish!
Yokodera-kun's wish transported you here,
and you turned the school
buildings into a bit of Italy.
And so, Tsutsukakushi Tsukushi will
happily be an exchange student in Italy.
In other words, you were simply a stepping stone to fulfilling Yokodera-kun's wish.
What...
Hold on! How is it my...
Oh, right.
You don't remember.
So you don't know why.
You wished for it years ago.
That Tsutsukakushi Tsukushi could go to Italy when she grew up.
No way...
If you don't believe me,
then try canceling the wish.
However, whatever was summoned to fulfill the wish will disappear.
Shut up!
You should just...
Just go to hell!
You wished for it.
You wished for me to do it.
And so, I'll grant your wish.
As you wished, I'll go to hell.
Along with Azuki Azusa.
Is that okay with you, Yokodera-kun?
If you cancel your wish, the stepping
stone's wish may be canceled as well.
She'll disappear, and Azuki Azusa may be saved.
Does the prince who made the swallow suffer
intend for her to sacrifice herself yet again?
She's simply a stepping stone.
Or is it that you can't show your loyalty to her?
Loyalty to Azuki Azusa...
Like...
The prince gently...
takes the princess, and they...
kiss.
Onii-chan...
Cancel it.
Perfect.
You never make the wrong choice.
That's you.
I'll cancel the wish.
First, I'll change this school back to normal, and eliminate the step—
Y-You—
What are you—mph!
Huh?! What?
Wh-What?!
Pervert?! Kiss?!
How's the athletics festival?
Stay away from me, pumpkin!
Don't kiss people in public!
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
I-I'll see you again when
I'm ready, so wait for me.
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow,
or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
No subject
I-I'll see you again when I'm ready, so wait for me.
I can't today, but maybe tomorrow, or the day after, or the day after that...
I get the feeling we were able to make up.
Senpai.
How about lunch?
Let's do it.
How about you, Emi?
I-If you insist, I can.
Chomp.
Ooh, a delicious chomp-chomp!
kimi ni baby sweet berry love
I'm in baby sweet berry love with you
honto no kimochi dake
It would be so nice if I could
wakeaetara ii no ni na
Share with you how I really feel
negai wo kanaete yo
Make my wish come true
c.u.t.e. funny cat
C-U-T-E funny cat
give me give me shiny time
Give me give me shiny time
p.r.e.t.t.y
P-R-E-T-T-Y
tiny tiny berry love
A tiny, tiny berry love
daisuki no heart mo
My heart full of love for you
gomen ne no namida mo
And these tears because I'm sorry
honto wa sunao ni misetakute
I really wish I could just show them to you
tsutaetai omoi to
I want to tell you that I feel this way
uragaeshi no taido
But the opposite is what I always say
jouzu ni narenai
I just can't do it right
kokoro moyou
Expressing myself
doushite karamawari
Why can't I get on the ball?
mune ga gyutto naru
My chest feels so tight
chigau kyorikan ga
Feeling so close to you
modokashii yo nee
Frustrates me so much
todoketai no
I want you to know
kimi to baby sweet berry love
I want a baby sweet berry love with you
kitto gikochinakute
I know it'll be awkward
demo ne massugu ni mitsumete
But I want to look you straight in the eye
sorairo utsushitai
So you can see a clear blue sky
motto baby sweet berry love
I want a more baby sweet berry love
semete kimi no mae de wa
I wish that at least in front of you
waratte okotte afureta
I can smille and pout all I want
ari no mama de itai
I want to be myself
dakara baby sweet berry love
That's why baby sweet berry love
issho ni hajimeyou
Let's start together
For the Longest Time
Next time: For the Longest Time.