Original Work
Seo Kouji
Kodansha
Weekly Shounen Magazine
I'm fine with watching baseball, but it's the Giants versus Yokohama.
I wish we could watch the Carps!
I wonder if we'll be able to meet any celebrities when we go to Tokyo.
I want to meet Sakurai Honoka so damn badly!
A
Train
Sakurai Honoka?! That'd be nice. I'd love to meet her too.
Approaching
Train
Akari, you finally understand me!
Approaching
Train
All right, everyone! Line up quickly!
Line up quickly!
The coaches are numbered 16, 15, and so on from the front.
The last coach coming in is coach number 1.
Platform
Class
Time
Destination
Open Seating Areas
Size
A
Nozomi
#120
10:44
Tokyo
1~3
16-coach
Hikari
#548
10:47
Shin-Osaka 1~4・7・8
8-coach
If you wish to smoke, please use the smoking rooms. Smoking in regular coaches is
We'll be going to Tokyo.
For a school trip?
Really? When?
Next week. It'll be a three-day trip.
I see! That's cool!
You'll be really nearby then, Haruto-kun!
Yeah.
Actually...
Why don't we meet for a little while?
I-It can be after you're done with school for the day.
I have free time until five.
Since I'll be going so far to meet you,
there's something I want to give you.
Yeah, all right.
Really?
You sure it works for you?
Yeah.
By the way, what is it you want to give me?
I'm not spoiling the surprise, but look forward to it.
So...
But I bet it won't be that easy to meet her.
Hey, were you listening?
I was!
Were you really?
Tokyo
Nozomi
Assigned Seating Only
Even for one minute is fine.
I want to see you no matter what.
"Whenever I saw Ojosan's face,"
"I felt that I had myself become beautiful."
"Whenever I thought of her, I felt a new sense of dignity welling up inside me."
Meet at 15:00
Haruto-kun
"If this incomprehensible thing that we call love..."
Eba was the first wind of spring that came a bit late.
My name is Eba Yuzuki, and I'm from Tokyo.
Nice to meet you!
Although I knew it was coming,
I didn't expect it to be so strong.
Damn it!
Why do I have to hide?
Why does she need to go to high school in the countryside?
She'll be living here when she's not even my relative!
Haruto-kun!
Your mom wants you to come down for some tea.
O-Okay.
She's no first spring wind. She's a damn storm.
With the strong wind obstructing my field of vision,
I was somewhat forced to accept the change in season.
I'm telling you, I can't ride a bike!
Amazing!
You're so fast!
You'll bite your tongue if you talk so much.
This is kind of fun!
Whoa, that's dangerous!
It's so fun!
The air here is great.
The sky is so clear too.
I'm speeding up!
Although Eba and I hadn't fallen in love yet...
we lived in the same house...
and we saw each other every day.
We were so close,
always within each other's reach.
But...
I really wanted you to see this.
Ice flowers!
They're so pretty!
I was planning on showing you these when it got really cold.
Luckily, we made it.
Thank you.
I won't forget this, even after I go back to Tokyo.
Don't go back to Tokyo.
Stay by my side forever.
Don't go back to Tokyo... and stay with me.
Everyone, your attention please!
We're going to the Tokyo Dome to watch the baseball game,
but it seems we'll get there ahead of schedule.
So you'll have some free time once we arrive.
You'll only have about an hour, though.
Make sure you get to the entrance on time!
We're on our way to the Tokyo Dome.
We're early, so we'll have free time there until five.
Haruto
A
We’re on our way to the Tokyo
Dome. We’re early so we’ll have
free time there until five.
Could we meet there
for a little bit?
Could we meet there for a little bit?
Oh right, I should bring that!
She's pretty! Really pretty!
Look, Takashi! They're shooting a TV show!
That's awesome!
Hey, Haruto, where are you going?
Sorry, I'll be back later!
Due to an accident at Okubo Station, JR Sobu Line will
A
Why does it have to be so...
Knock, knock.
Rin-chan?
Mom said to go take a bath since no one's using it now.
O-Okay, thanks.
Are you still doing that
long-distance relationship thing?
You meet and then what?
You'll just end up even lonelier.
It's just the next station. I can run there!
They're filming something for TV over there!
Wow, seriously?
Yeah, let's go watch!
Guess I'll wait until it's time to go.
Pedestrians
Automobiles
Only
There's something I want to give you.
Something you want to give me?
I'm not spoiling the surprise, but look forward to it.
That's why...
even if it's only for a minute...
even just for a moment...
I...
want to...
see you!
Haruto-kun!
So this is where you were.
Are you still doing that
long-distance relationship thing?
You'll just end up even lonelier.
I didn't expect you to come all the way to pick me up, Kanzaki.
Thanks.
Well, we're in the same class and all.
Our teacher will be mad at us if we're not on time.
Also...
U-Um...
Huh?
Kanzaki?
I-I want you...
to be my boyfriend!
"A woman is more happy when she is the sole object of affection”
Revenge for yesterday
"than when she is loved for reasons which transcend particular individuals."
"At least, I have noticed this tendency more in women than in men."
"My wife once asked me:"
"'Can't a man's heart and a woman's heart ever become a part of each other, so that they are one?"
Let's meet no matter what today.
I'll definitely be there by three!
Let’s meet no matter what today.
I’ll definitely be there by three!
I'm sorry!
Kirishima-kun!
I want you to be my boyfriend!
Boyfriend?
N-No, just pretend to be one, I mean.
Pretend?
I have a friend that moved to Tokyo when we were in elementary school,
and she wanted to meet up when I told her we'd be free on the second day of the trip.
What does that have to do with
pretending to be your boyfriend?
The thing is she bragged so much
about how her boyfriend is so kind and handsome.
And I somehow ended up telling her I also have a boyfriend.
Then she told me to bring him tomorrow.
Th-Then it doesn't have to be me. Maybe Takashi...
I know anyone will do,
but it's just pretend anyway!
What's wrong?
Um, well...
It's just...
Do I make you uncomfortable?
No, it's just that...
I have to meet Eba at three.
I know. I told my friend we're leaving at two.
I see. No problem, then.
Make sure you act like you're really my boyfriend while she's here, okay?
Well, I'll try.
U-Um...
What is it?
N-Never mind.
Actually,
why are there so many people here on a weekday afternoon?
Do Tokyoites have nothing else to do?
Let me introduce her. This is—
I'm Haruna! Nice to meet ya!
You're the boyfriend?
Oh, I'm Kirishima Haruto.
You're pretty handsome.
Don't worry, Nanami. I won't steal your boyfriend.
I-I wasn't thinking anything like that.
So how long have you been together?
How long?
Well...
we don't really know when it began.
He told me he loved me at a summer festival,
but I couldn't answer right away.
Oh, you didn't say okay right away?
Well, you're the shy type, so no surprise there.
Um, yeah, pretty much.
You were waiting for my answer, right?
You know...
I...
with you...
Haruto!
It's Yuzuki-chan!
But as we watched the fireworks together, I felt my heart pounding.
I realized I had feelings for him.
Yeah, yeah!
Asking a girl out while watching fireworks is super romantic!
And then?
When did you say yes?
Well, during the cultural festival, I guess.
The class decided on doing a café,
and he wanted to get some of our apples.
Since my family grows apples, remember?
So as we were going back home together...
Did you reject me because of Eba?
I see.
What made you say okay?
U-Um, but...
I...
All right.
I feel like I can give up on you now.
So let's become friends again.
No—
But I want to ask one thing of you.
That was...
Please don't tell Eba about this.
Huh?
It'd make it difficult for Eba to stay at my house if she heard about this.
I don't want her to go through something like that, even in the countryside.
So...
I lost to Kirishima-kun's sincerity, I guess.
Don't take me for a fool!
It seems he had feelings for me since middle school.
Why?
Why do you always choose Yuzuki-chan over me?
So I said okay.
I see. You've loved Nanami for a long time, huh?
My family runs a salted rib grill store!
Stop by sometime!
Yeah, of course!
You know...
Kanzaki...
I've always loved you!
Yeah, I've always loved her.
Long years of a one-sided love came to fruition, huh?
Well...
Let's stay friends.
I guess.
Then you've already had sex, right?
I mean, you're all lovey-dovey now, aren't ya?
O-Of course.
You guys are acting suspicious.
You're still calling each other by your last names, too.
Are you really going out?
Y-Yes, we are!
We're really close, right, Kanzaki?
Kanzaki?
We're going out,
and we're having sex too!
You can play with this.
What are you thinking, doing that in public?
You guys are hilarious.
See you. Mail me later.
Yeah, you too, Haruna-chan.
You could've at least squeezed her boobs.
You looked way too inexperienced.
She totally saw through us.
I did my best, though.
We'll look more like lovers this way.
I'm your boyfriend until this train leaves.
Yeah.
Eba?
Haruto-kun...
14:37 For Shibuya/Shinagawa
Train approaching
A
It's impossible.
Feelings change.
That's not true!
But yours changed, didn't they?
You loved Nanami-chan so much until a little while ago.
Feelings can change just like that.
Long-distance relationships never work out.
Twilight
Crossing
Twilight Crossing
Twilight
Crossing
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
tasogare kousaten kakeyoru
I run up to the twilight crossing
aitai to omou sonna kimochi wa
Our longing to meet each other
sora wo oyoideru kumo mitai ni
Are like clouds drifting in the skies
butsukatte tokete kieta
They bump into each other and melt away
itsukara darou surechigatteru
We've always been just passing by each other
sore demo dokoka de
Even still, I'm here
anata dake motometeiru
Only looking for you
aitakute sora ni egaita
Wanting to meet you, I drew in the skies
mirai eto tsuzuku negai
A wish that carries on into the future
kyou mo mata konna ni mo
Even today, you're still
mabushikute itoshikute
So bright and lovely
hidamari ni narande saiteru himawari mitai ni
Like the sunflowers that bloom toward the glowing sun
mitsumetetai kira kira my love
I want to see you, my shiny love