Are we there yet?
We'll be there soon.
Don't do that.
I'm so sorry.
Oh, it's okay.
Come on, tell her you're sorry.
I'm sorry!
It's all right.
Next stop
Ebisu
Bye-bye!
I'm... all right.
I'm all right.
Twilight Crossing 2
Women's
Bath
It was so crowded!
Yeah, it felt like a festival!
Did you go to Odaiba with your boyfriend?
Yeah, but Himuro-kun kept bugging me to go to a hotel with him.
Really?
That's horrible!
So did you go?
Of course not!
It's my fault.
What should I do?
Just leave them be!
Stuff like that's nothing new to their relationship, you know?
Still…
I'm pretty sure you're in trouble.
A
No new
messages
She saw her boyfriend holding hands with someone he used to love!
She didn't come to the meeting spot,
wouldn't pick up her phone,
and wouldn't answer texts either.
Jesus, what the hell is she doing?!
Am I even getting a signal?
Maybe she did call me a while ago!
That hurts.
What are you doing?
I should be asking you that!
What the hell are you doing?
Don't just sit there waiting for texts like a loser!
I'll...
go visit Eba's home!
It might be tough to get out through the front doors since the teacher's keeping watch.
Then how about using the emergency exit?
From there and through the parking lot, you should be able to get outside.
Then I'll distract the teacher just to be safe!
All right! We've got a perfect plan!
You guys are...
going to help me?
Well, yeah, and if we're gonna do it, we'll give it our all.
So buy me a drink!
Ice cream for me!
And it's gotta be Häagen Dazs green tea ice cream!
You've got until 10, when the teacher will be coming around for lights-out.
Go find her and make up by then!
I'm not going back like this!
No matter how angry she is,
even if she hates me now,
I want to see her.
I want to see her!
I wonder if Haruto and Yuzuki-chan met up by now.
I bet they did!
Whatever happens, they're bound by the red string of fate.
That was so out of character. So awkward!
What's your problem?
You? Talking about the red string of fate?
Takashi, just get me that over there!
Eba
I'm so stupid.
What the hell am I doing?
Haruto-san?
You scared me!
I was wondering who the creepy guy loitering outside my house could be.
I'm here for a school trip.
Can you call Eba for me?
I forgot to bring my phone.
I passed by her on my way back home.
What?
Where did she go?
Well, how would I know?
I can never figure out what she's thinking anyway.
Maybe she got a boyfriend and went to see him!
Long-distance relationships just don't last.
I believe in her!
Yeah, yeah. I'm not stopping you.
Wait! Please, can you call Eba for me?
She's probably just wandering around.
Just leave her, and she'll be back eventually.
I wouldn't mind if she never came back, though.
You know what she's always like.
Winning people over by acting like she can't do anything by herself.
She's just hungry for attention.
Seriously, she's irritating to watch.
What the hell are you talking about?!
She's not like tha—
You're the same, Haruto-san.
You're irritating to watch.
How long are you going to stand there?
I might call the police
and tell them I've got a stalker!
The night in Tokyo...
is so bright,
yet I can't even find her.
Give it up.
We don't have time. Let's get going.
Fine.
Did anyone say that the meeting place changed?
She's probably just wandering around.
Just leave her, and she'll be back eventually.
Not a chance!
I know!
I wouldn't mind if she never came back, though.
My name is Eba Yuzuki, and I'm from Tokyo.
Nice to meet you!
Your parents must be worried over letting you attend a high school this deep in the country.
Yes, but they let me since this is my dad's hometown,
and I'd be staying at an acquaintance's house.
But really, you're such a beautiful young lady!
When Eba came to Hiroshima, she was looking for a place to belong.
Thank you for the compliment.
I can't!
I can't do anything without you!
But I completely failed to notice that.
I'm not getting on.
What?
Take me back with you.
I'm not going to Tokyo.
She was just trying not to give in.
I drove her out.
I don't think of her as my big sister.
She was just enduring it.
Hello?
Eba, where are you right now?
Haruto-kun...
Right behind you!
She was just forcing a smile.
My dad got remarried.
My stepmother brought Rin-chan and Onii-san.
Because of that,
relationships are a little awkward in my family.
So...
Aren't we family?
Aren't I like your family too?
So it's okay to cry if you're having a hard time.
Then I'll do anything to help.
So...
I have to be her place to belong.
I need to be a steady, reliable man whom she can trust.
Yet...
Late!
You're late!
I sent you a text saying that I'd come meet you,
but you forgot to take your phone.
I even checked hotels. I looked for you everywhere!
I did hear about what you and Nanami-chan were doing,
but after seeing something like that, no one would—
I wanted to see you.
I wanted to see you...
so, so much.
That's not fair.
But I'm glad we could meet!
I was going to leave if you didn't show up in the next five minutes.
I see.
What's wrong?
Well, like...
Haruto-kun?
I'm sorry.
I said that I'd never make you feel alone,
but then I went and did something like that,
so I'm really, um...
sorry.
Forget about it.
But—
We're wasting time!
I want to talk about something other than apologies.
Okay.
Sorry, Eba.
I'm just dumb, slow-witted, and shy.
They're beautiful!
Hey, you!
What made you want to come to this town?
What?
The idea had to come from somewhere!
You came all the way here from Tokyo for school.
A long time ago, I visited this town once.
I really liked this place then.
That was the reason?
Yep.
But that's strange!
No, it's not!
No, no, that's just—
Does it matter?
Let's just say that was the reason.
I'm just dumb, slow-witted, and shy.
I couldn't really bring myself to hold your hand.
Since the moment we met, I must have been...
...in love with you,
probably since the moment we met,
all this time.
I've been in love with you for a whole lot longer.
Mom, this!
Akari, that way!
Whoa, Takashi, wait!
Hey!
Are you lost?
What's your name?
I won't tell you!
Why not?
I don't want to go back!
Huh? What do you mean?
I didn't want to come here!
H-Hey, don't cry!
Sheesh.
I'll take you to a nice place, then.
A nice place?
This is that nice place?
Yeah.
A flower blooms on this pond only once each year.
I don't see any flowers.
It's coming!
How's that?
See it blooming on the pond?
It's a huge flower!
It's so beautiful.
Thank you!
You finally smiled.
Do you like this town now?
Yeah!
Then no more crying.
It was because something bad happened,
but I feel all right now!
I see.
Then come back again if something happens!
Can I?
Yeah!
Promise me.
Sure.
It's a promise.
Here, this is for you.
It's in place of a birthday gift.
I got something too...
but I didn't bring it.
Don't mind it.
But as a boyfriend, I feel pathetic to be on the receiving end of things.
It's time for me to go.
Don't go back to Tokyo.
Don't go back to Tokyo... and stay with me.
It's impossible.
Feelings change.
That's not true!
But yours changed, didn't they?
You loved Nanami-chan so much until a little while ago.
Feelings can change just like that.
Long-distance relationships never work out.
Then it won't be a long-distance relationship!
If you feel that insecure,
I'll go to Tokyo with you!
You know that won't happen.
Even if you do, I'll be troubled.
To be honest, I was really happy...
when you asked me to be your girlfriend and said that you'd even go to Tokyo.
I...
I want to be with you for a while longer.
This isn't nearly enough.
I've got to go.
We have to say goodbye here. Send my regards to your friends.
I will.
The more exciting it was to meet,
the sadder it feels to say goodbye, huh?
Is something wrong?
Uh, no.
I was just thinking it's painful...
to be in a long-distance relationship.
Then should we break up?
Huh? What are you saying?
Take care, Haruto-kun.
See you later.
I'll...
I'll come see you again.
It's a promise.
Promise.
This is the one! The omelet rice from this restaurant called Amami was really good!
That looks delicious!
The waitresses were super cute too!
I want to see them again.
Then you can go to Tokyo alone!
Oh, I will!
You'll come too, right, Haruto?
Oh, yeah, I'll go too.
What? You weren't even listening, were you?
I was listening!
Come on, Nanami-chan, tell him something too!
No, I don't really...
We'll be living away from each other for a while,
Haruto's always like this!
but I'm sure we'll be all right.
I bet Yuzuki-chan is all that's on his mind!
Our relationship transcends time and distance
because our minds are connected.
Our long-distance love relationship...
has only just begun.
tasogare kousaten kakeyoru
I run up to the twilight crossing
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
aitai to omou sonna kimochi wa
Our longing to meet each other
sora wo oyoideru kumo mitai ni
Are like clouds drifting in the skies
butsukatte tokete kieta
They bump into each other and melt away
itsukara darou surechigatteru
We've always been just passing by each other
sore demo dokoka de
Even still, I'm here
anata dake motometeiru
Only looking for you
aitakute sora ni egaita
Wanting to meet you, I drew in the skies
mirai eto tsuzuku negai
A wish that carries on into the future
kyou mo mata konna ni mo
Even today, you're still
mabushikute itoshikute
So bright and lovely
hidamari ni narande saiteru himawari mitai ni
Like the sunflowers that bloom toward the glowing sun
mitsumetetai kira kira my love
I want to see you, my shiny love