How about coming to my place?
I'm poor, there isn't much room,
and I don't really have anything,
but the three of you can stay together.
Onii...
What are you talking about?
Don't get caught up in the moment.
I mean, you might be related to Hina, but you have absolutely no relation to Sora or Miu.
Who cares?
That doesn't matter at all.
Family has to...
...stay together!
happy happy girl
itsu kara kana fushigi
When did it happen? It's so strange
kono mune no oku wa
The deepest parts of my heart
kimi no kakera bakari
Are filled with bits of you
doushiyou haato bousou
What should I do? My heart's gone crazy
doki doki deeto no souzou
Imagining a date that'll happen, maybe
kyunte tobihanechau kodou
Beating like it'll fly out of me
shizen ni hoppeta potte
Without thinking, my hands are on my cheeks
somaru no kakushitemo ki ga tsuite yo
But hiding them won't help, I already know
katamuiteku kokoro no kakudo
My heart's compass keeps turning to one place
omoi no shisen wa kimi muki
My feelings point right to you
mou koi wo shiteru
I'm already in love
happy happy girl
eeru wo okurasete
Let me cheer you on
kimi ga mezasu sora idaku
I want to see the same world as you
yume wo issho ni oikakeru yo
Let's chase our dreams together from now on
candy candy love
riido wa mada mada tayorinai kamo demo
I might not be very reliable right now
senaka ni yorisou
But if I can become
sasae ni ne naretara
Someone that you can lean on,
sotto sotto suki de itemo ii desu ka
Then can I keep on loving you like this?
I Won't Cry
Hey, where did they go?
There's no one
on the second floor.
They couldn't have...
Anyway, let's look for them over at the station.
We might be able to catch them.
I can't believe this.
Hey, Uncles.
What's that yellow thing?
Hm?
That's the Seibu Line.
What about that silver one?
That's the Chuo Line.
What's this one?
This is the Chuo Line too.
No way!
Ow.
That hurt, you know?
That hurt, you know!
I'm talking about you.
I'm talking about you!
Calm down, Hina.
Don't be so loud.
Hm? Why?
You're bothering everyone else.
Bothering?
Uncle, do you have any regrets?
Huh?
What are you talking about?
We basically just cut everyone off.
Yeah, I guess so.
Don't you think things will get pretty tough?
Maybe.
Oh well!
You're with two cute girls and another cute girl in the making.
You must be pretty happy.
Um, Miu-chan...
Yes?
You sure got over everything quick...
Well, when we ran away from home,
it was kind of like a movie, you know?
I got all excited.
Well, that's good, then.
We're finally here!
It's like we're on a trip!
Hey, where are we going?
The zoo?
A theme park?
Unauna Heaven Show?
What kind of heaven is that?
Runa Runa Seven.
It's a Sunday morning superhero girl anime.
Runacular Sparkle!
What's that about?
You say it too, Uncles!
Huh?
Come on! Runacular...!
Sparkle!
This place is more like a city than I thought.
You know, I don't think the people here would take that very well.
But with this much stuff here, I don't think we'll have a problem with stuff like shopping.
You're pretty optimistic.
Huh?
In order to get to my apartment, we must first ride on that for quite a while longer!
We're getting on another train?
But first...
Yay! Yay! It's lunch time! Restarnant!
H-Hey! It's restaurant!
Say it right. Res-tau-rant.
Res-tar-nant!
Oh, well.
Let's eat here.
Looks good to me.
Sounds good!
Yay!
Okay, let's go.
Oh, no...
I forgot!
Today's Sunday!
Everyone's out with their family!
It might be a little hard for them
to see people having fun like that.
This place is full!
This place doesn't have self-serve drinks.
Hey, look! There's no peoples in here!
Special Menu
Skirt Steak Meal
Ribs Meal
Look at these prices!
I want to eat here!
I'm not sure about this place...
Why don't we eat at the
restaurant we were just at?
But...
No, I wanna eat here!
Stop it, you two.
Listen to what he says.
Fine.
So where are we going?
How about...
I know! Let's eat there!
( runa runa runa runa runa runa ~7 )
Seven!
kinkyuu jitai nan desu
otome junjou karen ni
Hey everybody, it's an emergency
Girls, be caring and cute
It sounds like an anime from another planet.
Hey, Onee-chan, sing this.
That's a duet!
Yeah, so sing it with Uncle.
I couldn't sing that!
In that case, I guess I'll go have fun with Uncle instead!
Sure, I'll sing whatever.
Here you go.
Your order of fried chicken and fries.
Who's that?
U-Uh...
Someone from my club at school.
Yay.
Sorry, something came up.
I'll make it up to you later.
Sorry!
What's going on in there?
You can't get with the girl you want, so you're going to the dark side instead?
Those are my nieces, you idiot.
They're my sister's kids.
You mean Yuri-san? That hot, nice, really hot sister of yours?
Yeah...
A lot of stuff happened, and well... I kind of ended up with them.
I see. Good thing I didn't report you.
Come on!
Call
Incoming
Aunt Yoshiko
Crap.
What's wrong?
It's my aunt.
They were going to split the girls up,
but I couldn't stand for it, so I pretty much just took them with me.
Are you an idiot?
You need to pick it up then, don't you?
I'll make sure the girls have a good time.
So take your time talking to your aunt.
Nimura...
Tomorrow's waiting!
Aren't you gonna eat, Onee-chan?
Wait a little longer.
But it's getting cold!
It's fine. I'll wait.
Hey! You can't, Hina.
It's good.
Hi there, girls.
Huh? You're my uncle's...
I'm his good friend, Nimura Kouichi.
Nice to meet you.
Thank you!
A flower!
Looks like he's gonna be in the bathroom for a while.
So I'll be your bodyguard for a while.
Whee!
Oh, I see.
You're pretty handsome, Nimura-san.
Thanks. You're pretty cute yourself.
Do you dye your hair?
No, I was born with it.
What? I'm sure you could be
a model if you wanted.
Thanks!
Do you want to sing together?
Okay. Let's have some fun!
Hello?
Yuuta-san?
Yes.
What you did is unacceptable.
What do you intend to do?
Shalalala, runla.
Good morning, Sun.
I'm going to raise them myself.
I know it'll be tough, but I'll get more jobs...
What about college?
If that ended up hurting your studies,
Yuri-san wouldn't be happy.
Hello?
Are you there?
I've apologized to the Takanashi family.
I'm sorry.
But if you're not absolutely sure about this,
bring the three of them back right now.
It will only make it worse for them if you aren't.
Is something the matter?
Huh? No, nothing really.
How about we head to my house?
Okay!
Yeah!
Momorail. Momorail.
Hey, are we going to the
airplane place next?
Hm?
Oh, this isn't the monorail that heads to Haneda,
so we won't be going to the airplane place.
Oh, I thought we picking up Daddy and Mommy.
Come on, Hina.
Look over there.
The sunset's pretty, isn't it?
It doesn't matter, let's keep walking there!
If you want to cry, look at the ocean.
If you walk in place,
you'll see your dreams.
Hey, will we see Torotoro-san?
Torotoro-san?
Torotoro-san from that video!
He lives in a place with
a lot of trees like this!
You sure have a lot of energy.
You aren't tired?
I'm totally fine!
Why do kids get so heavy
when they fall asleep?
I'll take her.
No, it's okay.
It's just a bit farther.
Okay, we're here.
We're here?
What do you think, Hina?
This is Uncles's apartment.
Wow!
It's bigger than our house!
There's a lot of rooms!
I'm going to clean up, so...
Th-That's a cute kitchen...
It's as big as our bathroom!
Really?
Anyway, make yourselves at home.
Okay, thanks!
The bath is cute too...
Where's the living room? And the other rooms?
There aren't any.
You keep it tidier than I thought.
I know, right?
I found some porno mags!
Oh, those are Nimura's!
What an idiot... I can't believe
he'd leave those here.
I was just kidding.
Stop that, already.
But since you got so worked up,
you must have some somewhere.
Miu!
'Kaay!
This is going to be hard
with that bed there...
Hey, hey, is this your house?
Yeah...
And it'll be your house from now on too.
My house?
This isn't my house.
You can see Sunshine City from my house.
Um...
You know, Hina.
Hey, Hina.
Listen closely.
We can't go back to that house anymore.
Huh? Why?
Just 'cause.
It'll be too difficult for you to understand, so I won't explain for now.
Anyway, this will be our
new home starting today.
Got it!
Anyway, let's take care of
this bed and make some room.
Sora-chan, Miu-chan, could you help me out?
What about Hina?!
Okay!
Hm...
I know.
How's this?!
Now there's enough room for the four of us!
Pretty nice.
It's like I'm sleeping over at a friend's place.
Um...
Can I use the restroom?
Oh, sure.
You don't have to ask
permission for everything.
I guess I'll put the table
out on the veranda.
Runa Runa Punch!
Onee-chan, this is bad! What should we do?
What are you going on about?
I could hear!
Hear what?
I could hear you going to the bathroom!
What?! Really?!
Yeah.
That means...
I kind of have to go now too.
No!
No! This isn't happening!
What's going on?
There might be something left!
Something left?
Like what?
Don't make me say it!
You flushed, right?
Of course I did!
And there weren't any problems, right?
Of course not!
Then what could be...
Uncle, you're lacking in
the delicacy department.
Huh?
Oh, I see.
How long should I wait, then?
I don't know...
An hour, maybe?
What?!
That's just how it is!
I was thinking of starting the bath
after going to the bathroom...
I'll do that instead!
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Okay, I have a question.
What now?
Where should we change?
Change?
Oh, uh...
You didn't think about it, did you?
Well, uh...
I know!
Do you have any thumbtacks, Uncle?
I guess this'll do.
All the water's spilling out.
We lost about half of it.
Sora Nee-tan, can I go mowmow?
What's that?
I always do it in the bath.
Stop that.
It tickles!
I haven't done this in forever!
Stop it...
Oh, she always does that with Yuri-san...
I think I'll get out now.
It's been a pretty crazy day, Nee-san.
Uncle!
Ta-da!
We'll be changing in here, so no peeking.
I wouldn't peek at kids changing, dummy.
Don't be silly, Miu.
This is so nice!
Come on, Hina. Dry yourself off.
It's hot!
I don't wanna!
Come on, Hina!
It's cold!
Hey, you're gonna catch a cold if you run around without drying off like that.
Sora-chan, hand me a bath towel.
H-Here.
Hey, don't look.
R-Right.
See, you're still drenched.
Geez, look over here.
Okay, now give me your left hand.
You could do it on the other side of the room.
Huh? What was that?
Never mind, it's fine.
It's kind of exciting.
Uncle!
Let's all play cards.
Sure. I won't lose, though.
I won't lose!
There!
What? Why?!
You're so easy to read, Miu.
You totally fell for that.
Alright, it's Hina's turn next.
I guess she's tired.
Sweepy.
Well, how about we get to sleep, then?
Hey, where's Daddy and Mommy?
When are they getting here?
Hina...
They'll be here soon, right?
I told you that Daddy and Yuri-san...
...went somewhere far away, right?
But they'll be back soon, right?
Mommy said that when she hugged me!
She said she'll be back soon!
I'm gonna go shopping.
Huh?
Onee-chan, watch Hina.
Miu!
Uncles too?
Huh?
Sora Nee-tan.
Sora Nee-tan?
Sora Nee-tan, it hurts...
I'm sorry.
Where did Miu Nee-tan go?
It's okay.
She'll be back soon.
You done shopping?
I forgot my wallet.
I see.
We're back.
Miu!
Dummy.
Dummy. Dummy.
I'm sorry.
I have two futons.
We'll put them next to mine,
so all three of you can sleep together.
I have the sheets and blankets my sister brought the last time she was here.
What about you?
I have some cushions,
so I'll be fine.
They smell like the ones at home.
Yeah.
Good night.
I'm glad...
The three of us will always be together.
Good night.
pikapika to hikaru boku dake no sweet love
Sparkling and bright, this is my sweet love
kanaeru kana kono ai wa
Will it work out? My love, for you
michitekuru koi wa nani iro darou na
This love filling me up, what color is it?
sukoshi dake miseyou kana
Maybe I'll show you just a little
tokimeki to mawaru chiisana shunkan
Sparking and spinning, a little moment
wakiokoru iro ga aru
There's a color just breaking through
yurayura to yureru chiisana sekai wo
Rolling and swaying, this little world
sotto sotto iyashitekuru yo
Softly, softly, sweetening it up
ochame sugi na kimi no coloring
It's way too much for me, your coloring
boku no naka wo meguri meguru yo
It just goes round and round inside me
kurukuru mawaru odoru kimi no coloring
Round and round, spinning, dancing, your coloring
o
kakenukete yuku hajiketa soda mitai
It flies right past me, like a can of soda popping open
o
suteki na color no kimi wa boku wo kanjiteru kana
Your colors are wonderful, can you feel me now?
o
staying in your love
kirakira na amai love
A sparkling, sweet love
kurukuru mawaru odoru kimi no coloring
Round and round, spinning, dancing, your coloring
maiagaru kana yawarakana ichigo milk
Will it go high enough? A soft, strawberry milk
suteki na color no kimi wa nani wo egaiteru kana
Your colors are wonderful, what are you painting now?
staying in your love
kirakira na amai love
A sparkling, sweet love
The eldest, Sora here!
I'm pretty nervous!
Sorry, I've n-never done a preview before!
What should I say...
Huh? There's only five seconds left?!
Uh, next time, um...
Oh no, time's up!
Wonderful life
See you again
Artist