I wonder if he'll be all right.
Uncle looked pretty nervous.
Yeah...
But we all cleaned the room together, so I'm sure he'll be fine.
You're doing a lot better than I expected.
I was afraid this environment would be a hindrance for the girls,
but it seems I was worried over nothing.
Does that mean...?
Yes, we'll see how things go for a while longer.
However, Yuuta-san,
do you realize how much more difficult things will become once school starts?
Yes, I understand.
I'll be fine!
Ants, ants!
Where are you going?
That's quite the line of ants.
Hi there!
Good afternoon, Hina-chan.
Good afternoon.
We've run into each other a lot lately.
I suppose we have.
Are you helping out with errands today too?
We are.
That's so nice of you all.
Nice?
We're all nice?
That's right.
You're very nice.
Let me give you a treat for being such a good girl.
Popsicle!
Thank you!
Hey, Hina...
It's okay.
It'd just melt if no one ate it soon.
Thank you for the popsicle.
Don't worry about it at all.
You're such a polite older sister.
That's right! And I love her so much for it!
Hey, Miu!
She's blushing!
Come on...
happy happy girl
itsu kara kana fushigi
When did it happen? It's so strange
kono mune no oku wa
The deepest parts of my heart
kimi no kakera bakari
Are filled with bits of you
doushiyou haato bousou
What should I do? My heart's gone crazy
doki doki deeto no souzou
Imagining a date that'll happen, maybe
kyunte tobihanechau kodou
Beating like it'll fly out of me
shizen ni hoppeta potte
Without thinking, my hands are on my cheeks
somaru no kakushitemo ki ga tsuite yo
But hiding them won't help, I already know
katamuiteku kokoro no kakudo
My heart's compass keeps turning to one place
omoi no shisen wa kimi muki
My feelings point right to you
mou koi wo shiteru
I'm already in love
happy happy girl
eeru wo okurasete
Let me cheer you on
kimi ga mezasu sora idaku
I want to see the same world as you
yume wo issho ni oikakeru yo
Let's chase our dreams together from now on
candy candy love
riido wa mada mada tayorinai kamo demo
I might not be very reliable right now
senaka ni yorisou
But if I can become
sasae ni ne naretara
Someone that you can lean on,
sotto sotto suki de itemo ii desu ka
Then can I keep on loving you like this?
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Thanks for Always Putting Up with Us
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Good job surviving the night, Segawa.
You're tougher than you look.
A
Hanamura Confections
The job's over for now, but you're welcome to join the American football club anytime.
A
Hanamura Confections
Later!
A
Hanamura Confections
Working two jobs in one night hurts.
Oh no.
Save me.
You there. You there.
Oh no.
Um...
Y-You want me to save you, right?
Oh no.
That's right.
You fell for it, Segawa Yuuta.
Sako-senpai?
Segawa-chan.
Are you okay?
Nimura, you're here?
Sup. It's been a while.
Yuuta likes shrine maidens in bondage.
I've learned of another one of your fetishes.
No!
So, what do you want?
You went through all this effort, after all.
Well...
You want to meet my nieces?!
Did you...?
It wasn't me.
Supposedly, Senpai talked to Miu-chan on the phone.
Huh?
I can't forget that beautiful voice of hers.
I might take you up on that.
I want to see her just once!
Oh, if that's all you wanted, you should have just told me sooner.
Oh, then you'll...
I refuse.
Why?!
I want to eat dinner and stuff under the same roof as your cute nieces!
Are they cute?
Are your nieces cute?
W-Well...
Uh...
Would you like to have dinner at my place?
Sure.
Okay! I'm having dinner with little girls tonight!
Welcome.
Hi there.
My name is Oda Raika.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Takanashi Miu. Ten years old.
Miss, you're quite pretty.
Hey... Hey...
Hina's three!
Hi there. Nice to meet you, Hina-chan.
Hey, Sora-chan, you should introduce yourself too.
I'm the eldest, Takanashi Sora.
Nice to meet you.
Hey, you're being rude to our guests.
Sorry, she's still a kid.
So cute...
Huh?
Buy a cake or something to make up for this later.
Why?
I'm truly honored to have been invited to your home today.
How pretty!
Thank you very much!
I've finally found my angel, Miu-tan!
You've found me!
And this, the makings of an angel-to-be!
Yay! It's a harem!
Harem! Harem!
Oh, you must be Sora-chan.
I heard you were fourteen?
Yes...
Just my luck. This one's an old hag.
Don't worry about it.
Sora-chan, you're cute.
Cute content: 100%.
All natural.
Okay...
Take that!
I won't hold back against a girl!
Especially not a fourteen-year-old hag!
What did you say?!
Sora Nee-tan, get him!
Watching closely?
Yeah, of course I am...
Miu-chan?!
All right, it's ready.
This looks great!
Yuuta, you eat some first.
Thanks.
It's fine!
I'll serve Onii-chan.
Hey, Sora-chan.
What?
Is there something wrong with me doing it?
That's not the issue here...
Uncles! Uncles!
Say, "Ah"!
All right, I guess I'll take you up on that.
Hina-chan, me next.
No fair!
Hina, me too!
And me!
You don't get any, Senpai!
Why only me?!
I had a wonderful time.
It was my first time seeing you like that.
I like cute girls.
Cute girls are justice.
Cute is ultimate.
Has work been hard?
Well, I guess it has.
But we have to get by somehow.
You've changed a little.
Huh? Really?
I can't really describe it, but I think it's a good change.
Thank you.
It doesn't have to be every day, but stop by the club room every once in a while.
We're lonely because you haven't shown up.
Lonely?
Who exactly?
The president.
Oh, Sako-san, huh?
I'm a bit lonely too.
Huh?
Good night.
Um...
Could you teach me how to cook sometime?
Call me anytime.
Yes!
Good night, Raika-san!
Runa Runa Kick!
Runa Runa Chop!
This isn't over!
I won't let it end like this!
Yay! I won!
You're a good voice actress.
That was some professional acting.
Y-You think so?
I do!
Bandler doesn't actually overreact like that, though.
Miu, Hina.
It's almost time for lunch.
Okay!
What will we have for lunch today?!
Soumen!
Soumen again!
What?
Soumen!
I'm finally done for the day.
You're working pretty hard, Segawa-kun.
No, not really.
You're really doing a great job here.
R-Really?
You worked a lot this month.
I'll give you a little extra.
Thank you so much, Manager!
But still,
I can't get too excited just yet.
Two commuter passes to Ikebukuro for school...
It's pretty expensive.
I can't cut our food budget any further.
And once college starts, I won't be able to work as much.
Raika-san?
When should I teach you how to cook?
She's coming over to teach me?
You've changed a little.
I can't really describe it, but I think it's a good change.
I shouldn't be complaining.
I still can work harder.
I need to worry about Sora-chan, Miu, and Hina right now.
Oh, right.
This'll be the first time they've taken the train to school.
All right!
Coming!
Lecture 1: Fried Rice.
Right!
First, you crack the eggs.
Let's see... Eggs...
Nee-tan, does your stomach hurt?
Hina, her stomach isn't what's hurting.
It's her heart.
Miu!
Oh, you could hear me?
Huh?
Yuuta, you're terrible at this.
Sorry.
I want to learn too.
What?
That's okay, right, Raika-san?
I don't mind.
In fact, I'd love that.
But I...
You cut it like this...
I see!
What game are Uncles and Nee-tan playing?
That's not a game.
That's called "a battlefield."
Well, I have to go to work right now.
Could you show her the rest for me?
Miu-chan, Hina, don't give Raika-san any trouble.
Okay!
I love Raika-chan!
Hey, don't call her that! She's older than you!
Yuuta, it's fine.
I don't mind if she calls me that.
Y-You sure?
Oh, right. I'm going to make a stop on the way home, so I'll be back a bit late.
Got it.
She's got a great body,
the face of a model,
and her cooking is top notch.
How can she be so perfect?
Is something the matter?
Oh no. It's nothing.
Onii-chan...
What's Onii-chan like at school?
Um, I mean...
What do you think of him, anyway?
I think he's interesting.
Huh?
I-Interesting?!
Do you mean as a man?
As a subject for observation, I guess.
Observation?
Sora-chan. Sora-chan.
You put in too much.
I, uh...
Raika-san!
No problem.
I'm really sorry.
Don't worry about it.
I'm happy I could take a bath with you.
You didn't want to take one together?
Oh no. It's not that.
Um...
How did you get them so big?
Big...?
Did you drink milk, or did you do special exercises or something?
I didn't really do anything.
If there were something I did...
I just loved what was cute.
I see...
Stare...
What are you doing?
That's the first time I've heard someone actually say "stare."
You finally smiled.
I'm happy.
R-Raika-san, I...
Raika-chan!
Let's wash together!
Raika-san's absolutely amazing naked too!
There's not enough room!
Wow!
Hey, Miu! Hina!
Oh.
Excuse me.
Could you wrap these as gifts?
Oh yeah, it's a surprise. A surprise.
I'm back!
Uncles, welcome back!
Welcome back!
Oh, did Raika-san go home already?
Oh, Sora-chan, Miu-chan, do you have a second?
What is it?
The two of you will be going to school by train now, right?
That being the case, I figured you needed some passes.
So I...
It's fine.
We were thinking of taking some time off from school.
We still haven't decided on Hina's preschool.
So while you're at college,
we'll have to take care of her.
What are you guys talking about?
It's fine. I'll look after Hina.
I might have to take fewer classes for the time being,
but I can make them up later.
But you won't be able to work...
H-How about we do this, then?
I can ask Nimura or Raika-san to watch her while I'm not here.
Yeah, I'm sure they'll be able to help.
I think we need to take care of ourselves...
We can't keep causing others trouble.
But...
Coming!
Oh, Miss Landlady...
Can I speak with you?
What? I'm being evicted?!
Of course.
Four people living in this one-room apartment?
That's just not acceptable.
I figured your relatives might just be visiting for a while, so I thought I'd just let it pass,
but this clearly violates the contract you signed.
Segawa-san, you have one month.
You must vacate this apartment within one month.
Understood?
pikapika to hikaru boku dake no sweet love
Sparkling and bright, this is my sweet love
kanaeru kana kono ai wa
Will it work out? My love, for you
michitekuru koi wa nani iro darou na
This love filling me up, what color is it?
sukoshi dake miseyou kana
Maybe I'll show you just a little
tokimeki to mawaru chiisana shunkan
Sparking and spinning, a little moment
wakiokoru iro ga aru
There's a color just breaking through
yurayura to yureru chiisana sekai wo
Rolling and swaying, this little world
sotto sotto iyashitekuru yo
Softly, softly, sweetening it up
ochame sugi na kimi no coloring
It's way too much for me, your coloring
boku no naka wo meguri meguru yo
It just goes round and round inside me
kurukuru mawaru odoru kimi no coloring
o
Round and round, spinning, dancing, your coloring
kakenukete yuku hajiketa soda mitai
o
It flies right past me, like a can of soda popping open
suteki na color no kimi wa boku wo kanjiteru kana
Your colors are wonderful, can you feel me now?
o
staying in your love
kirakira na amai love
A sparkling, sweet love
kurukuru mawaru odoru kimi no coloring
Round and round, spinning, dancing, your coloring
maiagaru kana yawarakana ichigo milk
Will it go high enough? A soft, strawberry milk
suteki na color no kimi wa nani wo egaiteru kana
Your colors are wonderful, what are you painting now?
staying in your love
kirakira na amai love
A sparkling, sweet love
There's someone I love.
They're close to me,
and yet they're so far.
That's why I don't want any more distance between us.
Next time, "I Won't Let That Happen!"
I Won't Let That Happen!
What can I do to make sure we're always happy?
See you again
Artist
Ejiri Tatsuma