It's like a dream come true!
We're taking a trip to Hot Springs Waterland Park!
Two days, one night, and dinner!
I never imagined we would get a chance like this either.
It's all thanks to Hina.
Jackpot!
Grand prize! A two-day, one-night,
family trip to Hot Springs Waterland!
Jackpot!
Uncles, who's Jack?
Are we there yet?
Hina, don't kick around like that.
It's okay. She's just really excited.
She can't wait to get into that big bath.
Yeah! I can't wait!
We didn't get to go swimming this summer, after all.
Hey, did you know? Onee-chan
even went on a diet just for today.
Don't lie!
Is that true? I did get the feeling you weren't eating as much.
I just... I just haven't been feeling very hungry.
It's the sea!
We'll probably see that soon.
happy happy girl
itsu kara kana fushigi
When did it happen? It's so strange
kono mune no oku wa
The deepest parts of my heart
kimi no kakera bakari
Are filled with bits of you
doushiyou haato bousou
What should I do? My heart's gone crazy
doki doki deeto no souzou
Imagining a date that'll happen, maybe
kyunte tobihanechau kodou
Beating like it'll fly out of me
shizen ni hoppeta potte
Without thinking, my hands are on my cheeks
somaru no kakushitemo ki ga tsuite yo
But hiding them won't help, I already know
katamuiteku kokoro no kakudo
My heart's compass keeps turning to one place
omoi no shisen wa kimi muki
My feelings point right to you
mou koi wo shiteru
I'm already in love
happy happy girl
eeru wo okurasete
Let me cheer you on
kimi ga mezasu sora idaku
I want to see the same world as you
yume wo issho ni oikakeru yo
Let's chase our dreams together from now on
candy candy love
riido wa mada mada tayorinai kamo demo
I might not be very reliable right now
senaka ni yorisou
But if I can become
sasae ni ne naretara
Someone that you can lean on,
sotto sotto suki de itemo ii desu ka
Then can I keep on loving you like this?
Warm Fuzzies
It's a big bath!
Okay!
Runacular...
Hey, now. No running.
Okay!
Let's go, Uncles!
Yeah!
Sorry for taking so long.
Wait, where's Sora-chan?
Miu-chan, what's wrong?
Uncle, you're lacking in the delicacy department!
Don't you think there's something you
should say before worrying about that?
Huh?
Onee-chan, I feel sorry for you.
Sorry for you!
Maybe it's too unnatural?
Men are just so predictable!
Yeah! They just keep looking at her boobs!
You're doing great!
Now let's try going splish-splash with your feet!
Splish-splash!
You asked for it, Hina!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Sora Nee-tan, the pool is like a bath!
It's warm!
Y-Yeah.
Huh? Aren't you going to swim, Sora-chan?
Um...
She's wearing that so you'd be the
first to see her wearing what's under!
Miu!
Guess who.
I-It couldn't be...
Raika-chan!
Correct.
Yahoo, Yuuta.
Um...
Wh-Why?
Hi!
Yo, Segawa-chan.
We came.
Segawa-kun! I thought you smelled fishy!
Yeah, sorry about that. I accidentally told them about your vacation.
I thought so.
We at the RORI are of one body and mind!
We may have been born apart,
but we vowed to die—and go on
vacations with angels—together!
I don't recall making any such vow.
And even if I did by some strange accident,
I would ask to have it annulled.
You disappoint me, Segawa Yuuta!
You...
You hoped to keep the sight of angels in swimsuits to yourself
and to take advantage of this trip to say,
"How about going to the mixed bath together as a family?"
A-And then...
You'd take the bathwater mixed with the wine of young girls...
and dr-dr-dr-drink deeply!
I don't like dirty jokes.
I wasn't thinking of doing anything like that.
What? I think going to the mixed bath is a good idea.
M-Miu-sama!
A mixed bath is a true El Dorado.
Though one may dream of it, none shall ever find the City of Gold.
And the one who seeks it now is Segawa Yuuta!
So, Onee-chan.
How about it? This is a
chance to get closer to Uncle!
No, no, definitely not!
I definitely don't want that!
Oh?
I hate to admit it, but it seems the old hag and I are in agreement.
Who are you calling an old hag?!
Like I said, I wasn't thinking of...
Uncles, what's a mixed bath?
Look, you made such a mess.
Hang on tight!
Okay!
Uncles, you can have the rest!
Oh, thanks!
Uncles, bathroom!
Okay, okay.
Maybe Raika-san really does...
No way.
That can't be true.
I mean, it's Onii-chan.
Uncles, I want to do that!
Sure, but it's really tall.
It's okay!
Yuuta.
Is something the matter?
I want to go too.
Can I go with you?
Raika-chan wants to do it too?
Yes.
Uncles, Raika-chan wants to go too!
Y-Yeah. Then I guess...
Me too!
Can I, Onii-chan?
Y-Yeah. We can all go together.
Good luck, Onee-chan.
Uncles, again!
Oh? Looks like you're hooked.
Ah, if only I could hold you like that.
Then Raika-san really does like Onii-chan?
Raika-san! Your top! Your top!
Uncles, what's wrong?
So he does like them big.
Uncles, what's this?
I wonder...
It feels like a cushion.
Uncle, there's a limit to just how lacking you can be in the delicacy department!
Sorry?
This is a girls' secret!
Huh?
Onii-chan, you stupid, perverted dummy!
That's what you call love.
Love?
Is that it?
Before I know it, I'm always watching them.
By the way, Oda-kun, there's a
place called Lovers' Cape nearby.
Lovers' Cape?
They say that those who ring the bell there together will be together forever.
I see.
I'll ask them to come tonight.
Sora-chan?
Did something happen?
You look kind of down.
Nothing happened!
Oh, Nimura-kun, perfect timing.
L-Like it matters to me who Onii-chan dates!
Onii-chan, you dummy.
What?!
Raika-san, you're in the same room as Sako-senpai and Nimura?
Yes.
I don't think that's such a good idea.
Really?
Why not stay in this room instead?
Okay, I will.
We'd love to have you here, Raika-san!
Don't you want Raika-san to stay here, Hina?
Yeah!
I'm sleeping with Raika-chan!
Then you can use my futon.
All right.
Yuuta.
Come on.
Raika...
Anything but that!
What the heck are you thinking?!
Onii-chan, you stupid pervert!
What do you mean?
You just invited Raika-san into your futon!
But... I'm going to the other room.
Then...
why don't we go to the bath?
What the heck am I doing?
Raika-chan, when you take a bath,
you have to go down to your neck and count to 100!
Very good, Hina-chan.
But I don't want to count to 100. Let's count to 100,000.
That looks like fun, Hina!
Miu-chan, you come here too.
Yay! I will!
Raika-san, you have a "cool beauty" kind of look going, but you're really fun to talk to.
You think so?
Yes!
I'm sure men are all over you because of that gap!
She's right.
Raika-san's beautiful, mysterious, and has big boobs.
Anyone would accept if she asked them out.
Just beyond this wall, Miu-sama is...
Both sides of this wall are connected deep under ground!
That means this is, in a way, a mixed bath!
Segawa-chan,
you're getting along great with Oda-senpai.
Y-You really think so?
But I'm having some misgivings about it.
Don't tell me you—
No, no.
While I wish for my best friend's utmost happiness,
I don't want anyone to get hurt because of it.
I only want the best for the community, you know.
But I do want to see you bag Oda-senpai.
I don't get it.
Miu-chan, your skin is so soft.
It's so smooth and white as snow.
That tickles!
What about me?
Hina-chan is special.
The best.
Raika-chan, tighter!
Raika-chan, can I go mowmow?
Mowmow?
Mowmow!
Hina-chan.
Sora-chan, want to join us?
I-I'm fine.
No need...
to be shy.
I'm not a kid anymore.
Oh?
You're not a kid?
What is it now?
Maybe it's just me,
but your boobs look smaller compared to when you wore your swimsuit.
Miu...
Relax. You don't need to get worked up about it.
Uncle didn't find out about the pads anyway.
Don't mention the pads!
Sora-chan, are you okay?
Sorry.
This is a moment of extreme happiness.
Raika-chan, higher, higher!
Higher, higher.
Oh, so cute.
Won't the three of you be my daughters?
Let's see.
Maybe if Uncle comes with us.
Yuuta too?
But then...
What?
What would Onee-chan do?
I don't care.
That room is...
Yuuta.
Mornin'.
What are you doing, Raika-san?!
Where are Nimura and Sako-senpai?
Don't worry. I got rid of them.
You "got rid of them"?
Show.
Sob, sob, sob.
For goodness's sake, forgive me, Lord Magistrate.
Um... what is it?
Hold this.
Okay.
Oh my!
Yuuta, do you like what you see?
R-Raika-san, this isn't right!
Why?
"Why?" Raika-san, are you okay looking like that in front of me?
I don't mind.
I knew it!
More importantly, Yuuta, does seeing this make you happy?
Well?
It makes me happy.
Very.
What are they doing?!
I see.
I did something to make you happy.
Now it's your turn to make me happy.
Right.
You're helping me with my first love.
Y-Your first love?
There's a place called Lovers' Cape near here.
Yeah?
Those who ring the bell together will be together forever.
Yes.
Stop right there!
Nimura?
And Sora-chan?
Onii-chan... um...
What is the meaning of this, Nimura-kun?
Sako-senpai?!
I planned to entrap Segawa-kun and take the angels!
Oda-kun and Hina-chan, and Miu-sama and I,
were to ring the bell at Lovers' Cape!
Yeah, but Sora-chan overheard that.
Then Lovers' Cape...
I want to ring the bell at Lovers' Cape with Hina-chan.
Y-You're kidding me.
That's all it was? What a relief.
Do you think this will count?
Well, wishing to be together forever isn't just something for lovers.
We're wishing that we can all be together forever.
Yeah!
All right. Next...
We'll be together forever!
Uncles and Sora Nee-tan and Miu Nee-tan and Raika-chan and...
Thank you, Hina-chan.
Raika-chan?
Those who ring the bell together
will be together forever.
I wish that we can all be together forever.
Lots of crazy stuff happened,
but it makes for a good memory.
Yeah.
It was full of surprises, but it
made for a fun family vacation.
I wish that we can all be together forever.
And...
pikapika to hikaru boku dake no sweet love
Sparkling and bright, this is my sweet love
kanaeru kana kono ai wa
Will it work out? My love, for you
michitekuru koi wa nani iro darou na
This love filling me up, what color is it?
sukoshi dake miseyou kana
Maybe I'll show you just a little
tokimeki to mawaru chiisana shunkan
Sparking and spinning, a little moment
wakiokoru iro ga aru
There's a color just breaking through
yurayura to yureru chiisana sekai wo
Rolling and swaying, this little world
sotto sotto iyashitekuru yo
Softly, softly, sweetening it up
ochame sugi na kimi no coloring
It's way too much for me, your coloring
boku no naka wo meguri meguru yo
It just goes round and round inside me
kurukuru mawaru odoru kimi no coloring
o
Round and round, spinning, dancing, your coloring
kakenukete yuku hajiketa soda mitai
o
It flies right past me, like a can of soda popping open
suteki na color no kimi wa boku wo kanjiteru kana
Your colors are wonderful, can you feel me now?
o
staying in your love
kirakira na amai love
A sparkling, sweet love
kurukuru mawaru odoru kimi no coloring
Round and round, spinning, dancing, your coloring
maiagaru kana yawarakana ichigo milk
Will it go high enough? A soft, strawberry milk
suteki na color no kimi wa nani wo egaiteru kana
Your colors are wonderful, what are you painting now?
staying in your love
kirakira na amai love
A sparkling, sweet love