happy happy girl
itsu kara kana fushigi
When did it happen? It's so strange
kono mune no oku wa
The deepest parts of my heart
kimi no kakera bakari
Are filled with bits of you
doushiyou haato bousou
What should I do? My heart's gone crazy
doki doki deeto no souzou
Imagining a date that'll happen, maybe
kyunte tobihanechau kodou
Beating like it'll fly out of me
shizen ni hoppeta potte
Without thinking, my hands are on my cheeks
somaru no kakushitemo ki ga tsuite yo
But hiding them won't help, I already know
katamuiteku kokoro no kakudo
My heart's compass keeps turning to one place
omoi no shisen wa kimi muki
My feelings point right to you
mou koi wo shiteru
I'm already in love
happy happy girl
eeru wo okurasete
Let me cheer you on
kimi ga mezasu sora idaku
I want to see the same world as you
yume wo issho ni oikakeru yo
Let's chase our dreams together from now on
candy candy love
riido wa mada mada tayorinai kamo demo
I might not be very reliable right now
senaka ni yorisou
But if I can become
sasae ni ne naretara
Someone that you can lean on,
sotto sotto suki de itemo ii desu ka
Then can I keep on loving you like this?
Come to My House
I'm really sorry about that.
I honestly didn't mean to.
Your mom said I'd be coming, right?
That's enough. She knows already.
Right, Onee-chan?
Do you remember me, Sora-chan?
Uh, then I guess I should introduce myself.
I'm your mother's younger brother, Segawa Yuuta.
Hina, you should introduce yourself too.
Takanashi Hina! Three years old!
So you're three years old now?
You've gotten pretty big.
I'm Takanashi Miu. Ten years old.
I'm in the fifth grade.
You're all grown up now.
Come on, Onee-chan. Introduce yourself too.
Sorry about her.
She's kind of shy.
And she's sometimes not very good with people.
Don't say stuff like that.
You've really grown up too, Sora-chan.
I was surprised.
Don't try to flatter me.
Don't keep acting like that.
You're in the eighth grade, right?
I'm really sorry about what happened.
It's fine.
Don't worry about her.
She'll get over it if you leave her alone for a while.
So, what should I do here?
You don't really have to do anything.
Just sit back and relax.
Uncles!
Let's relax!
You're pretty good!
But I'm not going to let you win!
Take this! And this!
Mine...
Wanna play again?
Mine died!
Yo-You're crying about that?!
Of course she would.
Onee-chan!
There, there.
Don't cry. Don't cry.
Uncle's a meanie, isn't he?
What the heck?
Damn it! I won't lose to you!
You're actually trying now, huh?
I'm not gonna hold back!
I wouldn't have it any other way!
Using that attack? Well then...!
There!
I won!
I lost.
You're so cool, Sora Nee-tan!
Pretty lame for an adult.
Lame! Lame!
Lunch is ready.
Yay! Food!
Let's eat!
I want the pink ones!
Okay.
Sorry you had to make the food.
No, it's okay.
I just boiled the noodles.
Yuri-san had already cooked the rest,
so I just microwaved it.
It's good.
This brings back memories.
Wh-What?
What's college like?
I guess it's pretty fun.
I've met some interesting people there.
Do you have a girlfriend?
That was awfully direct.
Well, you are kinda cool.
Don't tease me.
I don't have a girlfriend.
So the girl you like isn't into you?
H-How did you know that?
It's written all over your face.
Huh?
Come on! Don't tease me!
So there is someone you like, then.
Huh?
Is she pretty? Or is she cute?
I'm not really sure.
Just tell me!
It'll help me out in the future!
Knock it off, Miu!
Huh? Don't you want to know too?
I-I don't really care.
What a liar!
You even took another shower 'cause you knew he was coming by.
That's why he walked in on you, right?
Miu!
I'm done!
Hey! Wait!
Hey!
That's not why.
Huh?
I was cleaning, so I was sweaty, and I got all dirty.
That's why!
That's why?
That's why I...
took another shower.
That's all there is to it!
R-Right. Got it.
She fell asleep?
She ran around a lot today.
Come on, Hina.
Let's nap somewhere else.
Having siblings sure is nice.
I'm tired.
Yuuta, you can't fall asleep here.
You're so silly.
Twinkle, twinkle, little star,
how I wonder what you are.
Hey.
Hey, you can't fall asleep here.
You're so silly.
Sorry,
Nee-san.
Sora-chan?
Miu-chan?
Hina?
We all went shopping.
Miu
Oh.
We're back.
Oh, hello.
Wh-Who are you?!
Huh?
What did you do with my daughters?!
Where are they?!
Oh, no... um...
They all went shopping.
Lies!
What did you do to my daughters?!
Spill it!
O-Ow...
Stop it!
It's me!
Stop that!
I don't know you!
Tell me the truth!
Knock it off, you idiot.
Look closer. It's Yuuta. Yuuta!
I had him watch the house
while we were gone.
Huh?
Oh!
Hello.
Looks like Miu drew all over your face.
That girl...
I'm sorry!
It's okay.
Why did you do that?
He was sound asleep,
so I couldn't help myself.
Hey!
Don't get mad.
It's fine.
It's my fault for falling asleep like that.
Sorry, Yuuta.
But I'm glad. It seems like you all get along.
Why?
Because now I won't have to worry when I go with Shingo-san on his business trip.
Huh?
What kind of trip?
He's going on a trip to purchase some rare metals. It'll just be for a week.
Please take care of my daughters while we're gone.
Wh-What?!
You're not doing anything anyway, right?
I'll make sure you get a good
chunk of change for it.
That's a bit much.
Hey...
Miu-chan?
You can do it, right?
Please say you can.
I want to let her go with him.
Daddy and Yuri-san still haven't
gone on their honeymoon, so...
Sora...
She's been taking care
of us this whole time,
so they never had a chance to go.
So please...
Please?
Please.
Thanks. Take care of the kids for me.
Who is it? Who is it?
Oh, but you can't bring that big-boobed girlfriend of yours over.
I told you she's not my girlfriend.
Hurry and ask her out, then.
Knowing you, you're probably
just letting things play out
without telling her anything.
Well, keep at it, and good luck.
You're good at not knowing when to give up.
What's that supposed to mean?
Talk to you later.
Is it okay for Mommy and Daddy to leave for a while?
Yeah! It's fine!
I'll have fun with Uncles!
You're a good girl.
I'll be back soon.
Subject
Yuuta !!!
Thank you,
Takanashi Yuri
It's the first day of their trip, and it's raining.
They're already high above the clouds,
where the sun's shining.
They're on a plane, you know?
Right.
Now then, Uncle.
Huh?
Now it's time...
for us to teach you the rules of the house!
Teach you!
Huh?
We'll start here!
The bathroom?
You're only allowed to use this bathroom!
The one on the second floor is for girls only.
Actually, just don't go up there at all.
Don't go!
On we go!
Your laundry goes in this basket.
You're not allowed to wash your clothes with ours.
Not wash!
Next!
This soap is from the hotel we stayed at on our family trip!
Our bathroom stuff is off limits!
Off limits!
This is where you'll be sleeping,
but adult magazines are against the rules!
What do you take me for?
That's it!
Follow the rules and we'll have a fun week together!
Okay!
Right.
Also, we're calling you Daddy from now on!
What are you saying?
He doesn't really feel like an uncle.
Uncles is daddy?
What do you think, Daddy?
I think Shingo-san's the only one you should call that.
He's actually your father, after all.
Isn't he cute when he's embarrassed, Onee-chan?
Wh-Why are you asking me?
No reason.
So what are we gonna do now?
Games!
I want you to help me with my homework!
It's obvious that we should clean up the house.
Games!
Homework!
Cleaning!
We're cleaning, right?
Thanks for helping me with my homework.
We're playing games!
Homework!
We'll do it all!
Hey, girls. Come check this out!
What is it?
We should be able to see
a meteor shower tonight.
Take a look.
Oh, there's one!
Where? Where?
It's gone already.
I saw one!
Where? Where?
It's gone already.
I want to see one too!
All right, Hina.
Let's look for one together.
Where would one be?
It'll look like a star flying across the sky.
Where? Where?
Wow.
Twinkle, twinkle, little star,
how I wonder what you are.
Up above the world so high,
like a diamond in the sky.
Twinkle, twinkle, little star,
how I wonder what you are.
Thanks.
Huh?
You covered me up the other day, right?
I didn't realize until later, and I wanted to say thanks.
It's not a big deal.
Good night.
Night.
Are you awake, Onee-chan?
Yeah.
I wonder what Dad and Yuri-san are doing.
I think it's afternoon over there.
They said they were going
sightseeing on the first day.
I'm sure they're having fun right now.
I bet they're being all lovey-dovey.
Probably.
I'm glad they were able to
go on that trip together.
Yeah.
Good night.
A
Crash...
Airplane crash!!
A
Crash...
Airplane crash!!
A
Crash...
Airplane crash!!
Seriously?!
A
Crash...
Airplane crash!!
Seriously?!
A
Crash...
Airplane crash!!
Seriously?!
A
Crash...
Airplane crash!!
Seriously?!
A
Crash...
Airplane crash!!
Seriously?!
A
Crash...
Airplane crash!!
A
Crash...
Airplane crash!!
A
Crash...
Airplane crash!!
A
Crash...
Airplane crash!!
Seriously?!
A
Crash...
Airplane crash!!
Seriously?!
A
Crash...
Airplane crash!!
Seriously?!
A
Crash...
Airplane crash!!
Seriously?!
A
Crash...
Airplane crash!!
Seriously?!
A
Crash...
Airplane crash!!
Seriously?!
A
Crash...
Airplane crash!!
Seriously?!
A
Crash...
Airplane crash!!
Seriously?!
A
Crash...
Airplane crash!!
Seriously?!
A
Crash...
Airplane crash!!
Seriously?!
A
Crash...
Airplane crash!!
Seriously?!
A
Crash...
Airplane crash!!
Seriously?!
A
Crash...
Airplane crash!!
Seriously?!
A
Crash...
Airplane crash!!
Seriously?!
A
Crash...
Airplane crash!!
Seriously?!
A
Crash...
Airplane crash!!
Seriously?!
A
Crash...
Airplane crash!!
Seriously?!
A
Crash...
Airplane crash!!
Seriously?!
A
Crash...
Airplane crash!!
Seriously?!
A
Crash...
Airplane crash!!
Seriously?!
A
Crash...
Airplane crash!!
Seriously?!
A
Crash...
Airplane crash!!
Seriously?!
A
Crash...
Airplane crash!!
Seriously?!
A
Where's the passenger list?
Crash...
A
Airplane crash!!
Seriously?!
A
Where's the passenger list?
Crash...
A
Airplane crash!!
Seriously?!
A
Where's the passenger list?
Crash...
A
Airplane crash!!
Seriously?!
A
Where's the passenger list?
Crash...
A
Airplane crash!!
Seriously?!
A
Where's the passenger list?
Crash...
A
Airplane crash!!
Seriously?!
A
Where's the passenger list?
Crash...
A
Airplane crash!!
Seriously?!
A
Where's the passenger list?
Crash...
A
Airplane crash!!
Seriously?!
A
Where's the passenger list?
200 people missing in all,
including a Japanese couple.
A
Crash...
Airplane crash!!
Seriously?!
A
Where's the passenger list?
200 people missing in all,
including a Japanese couple.
A
Crash...
Airplane crash!!
Seriously?!
A
Where's the passenger list?
200 people missing in all,
including a Japanese couple.
A
Crash...
Airplane crash!!
Seriously?!
A
Where's the passenger list?
200 people missing in all,
including a Japanese couple.
A
Crash...
Airplane crash!!
Seriously?!
A
Where's the passenger list?
200 people missing in all,
including a Japanese couple.
A
Crash...
Airplane crash!!
Seriously?!
A
Where's the passenger list?
200 people missing in all,
including a Japanese couple.
A
Crash...
Airplane crash!!
Seriously?!
A
Where's the passenger list?
200 people missing in all,
including a Japanese couple.
A
Crash...
Airplane crash!!
Seriously?!
A
Where's the passenger list?
200 people missing in all,
including a Japanese couple.
A
Crash...
Airplane crash!!
Seriously?!
A
Where's the passenger list?
200 people missing in all,
including a Japanese couple.
A
Crash...
Airplane crash!!
Seriously?!
A
Where's the passenger list?
200 people missing in all,
including a Japanese couple.
A
Crash...
Airplane crash!!
Seriously?!
A
Where's the passenger list?
200 people missing in all,
including a Japanese couple.
A
Crash...
Airplane crash!!
Seriously?!
A
Where's the passenger list?
200 people missing in all,
including a Japanese couple.
A
Crash...
Airplane crash!!
Seriously?!
A
Where's the passenger list?
200 people missing in all,
including a Japanese couple.
A
200 people missing in all, including a Japanese couple.
Huge Accident in Japan
Shingo,Yuri
Takanashi
Segawa
Yuuta
Take care of the kids for me.
Keep at it, and good luck.
You're good at not knowing when to give up.
Were you able to get a hold of Miu's mother?
There's no point.
We're not sending Miu to some country where they can't speak Japanese.
If only Sora-chan's mother were still with us.
She was a good mother.
This isn't how it was supposed to be.
Onii-chan's luck hasn't been great.
Let's make our decision.
We've figured out where you girls will be going,
so I want you to listen carefully.
Hina will be staying with Aunt Mayumi.
Miu will stay with me.
It's a little far, but the
air is cleaner there.
It's a good place.
Sora will go to a boarding school that handles both middle and high school.
U-Um...
We don't want to be separated.
We want to stay together!
Yuuta-san...
We know how you feel, but that just isn't possible.
It's not like you're being sent across the planet.
You'll be able to see each
other whenever you want.
But...
We're thinking about what would make you happiest.
I really don't want to
be separated from him.
I'll... I'll raise Yuuta.
I'll get a part-time job or whatever it takes,
and I'll get him through college.
After all... Yuuta and I...
are the only family we have.
We have to stay together!
We won't cause you any trouble!
We'll listen to whatever you say.
Just let the three of us stay together.
Don't be selfish.
There's no way for the three
of you to be together.
How about coming to my place?
I'm poor, there isn't much room,
and I don't really have anything,
but the three of you can stay together.
Onii...
What are you talking about?
Don't get caught up in the moment.
I mean, you might be related to Hina,
but you have absolutely no
relation to Sora or Miu.
Who cares?
That doesn't matter at all.
Family has to...
stay together!
pikapika to hikaru boku dake no sweet love
Sparkling and bright, this is my sweet love
kanaeru kana kono ai wa
Will it work out? My love, for you
michitekuru koi wa nani iro darou na
This love filling me up, what color is it?
sukoshi dake miseyou kana
Maybe I'll show you just a little
tokimeki to mawaru chiisana shunkan
Sparking and spinning, a little moment
wakiokoru iro ga aru
There's a color just breaking through
yurayura to yureru chiisana sekai wo
Rolling and swaying, this little world
sotto sotto iyashitekuru yo
Softly, softly, sweetening it up
ochame sugi na kimi no coloring
It's way too much for me, your coloring
boku no naka wo meguri meguru yo
It just goes round and round inside me
kurukuru mawaru odoru kimi no coloring
o
Round and round, spinning, dancing, your coloring
kakenukete yuku hajiketa soda mitai
o
It flies right past me, like a can of soda popping open
suteki na color no kimi wa boku wo kanjiteru kana
Your colors are wonderful, can you feel me now?
o
staying in your love
kirakira na amai love
A sparkling, sweet love
kurukuru mawaru odoru kimi no coloring
Round and round, spinning, dancing, your coloring
maiagaru kana yawarakana ichigo milk
Will it go high enough? A soft, strawberry milk
suteki na color no kimi wa nani wo egaiteru kana
Your colors are wonderful, what are you painting now?
staying in your love
kirakira na amai love
A sparkling, sweet love
It's Hina!
We went to Uncles's place!
And then Sora Nee-tan went to
go pee, and stuff was bad.
"I Won't Cry!"
I Won't Cry
See you later!
See you again
Yabuki Kentarou
Artist: