I'm beat...
I'm home.
Oh, Uncles! Welcome back!
This is, uh... bad luck!
A complete accident!
I-I didn't mean to-
Ow!
Uncle, you're not living alone anymore, so try to have more delicacy, already.
happy happy girl
itsu kara kana fushigi
When did it happen? It's so strange
kono mune no oku wa
The deepest parts of my heart
kimi no kakera bakari
Are filled with bits of you
doushiyou haato bousou
What should I do? My heart's gone crazy
doki doki deeto no souzou
Imagining a date that'll happen, maybe
kyunte tobihanechau kodou
Beating like it'll fly out of me
shizen ni hoppeta potte
Without thinking, my hands are on my cheeks
somaru no kakushitemo ki ga tsuite yo
But hiding them won't help, I already know
katamuiteku kokoro no kakudo
My heart's compass keeps turning to one place
omoi no shisen wa kimi muki
My feelings point right to you
mou koi wo shiteru
I'm already in love
happy happy girl
eeru wo okurasete
Let me cheer you on
kimi ga mezasu sora idaku
I want to see the same world as you
yume wo issho ni oikakeru yo
Let's chase our dreams together from now on
candy candy love
riido wa mada mada tayorinai kamo demo
I might not be very reliable right now
senaka ni yorisou
But if I can become
sasae ni ne naretara
Someone that you can lean on,
sotto sotto suki de itemo ii desu ka
Then can I keep on loving you like this?
Oh man, I have to get
to work early today!
What Happened to the Girl
Later, then.
See you later!
Later...
See you later.
Watch out for cars!
Don't mess up the room.
Roger that.
Okay! Loger!
Come on, Onee-chan.
Are you still upset about what happened last night?
Not really.
Being in such a small room is pretty inconvenient.
It takes a while to hang the sheets up with thumbtacks every time we take a bath...
All right, it's finished!
Huh?
A
Curtains
It'd be great if we had something like this.
It would.
The room wouldn't feel as small, either.
But that'd cost money.
That's the problem.
It's not me.
Or me.
Found the beeping!
That makes five times now...
Shut up!
Oh, you finally picked up.
Segawa-kun, I found you a good part-time job.
With daily pay.
Who are you?!
Hey, you listening?!
Hello?
Hey!
Hey! Are you there?
Segawa-kun? Are you there?
Hello?
Huh? Hello?
Wh-Who... are you?
Um, I'm...
I'm his niece.
I'm staying with my uncle over summer break.
Oh, I see.
My name is Sako. I'm the
president of Segawa-kun's club.
Thank you for always helping him out.
How polite.
Make sure you have lots of fun while you're here.
Segawa-kun's really busy with work, so I can take you around Tokyo instead, if you want.
Sure, I might take you up on that.
Is something the matter?
N-No, I'm sorry.
I couldn't really hear you, so could you say that again?
Oh, sure!
I might take you up on that.
I can't breathe...
Sorry.
That Sako-san...
He's a nice person.
He found a job for Uncle.
I might take you up on that.
A voice like an angel's!
That angelic fragrance wafting from Segawa-kun must have been hers!
Judging from the sound of her voice, she must be around 10.
No, that's how old I hope she is!
She has blonde hair, twin tails,
and mischievous eyes!
Oh my, so cute!
Teehee
My angel...
Oda-kun!
Time out!
No... Stop it...
I'm...
I'm coming!
Yuuta's niece...
Delete this recording?
I might take you up on that.
Deleting
Deleted
Let's call Uncle's restaurant.
We shouldn't bother him while he's working.
Then what should we do?
He really is hopeless.
He forgets everything, doesn't he?
I'll be back soon.
See you.
Bye!
Hey, Miu Nee-tan. Look at this.
Hm? Let's see here...
That was fast!
Welcome back, Sora Nee-tan!
Um...
What is it?
I should probably change, don't you think?
Is this the wrong place?
Welcome.
A table for one?
Um...
I thought this was the place...
I see.
But I made a mistake!
Huh?
Wait-
AAA
Segawa
So that wasn't the place...
Sora-chan?
I thought it was you, Sora-chan.
Did you come to give that to me?
Yeah.
Be careful not to lose it, okay?
Sorry.
I'll make sure to have it on me from now on.
Please do.
It'd be a problem if you couldn't call me when you needed to.
T-That's right.
A big problem!
Anyway, keep working hard.
Sora-chan.
Huh?
Thanks for coming all the way out here.
I did it.
Mission complete! Good work.
Did Uncle say anything about your outfit?
Oh...
He didn't, actually.
He really doesn't have any delicacy, does he?
I don't really care that much.
You went out of your way to dress up too.
It's not that big of a deal...
Oh? I thought that was your favorite outfit?
Onee-chan?
I'm almost out of batteries, so I'm gonna go.
Talk to you later.
A
Curtains
The bad guy grabbed them both.
They struggle hard to get free.
"Hahahaha. I've won now,
Runa Runa 7!"
Runa Runa 7 is in trouble!!!
They won!
A
Segawa Yuuta
Coming! Who is it-
A
Segawa Yuuta
Watermelon Mask!
Hina, don't come over here!
Runacular Sparkle!
That was fast!
I live next door.
I brought a watermelon from back home.
Would you like some?
Sorry for stopping by so suddenly.
So you're staying at your uncle's place for the summer.
Sorry we didn't pay you a visit.
Sorry.
You two are very polite.
My name is Takanashi Miu.
I'm Hina!
I'm Atarashi Kurumi. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, as well.
Are you a student?
You would think that, since these apartments are
mainly for students, but I'm actually a voice actress.
Really? So do you get to go on TV and stuff?
Sometimes, I guess.
Look! Look!
Is it morning?
But it's almost lunchtime!
Let go of that girl!
They're playing Runa Runa!
It's a summer break Runa Runa Seven marathon.
Don't even try to move, Runa Runa Seven!
That's low!
It's Watermelon Mask!
Oh, it's an episode I was in.
Huh?
You're in this show?!
You're Runa Runa Seven?!
Huh? No!
Transform!
I wanna see a Runacular Sparkle!
Um, I'm not... Runa Runa Seven...
Let's hear your voice!
Huh?
I'll turn Runa Runa too!
Runacular Sparkle!
I'll leave you hopping this time! So long!
Curse you, Runa Runa Seven...
Huh?
yen
Sora-chan hasn't come home yet?
Nope, she's probably out shopping.
Uncles, come home soon.
I will.
Right, got it.
Hello?
Sora-chan, where are you right now?
Looks like I got on the wrong bus.
Want me to come get you?
I'll be fine.
I can get back by myself.
But...
I'll be fine.
Please recharge
I don't want to give him any more trouble...
This call cannot be completed
because the person you have called has turned their phone off
or is not in an area with reception.
Sora-chan
Segawa-chan.
I was planning on seeing you in action at work.
Huh?
Segawa-chan?
Sora-chan took the wrong bus.
She said she could get back on her own, right?
But she hasn't been here long.
There are a lot of places she doesn't know yet.
Let's split up and look for her.
Yuuta... You know...
You told me there was someone you wanted me to meet.
You can't just tell me you're dating someone and want to get married out of nowhere...
I...
Yuuta...
I can imagine you're surprised by how sudden this is.
But we had to tell you about it somehow-
Restroom.
Yuuta!
Miu!
If it hurts, you don't have to hold it in.
Let me see.
Just let me see.
That looks painful.
W-Wait a second.
Wait a second!
People are going to think I made you cry.
Please don't cry.
It's raining and my mom
brought me a umbrella. I'm so happy.
Drip, drop, drip, drop, la la la.
There we go. All done.
My sister told me a long time ago that I should carry these in my wallet.
I used to trip and fall a lot when I was a kid.
Well? Does it still hurt?
Good, now head back first.
Thank you... Uh...
Uncle!
Wait, am I this "Uncle"?
Yeah, because Yuri-san's...
Well, that's true, but...
I'm still in middle school.
Uncle's a bit...
How about Yuu-chan, then?
That's what my sister calls me, so please spare me from that.
Hmm... Then...
Onii-chan!
Sora-chan!
Something like this happened a long time ago, didn't it?
Huh? You remember?
You remember too.
Well, I just couldn't forget that.
You couldn't?
Never mind.
Here you go.
It's a shame your nice clothes got so dirty.
They're nicer than usual.
It took you a while to notice.
The sunset's pretty.
It's clear because it's just rained.
That's not it.
It's because we're together.
Huh? What?
Nothing.
Um...
Can I call you...
Huh?
Onii-chan?
Sure.
I'd like that better, anyway.
Thank you, Onii-chan.
I'm glad you ran into Sora-chan.
Yeah, sorry about that.
Later, then.
Yeah, talk to you later.
Pretty impressive.
A
Finances
Chiharu Preschool
Enrollment Guide
I need to work hard.
Oh, it's time.
A job that pays daily will really help out.
Thanks, Sako-senpai.
Wait!
Come over here!
This is just another case of bad luck!
Another complete accident!
A complete accident!
I'm really not doing this on purpose!
I'm going to work!
Uncle, you really need more delicacy.
I love strawberries!
Don't tell anyone about the things you see here.
Why?
Hanamura Confections' strawberry daifuku are supposed to be made by cute forest animals!
Strawberry
Daifuku
You can't ruin children's dreams!
pikapika to hikaru boku dake no sweet love
Sparkling and bright, this is my sweet love
kanaeru kana kono ai wa
Will it work out? My love, for you
michitekuru koi wa nani iro darou na
This love filling me up, what color is it?
sukoshi dake miseyou kana
Maybe I'll show you just a little
tokimeki to mawaru chiisana shunkan
Sparking and spinning, a little moment
wakiokoru iro ga aru
There's a color just breaking through
yurayura to yureru chiisana sekai wo
Rolling and swaying, this little world
sotto sotto iyashitekuru yo
Softly, softly, sweetening it up
ochame sugi na kimi no coloring
It's way too much for me, your coloring
boku no naka wo meguri meguru yo
ku
It just goes round and round inside me
na
gu
wo
yo
kurukuru mawaru odoru kimi no coloring
o
Round and round, spinning, dancing, your coloring
kakenukete yuku hajiketa soda mitai
o
It flies right past me, like a can of soda popping open
suteki na color no kimi wa boku wo kanjiteru kana
Your colors are wonderful, can you feel me now?
o
staying in your love
kirakira na amai love
A sparkling, sweet love
kurukuru mawaru odoru kimi no coloring
Round and round, spinning, dancing, your coloring
maiagaru kana yawarakana ichigo milk
Will it go high enough? A soft, strawberry milk
suteki na color no kimi wa nani wo egaiteru kana
Your colors are wonderful, what are you painting now?
staying in your love
kirakira na amai love
A sparkling, sweet love
It's Hina!
Me, Uncles, Sora Nee-tan, and Miu Nee-tan, go to see the doctor.
"A Wonderful Family Trip."
A Wonderful Family Trip
See you!
See you again
Artist
Katou Toomo