Onee-chan, take off your clothes.
Huh?
I'll undress too, so...
take them off...
Huh?
Wai-
What's gotten into you?
Wait! Cut it out, Miu.
You're so pretty, Onee-chan.
You're really pretty.
Onee-chan...
No!
Huh?
Wh-What is this?
What do you think?
You're going on your honeymoon, right?
You gotta look nice.
Huh?
Come here, Sora.
I couldn't afford a wedding,
but I bought this with
three months worth of pay.
It's beautiful.
Not nearly as beautiful as you, though.
Sora-chan...
Pass me some of that
Runa Runa 7 season-all.
happy happy girl
itsu kara kana fushigi
When did it happen? It's so strange
kono mune no oku wa
The deepest parts of my heart
kimi no kakera bakari
Are filled with bits of you
doushiyou haato bousou
What should I do? My heart's gone crazy
doki doki deeto no souzou
Imagining a date that'll happen, maybe
kyunte tobihanechau kodou
Beating like it'll fly out of me
shizen ni hoppeta potte
Without thinking, my hands are on my cheeks
somaru no kakushitemo ki ga tsuite yo
But hiding them won't help, I already know
katamuiteku kokoro no kakudo
My heart's compass keeps turning to one place
omoi no shisen wa kimi muki
My feelings point right to you
mou koi wo shiteru
I'm already in love
happy happy girl
eeru wo okurasete
Let me cheer you on
kimi ga mezasu sora idaku
I want to see the same world as you
yume wo issho ni oikakeru yo
Let's chase our dreams together from now on
candy candy love
riido wa mada mada tayorinai kamo demo
I might not be very reliable right now
senaka ni yorisou
But if I can become
sasae ni ne naretara
Someone that you can lean on,
sotto sotto suki de itemo ii desu ka
Then can I keep on loving you like this?
You're Not There
When I Want You to Be...
Those are freshly made. They're good.
These are good.
We'll take ten of the cheese-battered, then.
Coming right up.
Where's Hina-chan today?
Miu's picking her up today.
Oh, I see.
Please give these corn croquettes
to Hina-chan for me, then.
Thank you, as always.
Hina-chan's sister.
Hello.
Hina-chan isn't with you?
No.
Oh? Where's Hina-chan today?
Oh, she's with Miu today.
I'm surprised.
Hm?
Hina-chan's pretty popular.
She really is.
Yuuta was saying that it
feels like Hina is his daughter.
What's Onii-chan like at school?
He's a sleeping person.
Sleeping?
He's known for consistently falling asleep during lectures.
That's why he's a sleeping person.
He's really pushing himself
with all those jobs he has.
But he's happy. He's a dad.
Huh?
Yuuta said so himself.
That looks pretty difficult.
You won't be able to attend
the RORI like that.
Sorry,
but it feels like, right now, things are going well for me as a dad.
I see.
I go to work, head home,
and when I see their faces...
It just makes me really happy, you know?
He really said that?
Yeah. That's why I told him
I want to be a mother.
Huh?
You three are just
the cutest things ever.
So that's what she meant.
Huh? Somehow, my…
My boobs got bigger. Why?
Okay, I'll see you later.
Huh?
Oh, see you!
Later.
See you later, Onii-chan.
Come on, I'm not "Onii-chan" anymore.
We're married now. You know what
you're supposed to call me, right?
I...
Yu-Yuuta-san.
Good. Now where's my goodbye kiss?
R-Right...
You're finally awake?
You've been falling
asleep a lot lately.
S-Sorry.
I know what you mean! I've been like that too.
School
Eat
Sleep
Study
Free
Time
Eat
Review
When we're going to and
from school, you know?
I mean, it's fine when we can sit, but...
We're pretty much on our feet all morning.
On your feet?
Oh, Uncles is back!
I'm home.
Welcome back, Uncles!
Welcome back.
Were you a good girl today?
Yeah!
We did somersaults today!
I see!
That's amazing, Hina!
We'll be done here in a second.
Go ahead and take a bath first.
Sure.
So, Hina, want to take a bath?
Yeah!
Let's see. I need a change of clothes...
Oh, yeah... The room's kinda...
Sorry. Since school started up again, we've been pretty busy.
Don't worry about it.
I've been pretty busy myself.
I guess it just means we're
doing what we need to do.
Twinkle, twinkle...
You're too fast!
I was practicing singing,
like we do in school!
Oh, I see. Singing.
All right. Let's go to the bath!
Go! Go!
I've brought my husband with me.
Huh? That's weird.
Onii-chan?
It's okay, Sora.
We don't need to see him. We believe you.
But...
Yuuta forgot something.
He's so careless.
He forgot something?
Go look for it with him, Sora.
Takanashi Family
A
In this hot season, how is everyone holding up?
We've finished constructing Takanashi Shingo and Yuri's grave,
so we've sent this notice out to let everyone know. I'm sure it would
please them both for everyone to take some time to visit.
East Ikebukuro
Ikebukuro
Cemetery
But we won't be able to go.
I have to pick Hina up, make dinner, and everything else.
Sorry, Dad, Yuri-san.
Takanashi Family
How's school?
Any problems?
I guess it's okay.
What about your club?
Resignation
Letter
It's lots of fun.
That's good. My sister was really happy.
She was glad that you were able to join a club and have fun with everyone there.
Yuri-san was?
Yeah.
I'm sure it's rough at times,
but keep working hard
until you graduate.
Just kidding.
I bet I was acting too
much like a dad there.
Hey, Miu-chan.
I told you to wipe off the table.
I'm tired.
You snuck in some late-night gaming, didn't you?
That's not it.
What's wrong, then?
You're right...
How did you know?
Well, we are together all the time.
Darn.
Come on, Hina. Time to wake up.
Come on. Wake up, Hina.
Sorry, I just need a second.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Do you have some of that
medicine I gave you?
Yeah.
Take it when you really need to.
It's better if you don't take too much,
so only when you need to, okay?
Yeah.
You did really well this morning.
It's better not to worry Uncle so much.
Yeah.
If we make Onii-chan do more than he already is, I'm sure things would take a turn for the worse.
It'll work out somehow,
if we all work together.
Yo.
R-Raika-san. Hello.
What happened to your
lecture? Cancelled?
No, I was late today,
so I'm just ditching.
Why don't you stop by the RORI?
It's nice to have a long chat every so often.
Sure.
Then...
Actually, I'm sorry.
I took a long night shift today,
so when I get back home
I'm going to sleep.
My batteries are going to die soon too.
I want to be as close to
you as I can, honestly.
How about I grant that desire of yours for just a moment?
Here.
How about that?
Yeah.
Now then, farewell!
Work for justice.
Justice?
Cute is justice.
Right.
Where are we going?
We're going to get something I forgot.
Something you forgot?
What did you forget?
The happiness I have here.
Uncles!
Uncle!
Onii-chan.
I love you!
Huh?
No way...
Sora-chan?
Miu-chan?
Was it Nimura? No...
Who's there?
It's me.
Aunt Yoshiko?!
Hello?
Yes, I'm Hina's sister.
Hina-chan's got a bit of a fever.
What?
I tried calling your uncle, but I couldn't get a hold of him.
I wonder if she's okay...
She'll be fine. I know she will.
Should we keep this a secret?
It'll depend on Hina, but we should if we can.
Onee-chan, the lights are on.
Please keep it up.
G-Good evening.
Sora-chan.
Miu-chan.
What's wrong with Hina-chan?!
Hina!
Once she wakes up, heat this up.
Okay.
If you can't feed her,
then grate up an apple and give her that.
Sure. Thank you very much.
Yuuta-san, you should
completely understand now.
Think about the letter and have an answer ready soon.
Right.
I'm going to go to work.
Um, Onii-chan?
I want to look after Hina, but...
Where are we going, Onii-chan?
We should head back soon.
That's dangerous, Onii-chan!
Stop it!
Onii-chan!
Onii-chan...
Welcome back.
You're awake.
I wanted to ask you about some things.
All right, just for a bit.
Aunt Yoshiko was worried and
came to check up on us.
She borrowed the key from the landlord,
and when she went in the room, it was a mess.
She couldn't stand it, so she
cleaned it up and did the laundry.
She got mad at me for
the room being so untidy.
I should have done it.
I'm sorry.
It's not your fault.
But she just kind of got to me.
Have you been attending all of your classes?
Yes, pretty much.
What do you mean "pretty much"?
I...
This is too much.
You're not taking care of your
education or the children!
I'm making sure to take care of
Sora-chan and the others!
This was in one of the magazines.
Chiharu Daycare
We're having a musical
Have you even read it?
Chiharu Daycare
We're having a musical
It looks like this is the
first you've seen of it.
This is very important for children.
It looked like all the other papers
that came from the daycare,
so I was just going to look at
it later and left it there...
But everyone forgets things.
I didn't just make a mistake.
I was all excited that I was a father.
That's...
I didn't know anything...
I didn't know you two were
pretending to be fine, either.
When children have a change in
environment, they grow nervous.
It's common for signs to show
up where you can't see them.
They've been going to school full of energy...
I knew it.
Sora-chan's hasn't been going
to her club, you know?
Huh?
Miu-chan has been feeling lightheaded and goes to the nurse's office quite often.
You should have seen signs
of that just from living with them.
Being a parent means you should be keeping an eye out for that, at the very least.
When Hina broke out in a fever,
they couldn't even get a hold of me.
Well your phone was out of batteries...
It's my responsibility as a parent
to make sure it's always charged.
My sister always made sure to do that when we lived together.
But I'm...
I'm sorry.
It's even worse for me to
make you sad like that.
Onii-chan.
I'll think about it.
I'll think about what would make you girls happiest.
Think about the letter and
have an answer ready soon.
Did Onii-chan purposely
not mention the letter?
I couldn't get the letter off my mind.
See you!
See you later.
Be a good girl, Hina.
Hina, let's go for a walk.
Okay, let's go!
Onee-chan, you should come along.
Huh? Oh, I have something to-
Twinkle, twinkle, little star.
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
A
What's the
letter about?
Takanashi  Nobuyoshi
Uncle Nobuyoshi...
Yuuta-kun, are you doing well?
Are Sora and the others still the same?
I've heard some information
from Yoshiko-san,
but I still worry that the girls are going to school in poor health.
I said some harsh things during
the night of the funeral,
so I'm sure the girls hate me.
But I said what I did because I thought it was in everyone's best interests.
I couldn't do anything about
how they felt, though.
I've talked things
over with my wife,
and talked amongst the relatives,
and now I'm prepared to do whatever it takes.
I can take the girls in, all three of them.
It may be late to offer this,
but I think it's my responsibility
as an adult in this situation.
So I want you, Yuuta-kun,
to pursue your own happiness,
as Yuri-san would have wanted.
I'm sure Shingo and Yuri-san didn't want for you to sacrifice yourself for the girls.
Cheers!
Good for you, Hina.
You got better really fast.
Hina's a strong kid.
That's right! I am strong!
Runacular Sparkle!
Hey.
It's fine. It just means
she's gotten better.
I am fine.
I promised Bunny I would be.
If I work hard practicing
dancing and singing,
Mommy and Daddy will come back!
Hina...
I wonder where Mommy and
Daddy are right now.
I wonder if they'll call
when they get back.
I'm going to practice
a lot and show them!
Twinkle, twinkle, little star,
how I wonder what you are.
pikapika to hikaru boku dake no sweet love
Sparkling and bright, this is my sweet love
kanaeru kana kono ai wa
Will it work out? My love, for you
michitekuru koi wa nani iro darou na
This love filling me up, what color is it?
sukoshi dake miseyou kana
Maybe I'll show you just a little
tokimeki to mawaru chiisana shunkan
Sparking and spinning, a little moment
wakiokoru iro ga aru
There's a color just breaking through
yurayura to yureru chiisana sekai wo
Rolling and swaying, this little world
sotto sotto iyashitekuru yo
Softly, softly, sweetening it up
ochame sugi na kimi no coloring
It's way too much for me, your coloring
boku no naka wo meguri meguru yo
It just goes round and round inside me
kurukuru mawaru odoru kimi no coloring
o
Round and round, spinning, dancing, your coloring
kakenukete yuku hajiketa soda mitai
o
It flies right past me, like a can of soda popping open
suteki na color no kimi wa boku wo kanjiteru kana
Your colors are wonderful, can you feel me now?
o
staying in your love
kirakira na amai love
A sparkling, sweet love
kurukuru mawaru odoru kimi no coloring
Round and round, spinning, dancing, your coloring
maiagaru kana yawarakana ichigo milk
Will it go high enough? A soft, strawberry milk
suteki na color no kimi wa nani wo egaiteru kana
Your colors are wonderful, what are you painting now?
staying in your love
kirakira na amai love
A sparkling, sweet love
I love you, Uncles!
I love you, Uncle!
Onii-chan, thanks.
After all that?!
That's the best I can do!
It's fine, Onee-chan.
It's over now.
I Love Daddy Most in the World
It's not over yet.
See you again
Artist
Sukeno Yoshiaki