I promised Bunny I would be.
If I work hard practicing dancing and singing,
Mommy and Daddy will come back!
Hina...
I wonder where Mommy and Daddy are right now.
I wonder if they'll call when they get back.
happy happy girl
itsu kara kana fushigi
When did it happen? It's so strange
kono mune no oku wa
The deepest parts of my heart
kimi no kakera bakari
Are filled with bits of you
doushiyou haato bousou
What should I do? My heart's gone crazy
doki doki deeto no souzou
Imagining a date that'll happen, maybe
kyunte tobihanechau kodou
Beating like it'll fly out of me
shizen ni hoppeta potte
Without thinking, my hands are on my cheeks
somaru no kakushitemo ki ga tsuite yo
But hiding them won't help, I already know
katamuiteku kokoro no kakudo
My heart's compass keeps turning to one place
omoi no shisen wa kimi muki
My feelings point right to you
mou koi wo shiteru
I'm already in love
happy happy girl
eeru wo okurasete
Let me cheer you on
kimi ga mezasu sora idaku
I want to see the same world as you
yume wo issho ni oikakeru yo
Let's chase our dreams together from now on
candy candy love
riido wa mada mada tayorinai kamo demo
I might not be very reliable right now
senaka ni yorisou
But if I can become
sasae ni ne naretara
Someone that you can lean on,
sotto sotto suki de itemo ii desu ka
Then can I keep on loving you like this?
I Love Daddy Most in the World
We have to tell her.
Dad and Yuri-san aren't coming home.
Do you think she'll understand?
I'll tell her.
Twinkle, twinkle, little star,
how I wonder what you are.
Up above the world so high,
Hey, Hina.
About Mommy and Daddy...
Did they call?
No, they didn't.
Oh. When are they coming back?
Don't you wanna see them too, Sora Nee-tan?
Will they bring lots of presents?
They've been gone for so long, they have to have lots!
You know, Hina.
Dad and Yuri-san...
Mommy and Daddy aren't coming home.
They're very, very far away,
and they can't come home.
They can't come home?
It's sad, but that's how it is.
I'll go see them, then!
I'll go see Mommy and Daddy!
You can't!
You can't do that!
Why?
If Mommy and Daddy aren't coming home,
then I won't get to see them unless I go!
You can't go see them.
You can't see Mommy and Daddy again.
What about the musical?
They can't go.
No!
No! No! No!
I want Mommy and Daddy to come!
I've been a good girl!
Hina...
I'll go instead.
I'll be there for you, Hina.
I don't want Uncles!
I want Mommy and Daddy!
They promised!
Don't be so selfish-
I hate Sora Nee-tan!
Mommy and Daddy wouldn't break a promise!
I promised Bunny too!
I'm sorry, Hina.
No!
Don't cry.
Don't cry...
Please...
What's wrong?
Going to pick up Hina-chan?
Ah, yes.
Thank goodness she went to daycare.
I heard from Segawa-chan.
She didn't want to at first, but three days ago she suddenly changed her mind.
She's apparently having fun at daycare,
but she can't practice for the musical.
I see.
How is Onii-chan doing?
What do you mean?
Last night, I overheard Onii-chan.
He said, "Maybe I'm just an Uncles."
So that's why...
Do you think I can be their father?
Of course not.
Yuuta.
That's cruel.
Why would Raika-san say that?
Oda-senpai can be pretty harsh.
Is he okay? It is Onii-chan...
I believe in him.
Onee-chan!
It doesn't matter, let's keep walking there!
If you want to cry, look-
Hina-chan! Come here!
'kay!
You sure look happy in this rain!
Here you go!
Thanks!
She looks really happy.
She was talking to Bunny yesterday.
I won't cry anymore!
If I cry, Sora Nee-tan and Miu Nee-tan will cry too.
That's why I won't cry anymore.
She said that?
Apparently, she couldn't practice for the musical today, either.
I've talked it over with my wife and talked amongst the relatives,
and now I'm prepared to do whatever it takes.
I can take the girls in, all three of them.
It may be late to offer this,
but I think it's my responsibility as an adult in this situation.
So I want you, Yuuta-kun,
to pursue your own happiness, as Yuri-san would have wanted.
I'm sure Shingo and Yuri-san didn't want for you to sacrifice yourself for the girls.
Please respond by the end of the month.
I await your decision.
You're still up?
I wanted to talk to you.
What is it?
Maybe we should keep her home for Parents' Day.
Say something!
I'm still thinking.
I'm leaving the apartment early tomorrow.
Where are you going?
Somewhere.
To see Uncle Nobuyoshi?
I won't be too long.
Nee-san. I'm sorry I'm such a pathetic brother.
I'm so indecisive,
but I've finally decided.
It's kind of sad, but there's no other choice.
I-
No!
I don't want that!
Sora-chan?
I want to stay with you, Onii-chan!
I read Uncle Nobuyoshi's letter!
I don't want to go, even if it's all three of us!
I just want to be with you!
Thank goodness.
I feel the same way.
But you just said there's no other choice...
That it's kind of sad...
What's sad is that I can't be your real father.
Onii-chan...
That's fine, though.
I might be useless as a guardian, but I love all three of you.
More than anything in the world.
That's why I'll do everything I can to take care of you.
The same way Nee-san did.
Thank you, Onii-chan!
H-Hey! Sora-chan!
Uncle... Aunt...
Thank you very much for coming.
I've caused you more trouble than I'm worth.
No, you've given us a lot of time to think.
My letter was one of many solutions.
Frankly, I was indecisive.
I want to be clear-
No need.
We saw everything.
We can see that the girls have grown attached to you.
So we've decided that they can stay with you for a while longer.
Thank you very much!
Aunt Yoshiko, may I ask one question?
What is it?
Why did you let me do what I did?
I guess you might call it "atonement."
15 years ago, I felt the same way you did,
but I didn't have the strength to do anything.
The strength to take both you and Yuri-san in.
Aunt Yoshiko...
You really are Yuri-san's brother.
Thank you very much.
Still...
it won't be easy to take care of Hina.
I understand,
but I'm good at not knowing when to give up.
Uncle Nobuyoshi is a nice person.
Yeah.
He lives far away, so we never really saw him.
I didn't know, but...
we hurt them, didn't we?
All of our relatives.
Well...
Even you.
I'm sorry about everything.
Just try your best to be happy.
That's enough for me.
Okay.
I-I'm sorry! I-
It just felt like Yuri-san was holding me, so...
I see.
Nee-san did that to you a lot too, huh?
Like holding you close and messing up your hair.
She had the strangest effect on people.
At first, you'd be surprised, but before you knew it, everything would be all right.
I know what you mean. She was always like that-
Wait...
We can go!
Wait, Onii-ch-
Let's go!
Nee-san did that too.
My first Parents' Day after we lost our parents...
Sorry I'm late!
Give me a second...
Segawa Yuuta's mother, father, brother, grandfather, grandmother, and sister!
Basically, his entire family, Segawa Yuri, is here to see him!
Yay!
It was so embarrassing.
That's totally like her!
Yeah.
After that, everyone kept saying how amazing my sister was.
Hina, what's that?
Wait, Onii-chan...
What on Earth-
You'll see soon enough!
Sora-chan?
Um... hello.
Excuse me.
What's the fuss?
Thank you very much for what you said to me, Raika-san.
Do you think I can be their father?
Of course not.
I couldn't accept it and just ran out,
but now that I've had time to think about it, I understand what you were trying to say.
I'm not their father, but I'm their father.
Precisely.
Good work, Yuuta.
You're not their father, but you are their father.
Now then, Segawa Yuuta, which panel will you choose?
Just one question, Raika-san.
Will you be my wife?
Parents' Day
Chiharu Daycare
Musical
Hey!
Do you think she'll be okay?
I wonder if this will work.
Let's just try and see.
Raika-san?
No. Today, I'm your wife.
Don't pout.
Hina-chan's really popular.
We're all here for her.
Everyone...
Outta the way!
We can't see Hina-chan with you in the way!
Ah, I'm sorry.
Go get 'em, Hina!
We're all here for you!
Hina-chan, you're amazing!
You have so many mommies and daddies!
That mommy is pretty!
So many cute mommies!
I'll do my best!
Now then, let the show begin.
Let's start with a big greeting.
Mom and Dad, thank you for coming to see us today!
We are proud
to present to you
our musical.
We hope you all enjoy it!
Twinkle, twinkle, little star,
how I wonder what you are.
Up above the world so high,
I like this.
I love it.
like a diamond in the sky.
I'm so glad to be your wife.
Hear that?
Twinkle, twinkle, little star,
What now, Onee-chan?
Hey, don't push!
how I wonder what you are.
Keep it up, Hina!
Mommy and Daddy are watching!
Twinkle, twinkle, little star,
So that's your plan...
how I wonder what you are.
Being a father sure looks nice.
Don't go around being everyone's father, though!
Up above the world so high,
Hey now.
This kind of thing is too much for me! I'm going to-
like a diamond in the sky.
Twinkle, twinkle, little star
how I wonder what you are.
And now for our next song.
Acorn, rolly-rolly, roll, roll, plop!
You fell in the lake, oh my, no!
Out comes a little minnow, hello mister fish.
Parents' Day
Hi there little acorn, won't you play with me?
Nee-san, did you see?
I feel relieved after seeing Hina smile like that.
I'm truly blessed to be surrounded by such nice people at school and in town.
"Family" is a strange thing.
Even if it's just the two of you, you're family.
Even if you're separated, you're family.
Even if you're not related, you're family.
The four of us will always hold it dear.
The happiness of becoming a family.
Forever and ever.
He's almost here. Ready?
Roger!
Oh no! I gotta pee!
No. No peeing.
I can't hold it!
I'm home!
Huh?
Is anyone home?
Onii-chan!
Uncle!
Thanks for working so hard for us!
That's not right! Uncles is Daddy!
Here! A present from Hina!
For me?
That's right! Thanks for making us all so happy!
Thank you so much, Hina!
I want to eat cake!
You even bought cake?
Okay, let's take a picture!
Everyone together now. Come on!
What? I'll have to change first!
Huh? It's only one picture...
No peeking, okay?
I can't hold it anymore!
Miu!
Cake! Cake!
See, I told you...
Where does it hurt?
I'm sorry, but...
could you go outside for a while?
What about the picture?
This is more important than that!
Cake! Cake!
Uncles, open the door!
Er... it's the other way around.
Stop that, Miu!
Say something before you open the curtain!
I want cake!
Cake! Cake!
Come on, girls!
Listen to your daddy!
pikapika to hikaru boku dake no sweet love
Sparkling and bright, this is my sweet love
kanaeru kana kono ai wa
Will it work out? My love, for you
michitekuru koi wa nani iro darou na
This love filling me up, what color is it?
sukoshi dake miseyou kana
Maybe I'll show you just a little
tokimeki to mawaru chiisana shunkan
Sparking and spinning, a little moment
wakiokoru iro ga aru
There's a color just breaking through
yurayura to yureru chiisana sekai wo
Rolling and swaying, this little world
sotto sotto iyashitekuru yo
Softly, softly, sweetening it up
ochame sugi na kimi no coloring
It's way too much for me, your coloring
boku no naka wo meguri meguru yo
It just goes round and round inside me
kurukuru mawaru odoru kimi no coloring
Round and round, spinning, dancing, your coloring
kakenukete yuku hajiketa soda mitai
It flies right past me, like a can of soda popping open
suteki na color no kimi wa boku wo kanjiteru kana
Your colors are wonderful, can you feel me now?
staying in your love
kirakira na amai love
A sparkling, sweet love
kurukuru mawaru odoru kimi no coloring
Round and round, spinning, dancing, your coloring
maiagaru kana yawarakana ichigo milk
Will it go high enough? A soft, strawberry milk
suteki na color no kimi wa nani wo egaiteru kana
Your colors are wonderful, what are you painting now?
staying in your love
kirakira na amai love
A sparkling, sweet love
A
Takanashi
Segawa Yuuta
Sora
Miu
Hina
I'm home!
Welcome home,
Onii-chan!
Uncle!
Uncles Daddy!
Bye-bye
Artist
Nakajima Yuka