Oh, crap.
Segawa Yuuta
A
Nee-san, it's my first day of college.
You don't have to worry
about me so much anymore.
I'll find a good part-time job
and make it on my own.
Tama University for the Arts
Tama University
for the Arts
Roadway Observation Research Institute
New Student Get Together
A
Roadway Observation Research Institute
New Student Get Together
A
Roadway Observation Research Institute
New Student Get Together
A
Roadway Observation Research Institute
New Student Get Together
A
Roadway Observation Research Institute
New Student Get Together
A
Roadway Observation Research Institute
New Student Get Together
A
Roadway Observation Research Institute
New Student Get Together
A
Roadway Observation Research Institute
New Student Get Together
A
Roadway Observation Research Institute
New Student Get Together
A
Roadway Observation Research Institute
New Student Get Together
A
Roadway Observation Research Institute
New Student Get Together
A
Roadway Observation Research Institute
New Student Get Together
A
Huh?
So you're awake,
first year Japanese literature major,
Segawa Yuuta-kun?
How do you know my name?
You've got guts,
drinking until you threw up, and on your first night in college.
What's more, you did something terrible...
Something terrible?
Behold!
Sob, sob, sob.
Oda-kun, Oda-kun...
Put more emotion into it.
Sob, sob, sob?
No, I didn't mean to turn it into a question.
Sob, sob, sob...
Sob, sob, sob?
Anyway!
Sob, sob, sob...
First year, Segawa Yuuta!
Yes?
While you were drunk,
you did something extremely lewd to Oda-kun here!
Huh?
Sob, sob, sob...
I don't remember anything like that...
But you did!
You must make amends...
this instant!
Make amends? But-
You have no say in the matter!
Sob... sob?
Come on, Oda-kun! Say something!
I'm so scared.
Are you... making all this up?
Wh-What are you talking about?!
You most certainly-
Sako-senpai, I think it's
about time you stopped...
So bright!
C-Cut it out, Joker!
You're trying to probe me
and alter my body...
Sucks for you, Segawa.
Oh, uh...
You were sitting next to me...
You're... Nimura?
Bingo!
You were drinking non-alcoholic beer,
but you still got drunk off the
fumes from everyone else's alcohol.
That's right, Segawa Yuuta!
After becoming drunk, you took off all your clothes...
and ran around the shopping
district near the train station.
You saw the art piece in the
plaza there, climbed it,
and stood atop it with your arms akimbo!
Then, with both your hands at your crotch, a giant black-
I don't like dirty jokes.
Oda-kun!
How many times do I have to tell you? You're supposed to hit me with a fan when you riposte!
Oh. Right.
W-Wait! Hey!
Oda-kun!
N-No... I can't hold on...
Leave the rest to me.
O-Okay...
So what was all that about, anyway?
That's how the Roadway Observation Research Institute welcomes people.
Roadway... Observation?
A
Roadway Observation
Research Institute
RORI for short.
That's how they welcome
newcomers, it seems.
I never want to see them again.
But you know...
That "sobbing" girl was pretty cute.
Was she?
She could easily be a model or actress.
She may already be affiliated
with some agency.
You really think so?
I'm pretty good at sizing up chicks.
The "sobbing" girl, huh?
Hey, do you think Daddy'll be surprise?
It's "be surprised."
He's back!
Oh no! I gotta pee!
I'm home.
Huh? No one's home?
Mom? Sora?
Miu? Hina?
Let's go.
One, two...!
Welcome home!
Daddy, thanks for everything!
Here's your Father's Day present!
Thanks, girls!
Mom, take a picture for posterity.
Okay! I'm taking the picture now!
Okay, everyone scoot in.
Daddy's so happy!
Come on, look at the camera. It's just one picture!
Come on, girls! Listen to your daddy!
Listen to me, girls. I am your father!
Don't Call Me Daddy
What's up, Nee-san?
You're doing pretty
well, aren't you?
It's only been a month since you started college and you're already living with a girl?
Huh?
No, that's Nimura you're hearing.
Oh, Nimura-kun doesn't have a place to live?
He does, but he only uses it
when he lures girls back to his place.
I don't lure them. I invite them.
He even brought his bed along.
I'm the one paying the
50,000 yen rent every month.
That's why I pay for my own food,
and I do the cleaning and laundry, don't I?
Open up.
You should be able to do all of that yourself.
Get married when you graduate.
That again?
I might talk about this all the time,
but it's nice when your family gets bigger.
You should stop by sometime.
The dust still hasn't fully settled here, yet.
Hina says she wants to see her uncle.
Right?
She's still only two, isn't she?
She's three now!
Lately, when Shingo-san gets back from work,
she'll say stuff like, "Welcome home, Daddy!"
And why should I care?
Just come over here sometime.
I'm fine.
I don't want to break up your
family time by bugging you guys.
What was that?
Don't say anything like that again.
You'll always be family,
no matter where you are.
I married Shingo-san and gained two wonderful daughters.
We might not be related by blood,
and I haven't lived with them long enough for them to call me "Mommy,"
but I think of them as my family.
They're no different from Hina,
who I carried with me for all that time.
They're my daughters.
It's the same with you, Yuuta.
I'm sorry.
No, it's okay.
I'm sure you'll understand
when you fall in love
and make your own family.
Oh, crap.
It's been a while.
Have you been well?
I, uh...
Don't tell me you don't remember me?
Sob, sob, sob.
You're that "sobbing" girl!
Sorry.
That was my bad.
I don't mind.
I'm a second year liberal arts major.
Oda Raika.
I'm, uh...
I already know.
First year Japanese literature major,
Segawa Yuuta.
Th-That's right.
Question.
What did you mean by "the sobbing girl"?
Huh?
Oh, uh, after the party,
that thing you kept saying
in a monotone voice
really got stuck in my head.
Oh, I see. Sob, sob, sob.
Sob, sob... sob, sob.
Um, Oda-senpai?
I don't like being called that.
Call me Raika.
That feels kind of disrespectful...
Call me "the sobbing girl," then.
That's even worse.
What do you want to call me, then?
Uh...
How about just "Raika-san"?
Maybe something else
would have been better?
That's the first time I've heard that.
That might be nice.
Oh, thank goodness...
I'll call you Yuuta, then.
You're not using an honorific even
though we barely know each other?
How about Yuuta-san?
No, that's fine. Really.
I'd rather call you Yuuta, then.
Nice to meet you, Yuuta.
H-Huh? What's going on...
I'll talk to you later then, Yuuta.
Okay...
Nee-san, could I be...
That guy's kinda cute!
Yeah, he really is!
Hey, what do you think, Takanashi-san?
Who do you think the best guy over there is?
Sorry, I don't really know...
I'm not really interested in guys my own age.
Takanashi-san's always like that...
I always feel great after a bath!
What happened to Sora?
She's still in there.
She looked like she was thinking about something.
Maybe she's worried about us being gone.
I told her I was going to get someone to help out. Maybe that's why.
Yeah, Onee-chan is pretty shy.
We'll be gone for a couple days next week.
I'm planning on having
Yuuta watch you guys...
You should have told me sooner!
My arms!
My thighs!
Dieting now won't be enough!
Wait, Segawa!
Hey, Segawa-kun!
I understand what it's like
to be taken aback by a girl...
who's emotionless for 99% of the time and smiles the other 1% of the time.
But that girl...
You need to give up on her.
No thanks. See ya.
Wait.
Listen to what I found out from my research.
Oda Raika, twenty years old.
A second year liberal arts major.
She ranked first on her entrance exams
and was accepted on a scholarship.
She's great at sports and beat the tennis team with straight love games.
So she's pretty amazing, then...
She's got great grades and she's great at sports. A real looker.
Rumor has it that a bunch of guys,
even from colleges in other prefectures, used to flock around her...
during her freshman year,
just to get a look at her.
Well, yeah, of course.
But now, there aren't any guys
who even try to get near her!
That weirdo, the president of the RORI,
seems to be the only guy
that hangs out with her.
What do you think of that?
Raika-san is shy and very protective of herself!
Perfect! It all makes sense!
There's something wrong with your head!
What are you talking about?
She's got a great face and giant tits.
If no guy's trying to get with her,
it means Oda-senpai's a complete weirdo.
Weirdo?
I mean, if she wasn't, she wouldn't join
a weird club like this "Roadway Observation Research Institute" in the first place.
That's right! The Roadway Observation Research Institute...
Hey, wait!
Segawa!
That's right.
If I join that club, I can be with her all the time!
Raika-san, wait for me!
It's been too hot this year.
I couldn't take any more after two months at that job dressing up as a hero for little kids.
That's why I told you to get
a job at a family restaurant or something.
As of yesterday, I've been working for three months.
My trainee period's finally over.
Nimura-kun!
Hey!
How many girls have you lured into going to your place these past three months?
I didn't lure them. I invited them.
But I wonder why Raika-san called us out here.
Huh? Shouldn't you be happier, Segawa-kun?
I haven't really been able to talk to her yet.
I told you she was weird.
Actually, why did you join the RORI with me?
'Cause it seemed like it'd be fun to see your fate play out, of course.
Excuse us.
Oh yeah, I need to go somewhere.
Good luck! Have fun!
Hey! Nimura!
You traitor!
Didst thou drop the small one or the large one?
I didn't actually drop either...
How very honest of thee.
I shall bestow upon thee this special, suspicious parcel of mine.
What kind of experiment are you conducting this time, Raika-san?
Hm... It's a secret.
Anyway, let's go home.
Huh? You're going back wearing that?!
Pull on this.
But...
It'll be fine.
Whatever you say!
Oh my!
Raika-san, is it actually fun
doing stuff like this with me?
Yes.
Today, I was able
to expose another one of
your sexual idiosyncrasies.
What are you talking about?
Arousal resulting from stripping a goddess.
I'm not into anything like that!
Yuuta!
It is you, Yuuta!
There you are! Hey!
You're here really early.
I kept arriving right when the next
train was supposed to come.
There you go.
What's all this?
A gift of love and nostalgia.
See you later.
Oh, uh...
See you later this break.
It's hot out here! Hurry up, already!
Why do you have to go to a college that's so far away from Tokyo?
Did you come all the way
out here to complain?
Your order of fried mother is ready.
So what's up with all this stuff?
It's a bunch of your stuff.
Okay, I'm back on my feet for now.
Jeez, what's this?
I've been busy with essays and my job.
Don't mess with my stuff too much.
Oh? I thought you liked big boobs.
Huh?
W-What are those?!
Did you hide these when we
were living together too?
You've got it wrong.
These...
Why are you looking at that?!
Oda Raika...
Don't look at that!
Here's your assigned reading for the summer.
Make sure you submit a book report.
What's this?
Meow
Oh, it's that girl from before.
Look!
Oh, you're right!
Give me that!
I'm glad you got a big-boobed girlfriend, though.
She's just a senpai from my club.
But you like her, right?
So don't get any weird ideas
about my daughters.
What are you talking about?
This coming Sunday,
there's something really important
I have to take care of.
So I want you to come to my place.
Wh-What's going on?
You'll know when you get there.
Tell me now.
Just come without making a fuss.
I raised you all those years myself.
Please do it for me, your sister.
He said he'd be here Sunday.
This Sunday?
Yeah.
Wait, did you have something planned?
Huh? No, not at all.
I don't have anything.
I've only met him twice,
but our uncle was kinda cool.
You think so?
Uncles?
Uncles? Who?
Mommy's younger brother.
The person who recorded
your first birthday party for us.
I'll be able to see him again...
Way too many people...
Am I still in Ikebukuro?
Takanashi
He's in there, isn't he?
I don't like this! This can't happen!
He's been married twice, with kids from each!
Hi, there.
It's been a while.
Huh?
Do you remember me?
I, uh...
No one's ever forgotten me.
Look at the color of my hair.
I think that's a big hint in and of itself!
Y-Yeah, that's true...
Uh...
Sorry!
It's hot out here, isn't it?
Please, come on in!
Excuse me.
Sit wherever you'd like.
I'll get you something cold to drink.
Onee-chan, he's here!
Onee-chan!
Where's Nee-sa-I mean, your mom?
Daddy and Yuri-san already left a while ago.
Huh? What's going on?
Huh? No one told you?
Well, kind of...
I heard that you're supposed to stay here with us today while they're gone.
You should have told me.
Who's Uncles?
That's mine.
Huh?
That's mine...
I know, but...
That's mine!
Don't cry!
Uh, look!
Wow!
That was cool, Uncles!
Really?
Good.
Wait a second.
Am I "Uncles"?
Yep. You're Uncles.
You're Uncles because you're a Uncles.
At least call me Onii-chan.
I'm not even twenty yet.
Okay, Uncles!
Do it again!
Hurry!
Me too!
I can't do it...
Why? Why?
You might not be able to yet.
No!
No! I can't do it!
Wait, wait.
Your spit's flying everywhere!
I can't do it!
Come on, Hina. Don't cry.
You're making Uncle feel bad.
Trumpet! Blow the trumpet!
Here you go.
Fine. I'll help you, so stop crying.
You want to blow the trumpet, right?
Yeah!
I'll teach you, but it'll be tough.
Do you think you can do it?
Yeah! Teach me!
Okay.
But could you tell me where
the bathroom is first?
Bathrooms?
I want to wash your drool off my face.
The bathroom is straight
through there, past the stairs.
Thanks.
Jeez, kids are a lot of trouble.
happy happy girl
itsu kara kana fushigi
When did it happen? It's so strange
kono mune no oku wa
The deepest parts of my heart
kimi no kakera bakari
Are filled with bits of you
doushiyou haato bousou
What should I do? My heart's gone crazy
doki doki deeto no souzou
Imagining a date that'll happen, maybe
kyunte tobihanechau kodou
Beating like it'll fly out of me
shizen ni hoppeta potte
Without thinking, my hands are on my cheeks
somaru no kakushitemo ki ga tsuite yo
But hiding them won't help, I already know
katamuiteku kokoro no kakudo
My heart's compass keeps turning to one place
omoi no shisen wa kimi muki
My feelings point right to you
mou koi wo shiteru
I'm already in love
happy happy girl
eeru wo okurasete
Let me cheer you on
kimi ga mezasu sora idaku
I want to see the same world as you
yume wo issho ni oikakeru yo
Let's chase our dreams together from now on
candy candy love
riido wa mada mada tayorinai kamo demo
I might not be very reliable right now
senaka ni yorisou
But if I can become
sasae ni ne naretara
Someone that you can lean on,
sotto sotto suki de itemo ii desu ka
Then can I keep on loving you like this?
The second daughter here!
My sister was in the bathroom,
and my uncle saw her!
What will their fate be?
Next time:
"The Maid Saw It All: The Girl's Tears."
Whoever's responsible, come forward!
Come to My House
Look forward to it!
Sorry, I made that up!
See you again
Papakiki Artist:
Takemura Youhei