Uncles, you're scrubbing too hard.
Oh, sorry about that.
I'm going to wash it off now.
Close your eyes.
Okay, look this way.
Uncles, my eyes hurt!
Huh? Make sure they're completely shut!
It hurts! It hurts!
I'll wash it out.
Don't rub your eyes!
Onee-tan!
Stay still.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Onii-chan, you're going to
damage her hair like that.
You have to blow from the roots of the hair in the direction you're brushing.
The direction I'm brushing? Huh?
Give it here.
Nee-tan's good.
Um, Uncle, you don't have
work tomorrow, right?
R-Right.
Actually, I have a favor to ask.
I want to go to our house in Ikebukuro.
Huh?
There's something I want to pick up from there.
Can we go?
The Takanashi family is taking
care of that house now.
I'm not sure if we should go...
I have a key.
If we just slip in and out without
making a scene, we should be fine.
Hina wants to get something too, right?
Yeah!
Hina does too?
It's something really, really important!
happy happy girl
itsu kara kana fushigi
When did it happen? It's so strange
kono mune no oku wa
The deepest parts of my heart
kimi no kakera bakari
Are filled with bits of you
doushiyou haato bousou
What should I do? My heart's gone crazy
doki doki deeto no souzou
Imagining a date that'll happen, maybe
kyunte tobihanechau kodou
Beating like it'll fly out of me
shizen ni hoppeta potte
Without thinking, my hands are on my cheeks
somaru no kakushitemo ki ga tsuite yo
But hiding them won't help, I already know
katamuiteku kokoro no kakudo
My heart's compass keeps turning to one place
omoi no shisen wa kimi muki
My feelings point right to you
mou koi wo shiteru
I'm already in love
happy happy girl
eeru wo okurasete
Let me cheer you on
kimi ga mezasu sora idaku
I want to see the same world as you
yume wo issho ni oikakeru yo
Let's chase our dreams together from now on
candy candy love
riido wa mada mada tayorinai kamo demo
I might not be very reliable right now
senaka ni yorisou
But if I can become
sasae ni ne naretara
Someone that you can lean on,
sotto sotto suki de itemo ii desu ka
Then can I keep on loving you like this?
A Wonderful Family Trip
We're going out!
So happy!
I wonder if Hina's okay...
If she thinks about her
parents, she might get sad...
It's Runa Runa!
Well done!
Runa Runa won't forgive anyone
who does bad things!
Special move time!
Runacular Sparkle!
Excuse me...
Thanks for taking care of Hina...
T-Talk to you later.
Bye-bye!
Our neighbor...
She's in Runa Runa Seven.
She's a voice actress.
Oh, really?
Kotori
Shopping District
Oh, Hina-chan, good morning.
Good morning!
Oh, Hina-chan, you're going
out with your sisters?
Yeah!
Have fun.
Be careful.
Thanks!
She's pretty popular.
Whenever we go shopping,
everyone always talks to her.
We tend to get a lot of gifts when Hina is with us.
Good morning!
Oh, Hina-chan, you seem lively today.
Here you go. Have this.
It's good!
Take this too.
This too.
See?
Anyone who'd see that smile would want to give her something.
You have some too, Uncles.
Cell Phone
Sako-senpai
Oh no. It's Sako-senpai.
Cell Phone
Sako-senpai
What does he want?
Cell Phone
Sako-senpai
Uncles, your phone is ringing.
You're not going to say hi?
Uh... yeah.
Good morning, Segawa-kun!
You don't have work today, do you?!
I just happen to be free today too!
If at all possible, I'd like
to come by your place.
Is that okay?
It's fine, right?
No problem, right?
Today's kinda no good...
Hi!
Oh!
A new angel has descended!
Tachikawa
Kamikitadai District
A
The train bound for Tachikawa
with stop at Kamikitadai is arriving.
That announcer was the one for the station at the Tama University for the Arts, right?!
Wait for me! I'll be right the—
Onii-chan?
This place isn't safe, girls. Let's hurry.
Tachikawa
Kamikitadai District
A
Oh, Miu-chan.
Miu-chan, where have you been?
Have you been doing well?
Miu-chan, let's play.
Play with me, Miu-chan!
No! Play with me, Miu-chan!
Hey, calm down, you guys.
Who are you, mister?
Uh...
It's been a while, guys.
This is my uncle.
Hi there.
Uncle, could you go on ahead with Onee-chan and Hina?
Sure, but will you be okay?
Yes, I'll be fine!
All right, then.
We're here!
Will she really be okay?
Don't worry.
Miu's used to that sort of thing.
Really?
Takanashi-san?
Club president...
I knew it was you.
You haven't come to practice at all,
so I've been worried about you.
S-Sorry.
You'll be coming to choir
next trimester, right?
W-Well...
Hurry up! Let's go!
Let's go! Let's go!
I got it.
I'll head in first.
Take this.
Hurry! Hurry!
I'm hurrying.
You don't have to pull so hard!
Hey!
No one's here.
Hina, you know...
Your mommy and daddy are...
I know!
They're far away, right?
Y-Yeah...
I'm home!
It's dark!
Uncles, turn on the lights!
Sure. Where's the switch?
Right here.
Huh?
Is this it?
It's on!
Thank goodness. They haven't shut off the power or water.
You've done it now! Wait!
Hey, wait! Hina!
Wait! I'm your Uncles!
Uncles is going to get you!
It's been a while.
Yeah.
Sorry for making you wait.
No, it's fine.
Is everything okay with your friends?
Yeah, they're fine.
Everything's fine.
Now you've done it!
Hey!
Wait!
How's this?
What about this?!
Hina! Wait up! Come up!
Quit messing around, you two.
Okay!
What would we do if you got hurt?
But I guess it has been a while.
Okay.
We're going to get our stuff
together, so just wait down here.
I can help out too...
No!
You don't have to worry about me.
That's not the problem.
You really don't have any delicacy, do you?
I was just thinking I could help
you out with anything heavy.
Regardless, you just stay down here.
You can't come up no matter what, Onii-chan!
Hm?
"Onii-chan?"
Well, Hina...
You were going to look for
something important, right?
Uncles can help you out.
I don't need help!
I can do it by myself.
Hmm, where is it?
I'm bored.
Nee-san...
Ta-da! It's bunny!
Oh! So that was your important thing.
It's cute, right?
Mommy gave it to me!
Right?
H-Hina!
Uncles will play with you!
C'mon. Let's play together.
Wh-What?
Okay!
I-I see.
Shopping! Shopping!
What should we eat tonight?
Am I on the same level
as a stuffed animal?
No!
Carrots don't move!
Y-Yes! I'm a carrot!
Are you tired, Uncles?
Yeah. Just a bit.
You can sleep!
Ow!
Go to sleep.
Go to sleep, little baby!
I think I'm going to fall asleep.
It's been a while since I've
been able to relax like this.
I've been working every day, after all.
Segawa Yuuta. He's more clever than I thought.
Nimura-kun, do you honestly not know where he and his nieces are headed?
I don't know.
Is that really true?
Does it look like I'm lying?
That voice...
Hi!
Judging by her voice, she's
probably around the age of three.
She has round, innocent, black eyes.
And long, flowing, black hair.
I wuve you
The makings of an angel!
This guy's worse than I thought.
The birth of a new angel.
Are Yuuta's nieces cute?
Huh?
Teehee
Of course they're cute!
Look at this!
Teehee
Take a look at their lovely figures,
drawn from my imagination!
I wuve you
I'm going to find them!
I'm going to do my best to find
Segawa-kun's angels,
no matter what I have to do!
I'm getting goosebumps...
Crap. When did I fall asleep?
She drooled on me.
What's that?
What are you doing?
Want me to help you?
I'm fine!
You won't be able to carry that.
Why not split it?
Miu and I decided that we'd only take one bag each.
But you're going overboard...
It'll be fine.
Wait, it's not fine!
You're going to fall!
Onii-chan, are you okay?
Y-Yeah...
What's this?
Uncle, that's Onee-chan's favorite...
Huh?
No!
Ow!
All red!
It's gotten pretty late.
Your cheek is all red too!
Sorry... for taking so long.
You're bringing a change of clothes, right?
Y-Yeah...
Girls have it tough, you know?
I see...
Huh? Sora-chan, you wear a uniform.
Do you really need that many clothes?
Huh? Th-That's...
She wants a certain someone to see her at her cutest!
M-Miu!
Onii-chan has nothing to do with this!
Nothing to do!
I'm hungry.
Hungry!
Curry
Golden
Would you cheer up already?
I didn't do it on purpose.
S-Still...
Ow...
Uncles, does your cheek still hurt?
I'll blow on it for you.
Hina...
You're so sweet.
Well, excuse me for not being nice!
No one said anything like that!
It was written all over your face.
Uncles and Onee-tan are fighting?
That's right. It's a lovers' quarrel.
Miu!
You say sorry after you fight, right?
You're right. Hina's right.
Mr. Ducky, Mr. Ducky. Quack, quack.
Hina, make sure you stay warm.
I am!
I'm washing it out now.
Okay!
A shampoo hat.
Humanity sure has evolved.
Onii-chan.
Sora-chan?
I'll leave you a towel.
Th-Thanks.
Sorry.
No, it's okay.
I'm sorry I wasn't being more thoughtful.
I'll have some cold water ready for you.
I want water too!
Got it.
It looks like we were
able to make up, somehow.
It's all thanks to you, Hina.
Hina, are you tired?
Let's get you washed up quickly, then.
Is this pillow okay?
If it's too hot, turn
on the air conditioner.
Thank you.
Onee-chan, Hina's probably not
going to make it much longer.
Well, it is pretty late.
Okay, let's get some sleep.
Good night, Uncle.
Good night.
Night.
I can't sleep.
Excuse me.
M-Miu-chan?
What's wrong?
Um...
Can we sleep together?
Huh?
I couldn't sleep.
I knew you'd be here.
I thought I heard people talking.
I want to sleep with Uncles too!
Come on, Miu...
I just couldn't relax,
being all by myself.
You couldn't sleep either, could you?
That's not it.
Hina woke up, so...
You brought your pillow.
What are you talking about?
This is...
I couldn't sleep, either.
This room is a little too big for me too.
I was just thinking that I liked it more cramped.
I guess I've gotten used to the poor life.
We all feel the same way here,
so let's sleep together.
I guess I'll have to...
I guess I'll have to.
The character for "river."
But with an extra stroke.
It's more like the one for "small" than "river."
You're right.
Could I get a little closer?
Sure...
Me too.
Me too!
Why are you pinching me?
You were grinning just now!
No, I wasn't!
You totally were!
You're such a liar, Onii-chan!
That reminds me.
You've been calling him
"Onii-chan" lately, haven't you?
Why?
Well, uh...
You know.
Yeah.
How suspicious!
Did something happen, Uncle?
S-Stop it, Miu. Don't get so close.
I don't wanna.
Stop grinning, Onii-chan!
I told you I'm not!
Me too!
There's so much room here,
but it ended up the same as back home.
Good night, Nee-san.
Ready, girls?
Ready!
Yeah.
A-okay!
Here. You forgot this.
Huh?
But...
No matter how small the room is,
or how heavy your bag is,
you should take the things
you want with you.
Don't hold back.
Onii-chan...
I want to be with
Mommy and Daddy too!
I agree.
Everyone agrees. Take it.
Okay.
Uncles!
You can make a wish.
Mommy said that if you take care of this bunny, it'll grant your wishes.
Make a wish and cheer up!
Hina...
Thank you.
Thank you...
But that's your precious
stuffed animal, right?
So you should have it
grant your own wish.
Can I?
Yeah. It's enough for me that you're smiling.
Then I'll smile if it'll make you happy!
That looks heavy.
Let me take it.
Are you sure?
Take mine too.
I'll carry yours instead.
Sure.
What's this?
Hina's shampoo hat.
Now we won't have to worry.
That's just like you.
Yeah.
Uncles is strong!
Heavy!
pikapika to hikaru boku dake no sweet love
Sparkling and bright, this is my sweet love
kanaeru kana kono ai wa
Will it work out? My love, for you
michitekuru koi wa nani iro darou na
This love filling me up, what color is it?
sukoshi dake miseyou kana
Maybe I'll show you just a little
tokimeki to mawaru chiisana shunkan
Sparking and spinning, a little moment
wakiokoru iro ga aru
There's a color just breaking through
yurayura to yureru chiisana sekai wo
Rolling and swaying, this little world
sotto sotto iyashitekuru yo
Softly, softly, sweetening it up
ochame sugi na kimi no coloring
It's way too much for me, your coloring
boku no naka wo meguri meguru yo
It just goes round and round inside me
kurukuru mawaru odoru kimi no coloring
o
Round and round, spinning, dancing, your coloring
kakenukete yuku hajiketa soda mitai
o
It flies right past me, like a can of soda popping open
suteki na color no kimi wa boku wo kanjiteru kana
Your colors are wonderful, can you feel me now?
o
staying in your love
kirakira na amai love
A sparkling, sweet love
kurukuru mawaru odoru kimi no coloring
Round and round, spinning, dancing, your coloring
maiagaru kana yawarakana ichigo milk
Will it go high enough? A soft, strawberry milk
suteki na color no kimi wa nani wo egaiteru kana
Your colors are wonderful, what are you painting now?
staying in your love
kirakira na amai love
A sparkling, sweet love
This is bad!
Raika-san comes to our house, and
Sora Onee-chan's crush is in trouble!
Raika-san gets tied up, and she's in trouble?
And then something else happens, and we're all in trouble!
Thanks for Always Putting Up with Us
Next time: "Thanks for Always Putting Up with Us."
Be sure to watch it!
See you again
Artist:
Kirihara Izumi