All right, Uncle.
Take good care of Hina for us.
Got it.
Bye!
Okay, see you.
See you later!
Watch out for trains.
Hina, I think they should watch out for cars, not trains.
Trains go bump-bump.
We only have five minutes!
That's not good!
happy happy girl
itsu kara kana fushigi
When did it happen? It's so strange
kono mune no oku wa
The deepest parts of my heart
kimi no kakera bakari
Are filled with bits of you
doushiyou haato bousou
What should I do? My heart's gone crazy
doki doki deeto no souzou
Imagining a date that'll happen, maybe
kyunte tobihanechau kodou
Beating like it'll fly out of me
shizen ni hoppeta potte
Without thinking, my hands are on my cheeks
somaru no kakushitemo ki ga tsuite yo
But hiding them won't help, I already know
katamuiteku kokoro no kakudo
My heart's compass keeps turning to one place
omoi no shisen wa kimi muki
My feelings point right to you
mou koi wo shiteru
I'm already in love
happy happy girl
eeru wo okurasete
Let me cheer you on
kimi ga mezasu sora idaku
I want to see the same world as you
yume wo issho ni oikakeru yo
Let's chase our dreams together from now on
candy candy love
riido wa mada mada tayorinai kamo demo
I might not be very reliable right now
senaka ni yorisou
But if I can become
sasae ni ne naretara
Someone that you can lean on,
sotto sotto suki de itemo ii desu ka
Then can I keep on loving you like this?
A Little My Way
It's here!
We made it...
Just barely again today.
Shouldn't we start waking up earlier
and eating breakfast on our own?
If we did that in such a small room,
Uncle and Hina would definitely wake up.
That's true.
Uncle would want to start waking up early too.
Even after working late.
Silly Onii-chan.
Yeah.
Hey, Miu.
Has school calmed down a little?
Huh?
Yeah. Well...
I'm more worried about you.
Geez.
Next stop, Ikebukuro. Ikebukuro.
We're almost there...
Made it.
Yeah, we made it.
Finally...
It took an hour and a half to get here...
It's such a long trip.
Yeah, no kidding.
We have tomorrow off, so let's try to get through the day.
Let's do this.
Miu?
Yeah, you're right. Let's do our best.
That's from...
All right.
Good morning!
Morning.
Hey, Takanashi-san.
Miu-chan, good morning.
Good morning.
Morning.
There were cedars, cypresses, and all kinds of trees.
He quickly ran towards the... the...
Miu-chan, that was great.
Didn't you hate eggplants?
Did you know that eggplants are 198 yen per bag?
Huh?
Half a head of cabbage is a little over 100 yen.
Carrots are about 50 yen each.
Where's all of this coming from?
They're all pretty expensive.
So I can't waste any of them.
Miu-chan's been sleeping at school a lot lately.
She's coming to school from far away, right?
She probably has to wake up really early.
Maybe she doesn't have time to do her homework at home.
Miu-chan has a lot going on.
Her mom and dad passed away.
I feel sorry for her.
People feel sorry for me?
Hey, did you notice?
Her shoe was scuffed.
She's always dressed so nicely too.
I guess Miu-chan really does have it rough now.
Hello?
Is it all right if I walk around for a while?
Is something wrong?
It's nothing, really. I just wanted to.
Sure.
I'll tell Onii-chan, so take your time.
Okay, thanks.
Talk to you later.
What are you doing here?
Isn't school out already?
Yo.
Oh, it's just you, Nimura-san.
Sorry, did you think I was a cop?
Are you here in Ikebukuro for something?
No, I was free today and thought I'd go for a stroll.
And then I spotted you.
Miu-chan, are you free right now?
Huh?
How about we go on a date?
Wouldn't that make me your girlfriend, Nimura-san?
I like the sound of that.
Hmm... Let's see...
All right, just for this evening.
Only until 6 pm.
You have a time you have to leave by.
Kind of like Cinderella, huh?
Cinderella?
You're such a flatterer, Nimura-san.
What should I call you, then?
Miurin, Miyuyu.
Takamiu.
I guess Miu-chan works best.
Yes, that'd be fine.
So where should we go?
Okay, let's go to the ocean.
The ocean?
It's the ocean!
What do you think?
It wasn't what I had in mind,
but this isn't half bad.
Sounds like it was a good choice.
Stingrays look really cute when you see them from below.
Kiss! Uh... Mambo!
Puff!
Now for the sea lions!
You're next, Nimura-san.
Huh? Me?
All right.
That looks like...
Huh? Are you sure?
Don't worry about me.
Get whatever you want.
Let's see...
I'll have this, then.
Here you go. It's a coupon.
Oh, how considerate!
Thank you!
Miu-chan?
Oh, I got it!
Got what?
That sea lion looked like Sako-san!
Don't say that. I feel bad for the sea lion.
Besides, I think he looks more like a sea cucumber.
Um...
How's Uncle doing?!
What do you mean by how?
He has to take care of us, work, and now he's started school again.
I guess Segawa-chan's life does seem rather hectic.
Regardless, he's always upbeat.
People can't help wanting to lend him a hand.
They let him borrow their notes, and help him write his reports.
They really love Uncle, don't they?
They love you too, and acknowledge all the effort you put into staying together.
Raika-san loves cute things and can't take her eyes off of you girls.
The same goes for Sako-senpai.
Well, anyway, everyone in the RORI is hoping things will work out for Segawa-chan and you girls.
Thank you very much.
I guess that's Saturday afternoon for you.
People are having their dates on the way home from school.
That girl is cute.
She is.
I guess there are cute siblings like that, after all.
Siblings?
Hey, Nimura-san.
Huh?
We're the cutest couple in this place, aren't we?
Yeah.
Of course we are.
Take a look, Honey.
The world is jealous of us.
Thanks for treating me!
Okay, let's hit the next place.
Holding hands is a big event for a date.
You should only do it when it's the perfect moment for a girl.
"The perfect moment for a girl," huh?
Here we go!
It's perfect!
Three, two, one, cheese!
And stick.
Putting something like that on my cell phone...
It's like we're really dating.
That's because we really are.
Sorry about that.
We're really dating.
Let's keep going around the shops.
Miu-chan.
Here you go, Cinderella.
I'll get you a present to remember our date by.
There aren't any glass slippers, though.
Are you sure?
Of course.
I guess...
I'll take these.
They do have some!
How much are these?
M-Miu-chan, these are...
I was just kidding.
It's the thought that counts.
I'm Cinderella today.
I only want glass slippers.
Hey, could you come with me for a second?
Shoe Repair
Here you go.
It's all shiny!
No problems like this, right?
Here you go, Cinderella.
Thank you!
How is it, Cinderella?
Awesome!
It's already five...
What's wrong?
My ears are plugged.
You should yawn, then.
Sixtieth floor, observation deck.
Wow!
When you're so close you don't stop to look at things around you.
Yeah.
That's the apartment in Hachiouji...
And this is the house in Ikebukuro.
M-Miu-chan.
When I yawned, my ears got better.
Oh, you had tears in your eyes from yawning.
I was surprised.
Did you think I was crying because I missed my house back in Ikebukuro?
Yeah, I did.
Do I miss it?
The place I live now is far from the station,
the bath is small,
there are no laundry machines...
It's just one surprise after the next, really.
Sounds like there's almost nothing good about it at all.
At first, I really missed my old house,
but now...
My new house is smaller, so all the fun is packed together.
But I wouldn't mind if it were a little bigger.
Yeah.
I guess that's Nimura-san for you.
Thank you.
Have you noticed other things going on with me?
Do I... look sad?
Huh?
People pity me, and they worry about me...
I don't like people noticing those things.
That's because you're so considerate.
People tell me that a lot.
They say I don't really act like a kid, or that I seem grown up.
But I can't help being me.
You're fine the way you are, then.
You're wonderful in my eyes.
So you should just stay the way you are.
Nimura-san...
I should stay the way I am.
No wonder you're so popular.
You understand how women think.
Did you fall for me?
Sorry, but you're not my type.
Quite straightforward.
Learn a little from Nimura-san over here.
Uncle! Do you hear me?
We're all under one sky.
Yeah.
Evening has come, and the Sun is setting.
The bell of the mountain temple rings.
Let's all go home, everyone hand in hand.
Let's go home, along with the crows.
I'll be home soon!
I've made up my mind!
I'm going to break up with you!
I guess I'm the one being dumped.
I had a lot of fun today.
I had fun too.
I'm glad you were my prince.
Anyway, Cinderella...
is going to make her way home.
I'll walk you home.
It's fine.
Cinderella doesn't want anyone seeing her after the magic is gone.
See you!
Bye!
After all the children have returned home,
the big, round Moon stands in the sky.
When the birds are all dreaming,
the silver stars twinkle bright in the sky.
I'm home.
I'm tired.
Welcome back.
Thank you, Onee-chan.
I had a lot of fun.
Oh. That's good.
Welcome home.
You should take a bath.
Miu-chan, you're home late today. Did something happen?
It's a secret!
Right?
Keeping secrets is bad!
That's what the principal said!
Yeah, you shouldn't keep secrets from Uncles.
Girls are made of secrets,
Uncle.
Right?
Huh?
pikapika to hikaru boku dake no sweet love
Sparkling and bright, this is my sweet love
kanaeru kana kono ai wa
Will it work out? My love, for you
michitekuru koi wa nani iro darou na
This love filling me up, what color is it?
sukoshi dake miseyou kana
Maybe I'll show you just a little
tokimeki to mawaru chiisana shunkan
Sparking and spinning, a little moment
wakiokoru iro ga aru
There's a color just breaking through
yurayura to yureru chiisana sekai wo
Rolling and swaying, this little world
sotto sotto iyashitekuru yo
Softly, softly, sweetening it up
ochame sugi na kimi no coloring
It's way too much for me, your coloring
boku no naka wo meguri meguru yo
It just goes round and round inside me
kurukuru mawaru odoru kimi no coloring
o
Round and round, spinning, dancing, your coloring
kakenukete yuku hajiketa soda mitai
o
It flies right past me, like a can of soda popping open
suteki na color no kimi wa boku wo kanjiteru kana
Your colors are wonderful, can you feel me now?
o
staying in your love
kirakira na amai love
A sparkling, sweet love
kurukuru mawaru odoru kimi no coloring
Round and round, spinning, dancing, your coloring
maiagaru kana yawarakana ichigo milk
Will it go high enough? A soft, strawberry milk
suteki na color no kimi wa nani wo egaiteru kana
Your colors are wonderful, what are you painting now?
staying in your love
kirakira na amai love
A sparkling, sweet love
Sometimes even the smallest thing can make someone happy, right?
Especially if they're words said by someone you really care about.
Right, Onee-chan?
My Blue Sky
Next time: "My Blue Sky."
Watch it!
See you again
Artist
Aoki Ume