Good work today.
Same to you!
Episode 24
「Bandler's Demise」
How about some tea?
I will never forget this feeling,
and I will walk forth with courage.
I have to get home...
Spreading forth-
Stop!
Uh...
We made that part one octave lower.
We changed it after you left yesterday.
I'm sorry I forgot to tell you.
No, it's my fault.
How about we take a little break?
Okay!
I'm beat!
Um-
Everyone, the sheet music we're going
to use for the competition is complete.
It'll be tough, but we're aiming to win.
We're going to be practicing hard every day, so make sure you're ready.
Okay!
Practicing hard every day...
happy happy girl
itsu kara kana fushigi
When did it happen? It's so strange
kono mune no oku wa
The deepest parts of my heart
kimi no kakera bakari
Are filled with bits of you
doushiyou haato bousou
What should I do? My heart's gone crazy
doki doki deeto no souzou
Imagining a date that'll happen, maybe
kyunte tobihanechau kodou
Beating like it'll fly out of me
shizen ni hoppeta potte
Without thinking, my hands are on my cheeks
somaru no kakushitemo ki ga tsuite yo
But hiding them won't help, I already know
katamuiteku kokoro no kakudo
My heart's compass keeps turning to one place
omoi no shisen wa kimi muki
My feelings point right to you
mou koi wo shiteru
I'm already in love
happy happy girl
eeru wo okurasete
Let me cheer you on
kimi ga mezasu sora idaku
I want to see the same world as you
yume wo issho ni oikakeru yo
Let's chase our dreams together from now on
candy candy love
riido wa mada mada tayorinai kamo demo
I might not be very reliable right now
senaka ni yorisou
But if I can become
sasae ni ne naretara
Someone that you can lean on,
sotto sotto suki de itemo ii desu ka
Then can I keep on loving you like this?
My Blue Sky
I'm sorry I'm late!
I was wondering what was keeping you.
I'm really sorry.
Hina-chan, she's here.
Sora Nee-tan, you're late!
Sorry.
What about this?
Twenty-five.
And this?
Fifty-six.
Okay, so here's a question.
What's this?
Um...
Thirty-five.
That's right!
Yay! I did it!
English test answer sheet
percent
Forty-eight!
Don't say that out loud!
That's awesome, Sora Nee-tan!
This one's fifty-six.
I guess so...
Onee-chan, are your grades slipping?
Just a bit.
I guess we do have less time to study.
I'll work harder next
time, so don't worry.
Miu, how's school going for you?
I'd like to say it's going fine,
but I was feeling lightheaded
so I skipped P.E. today.
They told me I should go home early,
but I convinced them to let me rest in
the nurse's office instead.
I see.
You have it rough too, huh?
Don't tell Uncle!
Yeah, same here.
Hina wants secrets too!
It's nothing!
It's a secret!
Sora-chan, thanks for making my lunch.
Sorry I couldn't make any
good side dishes today.
What are you saying? It was delicious.
Keeping up with studying,
my club, the housework...
I can't do any of them right.
Once we start practicing
for the competition,
I won't have time to pick up Hina,
or help out around the house.
Resignation
Letter
I'd like to quit.
Resignation
Letter
Huh?
You went out of your way and asked me to join, but...
I'm sorry.
Wait. Hold on, Takanashi-san.
I know you're going
through a lot right now,
but do you really have to quit?
I'm useless.
I'm not very sharp, and I can't do anything very well.
I'd like to focus on things
at home right now.
I need to help my family.
Don't you like singing, though?
I do, and that's why I'm making this decision.
I'm sorry.
I made the right decision, didn't I?
Now I'll be able to focus on other things.
All right! One, two...
Ow!
Sora-chan, are you okay?
Did you burn yourself?
I'm fine.
No, you have to cool it under water.
I'm fine, really...
We can't have such a young girl
getting burn marks on her hands.
Come on...
This might be a little too much...
Onii-chan, that's burnt...
It's fine.
What should we...
...do now?
Which character is Atarashi-san playing?
A villain, Bandler,
but the Runa Runa defeated her the other day.
I see. That explains it.
Did something happen?
Last night, I ran into Atarashi-san.
Um, good evening.
Who're you?
Your neighbor, Segawa.
Are you okay?
My neighbor?!
My neighbor is Segawa-san.
Oh, Segawa-san, the neighbor.
Yeah, right.
U-Um...
It's true! You're my neighbor!
Y-Your voice is too loud!
I guess it's because you're a voice actress.
Voice actress?
No, no.
I'm not a voice actress.
I'm going to quit being a voice actress!
She's going to stop being a voice actress?
Yeah. That's what she said.
She's strong!
She's in a completely different
league from Bandler!
Don't think you're so great just 'cause you defeated Bandler.
Take this!
So Kurumi-san's going to quit...
She really liked her job too,
so I wish she wouldn't quit.
I'm sure Atarashi-san has her reasons!
It must be hard for her to continue!
That may be so, but still...
...with courage.
Spreading forth...
Into the blue sky.
Twinkle, twinkle, little star,
how I wonder what you are.
Up above the world so high...
Sora Nee-tan, you're not
going to sing too?
Let's sing together.
Maybe next time.
Why?
Why aren't you going to sing?
Hina-chan, are you hungry?
I am!
I'm going to go do the laundry.
See you.
See you!
Hello.
Are you... really going
to stop being a voice actress?
Onii-chan told me.
I don't have any work as a voice actress this month.
I went to a bunch of auditions,
but I couldn't get any parts.
And I made a promise with my parents that I'd go back to the countryside if I didn't get any work.
But Hina really likes you.
Hina really likes the Runa Runa.
I'm just an enemy,
and I got defeated.
See you.
Do you really have to quit?
Didn't you start because
you liked the job?
I'm such a hypocrite.
Special evening sale!
One pack of eggs, 88 yen!
First come, first serve!
All right. Now I can
make more fried eggs.
But how long is it going to take for me to actually make one properly?
Hello?
It's me.
Have you already done the shopping for dinner, Sora-chan?
No, I just got to the supermarket. I'm just about to start.
Good. Raika-san said she'd
cook dinner for us today.
Huh?
You've been making dinner every day lately.
You can relax today.
Sora-chan?
Fine! I will!
Raika-san is better than me, after all.
I'm going to have fun!
Banana Chocolate Cream
Strawberry Special
Peach Special
Banana
crêpe
I've always wanted to try this.
Five packs of eggs...
Would you like to hold him?
No, it's fine!
He told me to relax today...
Twinkle, twinkle, little star,
how I wonder what you are.
Up above the world so high...
Guess who.
Blow.
R-Raika-san?!
Hello.
Stare.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Sora-chan, you're kind.
Huh?
You're saying nothing's wrong because you don't want me to worry.
I want to worry about you, though.
I'll give you advice.
Come on.
It's not that big of a deal.
Things just aren't going that well.
That's all.
U-Um...
Cute...
Please don't tease me!
I'm really worrying over here!
You're really worrying,
so you're burning yourself out.
That's what it is to be 14.
Always trying your best.
That's Sora-chan.
Sora.
If you feel like crying,
do so in my arms!
Huh?
I read in a book that this is how you make women feel better.
Was that wrong?
You laughed.
Yay.
Fortune comes to those who smile.
Raika-san...
You can't fight on an empty stomach.
Let's go back and get some food.
Sure.
It's good!
Raika-san, you're awesome!
There sure is a lot of stew.
I might not be able to eat it all.
It'll last long, so don't worry about it.
You can keep it in the fridge
for about three days.
I froze some other
side dishes for you girls.
You're a lifesaver! Right, Onee-chan?
Huh?
Y-Yeah...
Thanks for the food!
See you.
Raika-san, thanks for today.
I'm not too good at cooking...
I was really bad at first too.
But everyone's happy when you
make good food for them.
So that's why I make food.
It's the same for you, right?
Yeah.
Then it's fine.
You'll be able to make good food.
Knowing you, you'll be fine.
You must be tired after working all day.
Have some tea.
Thanks.
I want milk!
Coming right up.
Huh? There's none here.
I forgot to buy some! I'll go get it now.
I'll go.
Onii-chan, you just got back from work.
You're tired, right?
I'll go.
Yeah, but it's dark out...
I'll be fine.
No, I'll go.
No, I'll be fine.
Go, go.
Go, the both of you.
Go.
Onii-chan, thank you.
You asked Raika-san to make food for us.
No, I'm supposed to be helping out,
but I've been working this whole time.
Sorry for leaving it all to you.
No, you're working so hard for us.
You're working hard for
the family too, right?
Yeah, but I still can't
cook fried eggs right.
I just end up causing problems.
That's fine.
I used to think I had to try not to
cause trouble for anyone at all.
I thought I had to do
everything on my own.
Then I ended up
living with you guys.
I started thinking making waves and having other people make waves isn't so bad after all.
That's what it means to help each other out.
I've been thinking,
maybe that's what a family is.
It's okay if I cause problems?
Surprising, huh?
Thank you, Onii-chan.
I wonder if he'll end up
liking my food someday too.
Is it okay for me to cause
problems for you again?
Is it okay if I'm not perfect?
If I'm just going to end up running around, burning myself out, then...
Um...
That resignation letter I gave you...
Here you are.
Huh?
I didn't give it to anyone.
But... why?
Because you're an integral
part of the chorus club.
I kept thinking about
how to get you back.
Choirmaster...
Thank you, Takanashi-san.
I don't think I'll be able
to come to club for a while,
but when I can sing again, can I come back?
Of course!
I'll be waiting for you.
Takanashi-san, I'm sure you can sing,
no matter where you are.
So you'll be fine.
Stay strong.
I will.
Atarashi-san.
I wanted to tell you something.
I got a part from an audition.
I got another job as a voice actress.
Really?
I won't be a main character.
I'll have a name,
but won't be a regular.
I might end up disappearing partway
through the series again too.
Congratulations!
Congratulations, Atarashi-san!
Thank you.
It's all thanks to you.
Huh?
I remembered after I talked to you...
I really like working as a voice actress.
I'm glad I didn't give up.
Yes!
That looks good!
Amazing, Onee-chan!
It looks good enough to sell!
R-Really?
I almost feel bad eating it.
I made it for you to eat, so hurry up and eat it.
I'll have some, then.
Yeah!
Twinkle, twinkle, little star,
how I wonder what you are.
Up above the world so high,
like a diamond in the sky.
Twinkle, twinkle, little star,
How I wonder what you are.
pikapika to hikaru boku dake no sweet love
Sparkling and bright, this is my sweet love
kanaeru kana kono ai wa
Will it work out? My love, for you
michitekuru koi wa nani iro darou na
This love filling me up, what color is it?
sukoshi dake miseyou kana
Maybe I'll show you just a little
tokimeki to mawaru chiisana shunkan
Sparking and spinning, a little moment
wakiokoru iro ga aru
There's a color just breaking through
yurayura to yureru chiisana sekai wo
Rolling and swaying, this little world
sotto sotto iyashitekuru yo
Softly, softly, sweetening it up
ochame sugi na kimi no coloring
It's way too much for me, your coloring
boku no naka wo meguri meguru yo
It just goes round and round inside me
kurukuru mawaru odoru kimi no coloring
o
Round and round, spinning, dancing, your coloring
kakenukete yuku hajiketa soda mitai
o
It flies right past me, like a can of soda popping open
suteki na color no kimi wa boku wo kanjiteru kana
Your colors are wonderful, can you feel me now?
o
staying in your love
kirakira na amai love
A sparkling, sweet love
kurukuru mawaru odoru kimi no coloring
Round and round, spinning, dancing, your coloring
maiagaru kana yawarakana ichigo milk
Will it go high enough? A soft, strawberry milk
suteki na color no kimi wa nani wo egaiteru kana
Your colors are wonderful, what are you painting now?
staying in your love
kirakira na amai love
A sparkling, sweet love
Where are you going, Onii-chan?
We made it this far.
Is it over already?
I'll be fine.
I'm prepared for what'll happen.
Next time: "You're not There When I Want You to Be..."
You're not There When I Want You to Be...
Please wait for me.
See you again
Artist
Izumi Tsubasu