I know it's strange to say this about myself,
but my life has played out like a drama.
Segawa Yuuta
A
One of my earliest memories was losing my parents.
My sister was strong enough to raise me in their stead.
But then, I lost her too.
Recently, I fell in love. I was going to have a great time living on my own, but now, in my small room...
Huh?
Why...
I can't move...
Good morning, Uncle.
G-Good morning, Miu-chan.
Just stay like that for a little longer.
I think my sister will wake up soon.
Huh?
What?!
Th-The way she's clutching onto me isn't good at all...!
Isn't that nice?
You get to wake up with a cute girl hanging onto you.
No, that's not the problem here.
Potty...
Okay.
Wai-
Wait a secon-!
G-Good morning...
No!
Ow!
Bawmp! Bawmp!
It's a bump, not a bawmp.
You didn't have to hit him.
But...
Don't worry. It'll go away soon enough.
Huh? What's wrong?
What are you doing?!
I'm just changing...
Do it over there!
I can understand if it's you three
changing, but I don't care if you see me.
When it comes to girls, you lack delicacy, Uncle.
You think so?
Well, okay.
Then...
No!
You have to wait for an hour after a girl uses it!
Oh yeah, I forgot about that...
I'm hungry.
I forgot about breakfast.
There's no food?
I'm sorry, Hina!
I'll hurry up and change!
happy happy girl
itsu kara kana fushigi
When did it happen? It's so strange
kono mune no oku wa
The deepest parts of my heart
kimi no kakera bakari
Are filled with bits of you
doushiyou haato bousou
What should I do? My heart's gone crazy
doki doki deeto no souzou
Imagining a date that'll happen, maybe
kyunte tobihanechau kodou
Beating like it'll fly out of me
shizen ni hoppeta potte
Without thinking, my hands are on my cheeks
somaru no kakushitemo ki ga tsuite yo
But hiding them won't help, I already know
katamuiteku kokoro no kakudo
My heart's compass keeps turning to one place
omoi no shisen wa kimi muki
My feelings point right to you
mou koi wo shiteru
I'm already in love
happy happy girl
eeru wo okurasete
Let me cheer you on
kimi ga mezasu sora idaku
I want to see the same world as you
yume wo issho ni oikakeru yo
Let's chase our dreams together from now on
candy candy love
riido wa mada mada tayorinai kamo demo
I might not be very reliable right now
senaka ni yorisou
But if I can become
sasae ni ne naretara
Someone that you can lean on,
sotto sotto suki de itemo ii desu ka
Then can I keep on loving you like this?
Wonderful Life
H-Hi there.
Here we are.
This much?
You bought a ton of stuff.
Anyway, this should be enough for now.
I don't know what everyone likes,
so I just bought a bit of everything.
Panty!
Huh? Panties?
She means party.
There's a lot of food, so I guess she remembered her birthday party.
Yeah.
How much was it?
Huh?
We'll pay for our share.
Don't worry about that.
But...
Really, you don't have to worry about it.
I have to go to work, so you all eat together.
Make sure you lock up.
If someone comes by, don't open the door no matter what.
Okay!
Why?
It'd be a huge problem if you three got lost!
And what if you run into a bad guy?
I see...
Got it?
Okay!
I'll be back before it gets dark.
Okay?
Okay!
See you, Uncle.
See you!
See you later.
See you, huh?
All right.
You're still upset?
You're the one who snuggled up to him while you were asleep.
I-It's not that...
He just left without eating breakfast...
So you wanted to eat with him.
N-Not really.
It's long!
So that's how much it cost.
If this is how much he's going to be spending, then we might not last the week.
What's that?
It's the money Daddy and Yuri-san left us before they went on their trip.
We should pay for this.
But Uncle probably wants to keep his pride.
I need to increase my work hours.
But if I come back too late, they'll get worried.
I'm going to raise them myself.
I know it'll be tough, but I'll get more jobs...
What about college?
What should I do?
Good morning.
Raika-san, what are you doing here?
No way... Did she come to see me?
Whoa, no way.
I never thought I'd run into you here.
What a surprise.
I'm, like, super happy to see you.
As monotone as ever, huh?
Someone told you to say that, didn't they?
Oda-kun, put more emotion into it.
I knew it was you, Sako-senpai.
Wait. You're here too, Nimura?!
Yo.
What a coincidence, Segawa-kun.
We members of the Roadway Observation
Research Institute must be tied together by fate.
No, you've just been waiting for me there, haven't you?
Do you need something?
You haven't been coming to the RORI.
They can't just have their new members not show up.
You joined, so you need to come.
Sorry, I've been a little busy.
That smell...
Do I smell, or something?
The faint scent of a sweet angel...
Such a pure aroma...
This is...
The scent of a young girl!
For a guy that lives by himself
He can smell that?!
in an apartment close to the college...
who works part-time at a restaurant and doesn't get much time off...
I haven't said anything about the girls.
to smell of an angel in the morning...
This guy isn't normal.
Raika-san, I'm very sorry for asking this out of the blue, but...
Sako-senpai, I'll come to the RORI today so...
You can come whenever.
Segawa-kun!
I have some questions as to what kind of life-
Oda-kun, what are you... so suddenly...
Sako-senpai's really dangerous!
I can't let him meet my kids no matter what!
A small room makes cleaning easy.
There's a problem with this room.
What is it?
It's simple, but it's not cute at all.
There's nothing exciting in here.
Exciting?
Where's the exciting?
Hina!
Ouch...
I need something to wipe this up!
It's even messier now...
We also need to wash our clothes...
Yeah.
Let's see...
There's no washing machine.
How does Uncle do his laundry?
Does he wash it by hand?
He probably takes it to the cleaners.
Segawa Yuuta
A
No!
Uncles said no!
We'll see the bad guys!
Would you be scared if you ran into a bad guy by yourself?
Yes...
But what if we were with you?
Nope!
Right?
We need to do the laundry for Uncle.
Okay! Let's go!
If we run into any bad guys, we'll be fine since since we're together.
Let's do our best.
A bad guy!
No, she's not!
H-Hello.
Hello.
Let's go.
A
White Delivery
Cleaning
Huh? You can't?
You can't clean underwear?
You can't anywhere.
She's right.
Onee-chan, underwear isn't written on here.
What should we do...
If you need to wash underwear,  head over there.
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
A
Large-scale
Laundromat
I'm really grateful to Uncle.
Me too.
He's the reason we can even be together.
But this is a completely different story.
I will not let you wash his underwear with our stuff.
But it'll cost more if we do it separately.
Another 200 yen...
If we keep this up for a month, it'll add up to 6,000 yen.
We'll just have to deal with it.
We're going to live together,
so we have to do our best and wash everything together...
But if his underwear ends up touching mine...
No.
Absolutely not!
Spending this 200 yen was an absolute necessity.
I'm sorry, Uncle.
Vegetables!
100 yen?
All this only costs 100 yen?
That's really cheap.
Is this a store?
Look over here.
It's a flower.
Cute!
Exciting, right?
Yeah!
What are you doing, Onee-chan?
Buying ingredients.
I'll make dinner.
Huh? Have you ever cooked before?
I did during cooking practice in home economics.
I helped Yuri-san out too.
If we buy these vegetables and cook with them, we can save a lot of money!
Now we'll be able to get that 200 yen back.
I don't think I can stop her.
Are you cooking dinner already?
I want to make lots of things.
If it gets cold, we can just warm it up in the microwave.
What should I make...?
Are you sure you can do this?
I-I'll be fine!
Oh, I know. I'll cook the rice first.
The flowers are nice, but we need a vase...
Torotoro, Torotoro-san.
Toroto-
Hi-Hina, what are you drawing?!
Exciting!
Torotoro-san.
Okay, we're done with Torotoro!
Yay, Torotoro!
What are you doing?!
Hey, Miu, you'd better wipe that off!
You can't erase this.
Huh?
They're permanent markers.
Since there's already stuff on the wall, we might as well make it cute.
I'm not... so sure about that...
Torotoro-san!
I'll just pretend I didn't see that...
What are you making?
Uh...
Stir-fry... I guess.
Bingo! That's right!
Coming!
Hey, Onee-chan! You can't answer that!
Oh, right.
Shh...
Who is it?
Shh!
Be quiet!
Why?
Shh!
It might be a bad guy!
I'm scared!
Hey, Hina!
That's hot!
Onee-chan, are you okay?!
I'm fine. Hina!
Um, you seem busy, so I'll come back later.
Sorry about that.
Where's the strainer?
Hina'll help!
Then could you put these on the table over there?
Okay!
We need to clean...
Ow!
Hello? Sora-chan?
It's me. Are you fine over there?
Y-Yeah.
We're totally fine.
What time do you think you'll be home?
Sorry, I'm going to be late today.
Huh?
Okay...
Got it... Talk to you later.
Onee-chan?
Uncle's going to be late, so we should start eating without him.
Uncles won't eat with us?
So we didn't really have to go out of our way to make dinner.
We still have leftover food from this morning.
Let's make something.
We don't have to eat together.
We should do it for Uncle, because he's working so hard.
But the leftover food from this morning...
That's the food Uncle bought for us.
So we should be the ones to make his food.
That double shift was pretty rough.
This is the real deal.
The main course will be salisbury steak.
It'll be fine this time!
It's burning!
It's flying!
O-Onee-chan!
C-C-Calm down!
I'm back.
What are you doing?!
As long as you understand.
I'm just glad you're all safe.
We managed to make some rice balls...
But we messed up a lot...
This is supposed to be salisbury steak.
This is supposed to be stir-fry.
You don't have to force yourself to eat it.
I'll eat what's burnt.
I'm happy.
This is a pretty good meal.
What is this?
Strawberry cake.
Strawberry?!
Thank you!
Then I'll have some!
This might be nice.
Gotta pee!
What? Again?
Will I ever be able to use my own bathroom again?
Oh, Sora-chan. What's up?
Well...
Thanks for getting upset with me.
Was I too harsh?
But why did you buy us cake?
It cost a lot to buy us breakfast.
I told you not to worry about money.
I can't help but worry!
Of course I'd worry.
Sora-chan...
I'm glad you bought a lot of stuff for us,
but you won't be able to keep this up.
Thanks for worrying about me.
That cake was being sold for cheap since the store was closing.
But...
I was happy.
Huh?
I was happy that someone was there to say goodbye to me in the morning.
That's why I...
I really...
wanted to do something
that would make everyone happy, just for today.
But I didn't say goodbye to you.
I heard you, loud and clear.
Uncle...
We can start worrying about money tomorrow.
It'll all work out if we try.
I...
I didn't say it before, but...
What is it?
Welcome home.
I'm back.
Hina, you need to take a bath soon.
Okay, Hina, you wanna take a bath together?
Yeah!
Let's all take a bath together!
What?
Onee-chan, why don't you?
Miu!
I love you.
Good night.
pikapika to hikaru boku dake no sweet love
Sparkling and bright, this is my sweet love
kanaeru kana kono ai wa
Will it work out? My love, for you
michitekuru koi wa nani iro darou na
This love filling me up, what color is it?
sukoshi dake miseyou kana
Maybe I'll show you just a little
tokimeki to mawaru chiisana shunkan
Sparking and spinning, a little moment
wakiokoru iro ga aru
There's a color just breaking through
yurayura to yureru chiisana sekai wo
Rolling and swaying, this little world
sotto sotto iyashitekuru yo
Softly, softly, sweetening it up
ochame sugi na kimi no coloring
It's way too much for me, your coloring
boku no naka wo meguri meguru yo
ku
It just goes round and round inside me
na
gu
wo
yo
kurukuru mawaru odoru kimi no coloring
o
Round and round, spinning, dancing, your coloring
kakenukete yuku hajiketa soda mitai
o
It flies right past me, like a can of soda popping open
suteki na color no kimi wa boku wo kanjiteru kana
Your colors are wonderful, can you feel me now?
o
staying in your love
kirakira na amai love
A sparkling, sweet love
kurukuru mawaru odoru kimi no coloring
Round and round, spinning, dancing, your coloring
maiagaru kana yawarakana ichigo milk
Will it go high enough? A soft, strawberry milk
suteki na color no kimi wa nani wo egaiteru kana
Your colors are wonderful, what are you painting now?
staying in your love
kirakira na amai love
A sparkling, sweet love
Miu here!
The wet middle school girl: Sora Onee-chan.
Was it a forbidden desire that led her there?
Or was it something else?
Next time: "What Happened to the Girl."
What Happened to the Girl
Look forward to it!
See you again
Artist
Miyano Hirotsugu