happy happy girl
itsu kara kana fushigi
When did it happen? It's so strange
kono mune no oku wa
The deepest parts of my heart
kimi no kakera bakari
Are filled with bits of you
doushiyou haato bousou
What should I do? My heart's gone crazy
doki doki deeto no souzou
Imagining a date that'll happen, maybe
kyunte tobihanechau kodou
Beating like it'll fly out of me
shizen ni hoppeta potte
Without thinking, my hands are on my cheeks
somaru no kakushitemo ki ga tsuite yo
But hiding them won't help, I already know
katamuiteku kokoro no kakudo
My heart's compass keeps turning to one place
omoi no shisen wa kimi muki
My feelings point right to you
mou koi wo shiteru
I'm already in love
happy happy girl
eeru wo okurasete
Let me cheer you on
kimi ga mezasu sora idaku
I want to see the same world as you
yume wo issho ni oikakeru yo
Let's chase our dreams together from now on
candy candy love
riido wa mada mada tayorinai kamo demo
I might not be very reliable right now
senaka ni yorisou
But if I can become
sasae ni ne naretara
Someone that you can lean on,
sotto sotto suki de itemo ii desu ka
Then can I keep on loving you like this?
Story No. 5875
Sora-chan's Purity at Risk?!
I'm Sora.
As strange as it sounds, I'm stuck in this situation.
We're in here, by the way.
It's all Miu's fault.
This morning, I was going through my clothes
thinking about what to do with the clothes
I'd grown too big for but didn't want to throw out.
When all of a sudden, Miu walks in.
Onee-chan's rolling around
in her underwear because you aren't around!
Miu!
She was on the phone with Onii-chan.
Oh, you have the graveyard shift tonight, right?
Miu!
'ello.
Onii-chan had the graveyard shift at work, so he asked Raika-san to take care of us.
I need to get back at her, Raika-san!
I told her that I wanted to get back at Miu, and...
Okay.
I brought two costumes.
You can use one of them.
This was what Raika-san envisioned.
I changed into my costume and waited in the heat.
Onee-chan! Raika-san!
Huh? That's weird...
Coming!
Huh?
Shiori-san!
Um, so...
A friend let me borrow a horror movie,
but I'm too scared to watch by myself...
I was hoping someone would watch it with me...
Is Yuuta-san home?
Sorry, but he's at work right now.
I don't know where Onee-chan went either.
Could I watch it with you?
Hina!
Lucky.
We couldn't put up with the heat any longer,
so we ended up like this.
It's so stupid.
Cheer up, Sora-chan.
After more than ten minutes of brainstorming,
I've come up with the best way to escape from this situation.
That's great.
What do we do?
We force the door open by breaking the duster.
Wait, don't!
Well, that duster was Yuri-san's...
Okay, twirl, twirl!
And dust, dust!
I wanna try too!
Here.
So, if we could avoid breaking it...
Let's try something else, then.
We catch the duster with a string.
Well?
Um...
But we don't have any string...
Don't worry.
The crack is wider at the top.
We pull the string back in from below,
and lift.
Target locked.
One, two, and three.
Ouch.
Mission failed.
Sora-chan.
One, two, and three!
What do we do now?
Well...
They're really big...
Oh, I'm sorry.
Sorry.
I can't hold myself up much longer.
Sora-chan, have you ever kissed someone?
No...
We need to save your first kiss, then.
But...
She's so close...
I'm home.
Huh?
Where'd everyone go?
I even finished my work early so I didn't have to work the graveyard shift.
Oh no...
Her boobs are rubbing up against mine...
It feels weird...
What's happening to me?
Is Raika-san going to take it?
My first...
I've got it.
Sora-chan? Raika-san?
Huh?!
Success.
Why are you both naked?!
Onii-chan!
Uncle?!
Yuuta.
Miu-chan's Fashion Advice
Story No. 7522
Miu-chan's Fashion Advice.
Wait, this is that famous cake from that famous store in Shiinamachi?
That's right!
The legendary cake that has people lining up
and a reservation list filled half a year in advance!
Wow!
I can't wait to see it!
Where is everyone?
Uncle's at school, and Onee-chan and Hina are out for the day.
How about we eat this ourselves, then?
Oh, man. What kind is it?
A full gâteau aux fraise.
It's so pretty!
Right?!
I want to try this middle part—
I'm so sorry.
I'll get something to clean—
No, wait!
Huh? Miu-chan?
It'd be a huge waste! We gotta eat it up!
It's way too good!
I-I'm glad you like it, Miu-chan.
Have some too.
Sorry.
It's okay.
Now for a little more!
I look forward to it this Sunday.
What about the cake?
I put an order in today.
It's special, so we won't eat it for a little longer.
It wasn't much, but still.
I'm so sorry. That cake must've been really expensive...
It's fine.
It was delicious.
Yeah!
I'll wash you now.
Okay, turn around.
Okay!
You've got a great body, Shiori-chan.
And your boobs are nice too!
Huh?!
I think I'm pretty normal...
Excuse me!
What?
If you put them together and showed a little cleavage, the guys'd be all over you!
No, I don't need that!
It might be a little rude coming from a kid, but you're so cute!
Don't tease me!
I'm not teasing you.
The guys like you, don't they?
No way.
Not at all.
And I don't care for them anyway.
You don't need all the guys to like you.
You just want a special one to like you, right?
No, I don't...
But most of the stuff you wear is really plain, Shiori-san.
You think so?
Oh, I got it!
Shiori-san...
Let's try on all sorts of clothes until yours dry!
M-Miu-chan, why am I blindfolded?
It'll leave a bigger impression on you if you don't see until you're all dressed!
That may be so, but...
All right, first outfit! Let's go!
Put it on quick, okay?
Okay, we'll start with something grown-up!
Like this! Wow, Yuri-san, aggressive!
One, two!
Ta-da!
No way...
Is this really me?
Isn't it nice?
It really is!
...I think.
Let's try something friskier next!
There's more?!
Of course!
Next up is this!
Ta-da!
This one's really embarrassing!
But you're always such a prim and proper class rep.
Everyone'll love it if you go a little wild!
Y-You think so?
Try doing a class rep kind of pose and see!
Hey, you boys!
I think I like it...
Right?!
Now...
Blindfold again!
I wonder what else we have...
Oh, wow!
This'll be great!
What is it?
Don't you worry!
But... you're scaring me...
Now then!
No way!
I knew it was something like this! It's way too small!
It's from when Yuri-san was in middle school.
It's like you're Segawa Shiori-san when you're wearing that!
Huh?
Segawa Shiori...
Exactly. From now on, you'll be known as Segawa Shiori, not Kitahara Shiori.
Y-Yuuta-san?
Does that mean...
We're married.
And we'll be together forever.
Um...
B-But...
Wh-Why a swimsuit?
It turns me on.
That's right, Shiori-san.
We'll all be together forever.
Huh?
"We'll all"? What do you mean?
It's obvious, isn't it?
Onii-chan belongs to everyone.
Huh?
Me too!
Hina!
Hina?
I'm in middle school, but I'll try my best!
You're all so cute!
All right!
Hugs for everyone! Come on!
Yay!
No! No! No!
I'm sorry.
You don't like the dress?
Oh, no. I didn't mean no to the dress...
Something else...
You look so cute when you're flustered.
C'mon, Miu-chan.
I wonder if I'll get to wear a dress like this one day.
Of course you will.
I bet you'll fall in love with someone wonderful,
and wear a dress you designed yourself.
That sounds great!
I'll do that!
Will you make my dress too, then?
Thank you for your order!
You're so cute!
All right!
It's your turn next!
Be a good girl now!
Wait, hang on!
That's—
There we go!
I'm home.
Thank you for having me.
Oh, good evening.
Come and join us, Onii-chan.
Sounds good.
What's this?!
Wow, wow!
As far as yukata go, Shiori-san's in the lead.
But two years from now, Onee-chan'll be just as good.
I wonder how thing's will be in ten years.
I can't wait to see!
Story No. 7523
Hina-chan's Big Adventure
Hina-chan's Big Adventure.
Looks like it's raining, Bunny.
But it'll be sunny when we get there!
Bye-bye!
Hina, time to wake—
Huh?
Hina?
That was scary!
We're dry, though!
Did you find her?
No...
I went all the way to the station.
I checked around the park.
I wonder where she went.
I hope she's okay...
Hello?
Karaoke
I was coming home from work this morning,
and ran into Sako-senpai, who wanted to do some karaoke.
You free today?
Sorry.
Actually...
What?!
Segawa-kun! We'll help look!
Um...
Which way was it?
If you take the subway from the station, then maybe ten minutes?
You can get there if you turn right at that one restaurant and keep going too.
But walking would take forever.
Oh, yeah! Turn right!
Which way is right?
I'll go this way!
I couldn't find her.
Where else could she have gone?
Why would she do this?
And today, of all days.
Let's keep looking a little longer.
If we still can't find her, we'll call the police.
The rain stopped!
Y'know, Bunny. They say it's always sunny above the clouds!
Isn't it weird?
Look!
The rainbow's so pretty!
Wow!
Hina-chan!
Shiori Nee-tan?
Hina-chan, are you alone?
Yeah!
I'm going to go on a ferris wheel!
Ferris wheel?
Yeah! At Egg Town!
Egg Town? You mean the theme park?
Yeah, yeah!
I need to go!
Bye-bye, Shiori-tan!
Wait, it's the other way!
Huh?
I'll take you there.
Oh? Thank you so much, Shiori-chan.
D-Don't mention it.
She said she asked if you could go today, but you said you wouldn't be able to.
If you're all busy, I can go with her.
That's not it.
Today's my sister's... Hina's mother's birthday.
So we were going to visit her grave with a cake.
But we didn't know if Hina understood yet, so...
I see.
I'm sorry.
I even promised to take her there...
Oh, Hina-chan's done eating.
I'll take her on the ferris wheel, then back home.
All done!
The rice ball was yummy!
That's good!
Let's get going.
Yeah!
It's the ferris wheel!
Hina-chan, don't run! It's dangerous!
The line's pretty long.
But you can wait, right?
Yeah!
We're almost there.
Hina!
Uncles?
Sora Nee-tan? Miu Nee-tan?
Hina, why'd you leave the house without telling us?
We were all really worried!
U-Um...
Now say you're sorry.
Did you want to ride it that badly?
Fine, then.
Let's all ride it together.
But Uncles didn't line up, so we have to line up again.
Is that okay?
I'm sorry!
Ages
Children under the age of 7 must be accompanied by a guardian.
Guardian Required
I haven't been on a ferris wheel in forever!
I wonder how many years it's been for me.
Look! It's the Skytree!
I wonder where Tokyo Tower is!
You're really quiet, Hina-chan.
You know, today's Mommy's birthday!
So I'm gonna show her my drawing!
Hina...
Mommy's in Heaven, so I need to be in the sky too!
Happy birthday, Mommy!
I'm doing great!
Hina...
Huh?
What is it, Uncles?
Let's all wish her a happy birthday, Onii-chan.
Yeah.
Yay!
You can have my seat, then.
Thanks.
Come on, Onee-chan. Over here.
Okay.
One, two...
Happy birthday, Nee-san!
Happy birthday, Mommy!
Happy birthday, Yuri-san!
Nee-san, are you watching us?
Hina-chan's grown up to be such a good girl.
I'm sure it's a big relief for you.
I'll watch over the girls until they've grown up.
Yeah.
Until they're all married...
I'll do my best.
I wanted to ride too.
With Hina-chan.
What do you mean, emergency maintenance?!
I was supposed to be riding a ferris wheel with my innocent fairy Hina-chan right now!
There, there.
Give me back my fairy time!
Senpai, cut it out!
pikapika to hikaru boku dake no sweet love
Sparkling and bright, this is my sweet love
kanaeru kana kono ai wa
Will it work out? My love, for you
michitekuru koi wa nani iro darou na
This love filling me up, what color is it?
sukoshi dake miseyou kana
Maybe I'll show you just a little
tokimeki to mawaru chiisana shunkan
Sparking and spinning, a little moment
wakiokoru iro ga aru
There's a color just breaking through
yurayura to yureru chiisana sekai wo
Rolling and swaying, this little world
sotto sotto iyashitekuru yo
Softly, softly, sweetening it up
ochame sugi na kimi no coloring
It's way too much for me, your coloring
boku no naka wo meguri meguru yo
It just goes round and round inside me
kurukuru mawaru odoru kimi no coloring
o
Round and round, spinning, dancing, your coloring
kakenukete yuku hajiketa soda mitai
o
It flies right past me, like a can of soda popping open
suteki na color no kimi wa boku wo kanjiteru kana
Your colors are wonderful, can you feel me now?
o
staying in your love
kirakira na amai love
A sparkling, sweet love
kurukuru mawaru odoru kimi no coloring
Round and round, spinning, dancing, your coloring
maiagaru kana yawarakana ichigo milk
Will it go high enough? A soft, strawberry milk
suteki na color no kimi wa nani wo egaiteru kana
Your colors are wonderful, what are you painting now?
staying in your love
kirakira na amai love
A sparkling, sweet love